THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
Your life is worth more than that car.
Don't let anyone make you feel worthless.
Watch Saikhim closely.
Don't let her contact such men again.
I think I'm pregnant.
Why is this happening to me?
Even if I had nothing but my body,
you still couldn't beat me
because you never let her be free,
so she flies back to me, the scumbag.
If you don't mind,
my son wants to marry Saikhim.
You think your son is a match
for my daughter?
Even if he died and were reborn,
I doubt he'd be enough.
-Would you live here with me?
-Who would I be to you here?
You'd be my lady.
If he's arrested,
Saikhim has nowhere to go.
Am I bad enough for you now?
My only mistake was falling
for a woman like you!
LOVE… HAS TURNED INTO HATE
SEVEN YEARS LATER
We've found the island's owner.
I'm heading there now.
They can offer a price first.
PHUKET
Please prepare a rough appraisal.
I'll use it in the negotiation. Thank you.
This way, Miss Saikhim.
What are you doing?
Sending a lantern to my dad in heaven.
I see. This lantern can fly that far?
When I miss my dad,
I release lanterns here.
Whatever wish I make,
it always comes true.
Your dad must be so proud of you.
Do you know someone in heaven, miss?
You can send them a letter.
I don't know if he's still up there.
It's been seven years.
Miracles do happen, miss.
THE CAR IS READY
Is it much farther?
We're not halfway yet, miss.
It's odd to build a house on this island.
Oh, great.
What now?
What happened?
The gas might be leaking.
I guess I'll go get some more.
I'm not sure if they have any.
In that case, I'll go on alone.
Please take care of the car
and pick me up when it's ready.
I'll be at that house.
Sure, miss.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Excuse me.
How far
from here is the island owner's house?
Excuse me.
Gla.
Please excuse me. I must be seeing things.
Why do you look like someone I once knew?
Someone you knew?
Just like him.
Really?
The world isn't that small.
He's dead.
You do look like you've seen a ghost.
I'm sorry, you see,
I'm looking for the island's owner.
Do you know them?
I heard they own
a holiday home on this island.
Everyone knows them.
Could you please take me to them?
Please take this for your trouble.
Thank you so much.
Are you sure this is it?
Hello.
Is anyone there?
I've reached their house,
but I haven't seen them.
It seems an odd home.
I didn't expect them to live here.
Pick me up here.
Wait, mister.
The island owner isn't here.
How can I reach them?
You'll know when you see 'em.
Wait.
1,000
Thanks.
When the astrologer said
our destinies were incompatible,
I got so anxious.
My element is earth.
But these colors
are inauspicious for me.
If we could just add some red,
it would enhance my confidence.
I want some bold colors
for that expensive look.
Could you please modify the palette?
Okay, I'll update the design.
I'm sorry to make you update it again.
It's only a small tweak, right?
Certainly. We do our best for our clients.
Thank you so much.
KHIM
Why so many design updates?
This is like the millionth time.
Which grandpa or auntie
told them to do this?
I've made and burnt down
almost a hundred models now.
They know that I design houses, right?
I can't fix their destinies.
Aren't you used to it?
No, not yet.
Come on. You're amazing, Lita.
This will be easy for you.
Yeah, of course.
So did you call me
to talk about something specific?
I'm doing some business in Phuket.
Something odd happened.
I saw Gla here.
Gla who?
Wait. Do you mean that guy?
He's so much like him.
Even his voice is like his.
I thought it was him.
But he died long ago, Khim.
Well, exactly. That's why I'm wondering.
How can someone look so much like him?
The only thing missing is his tattoo.
Maybe he's his twin
or some other family member?
Gla only had a little sister.
So did he recognize you?
No.
He didn't know me at all.
So don't worry about it.
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
So are we going to fly
to Hong Kong together tonight?
I guess I'll be late.
I might have to get on a later flight.
But I'll be there tomorrow before noon.
Tell Tan for me, Lita.
Hey! This is a huge event.
Don't you dare miss it.
Hello? Khim?
What?
I brought your boss to the island's owner.
She said you can just leave.
They'll take a helicopter to the airport.
Nobody turned up.
I guess we missed each other.
Can I leave a letter and my business card
for the island owner?
Your driver is at the beach.
Get in the car. I'll drive you there.
Come on.
Are you from here?
Have you been here long?
No.
What are you doing here?
Did the owner of the island hire you?
Has anyone ever tried to buy this island?
No one.
Really? You think the owner would sell it?
Fifty million.
They'd sell it for just fifty million?
No. I'm talking about the ransom.
What do you mean?
Pay me fifty million, and I'll let you go.
What?
Will they still care about Miss Saikhim
now she costs so much more?
Will your dad pick you
or the money this time?
Who are you exactly?
What do you want?
-Mr. Sansern, please help!
-Miss Khim?
What's wrong?
I've abducted her!
Pay me fifty million and I'll let her go.
Where are you now?
On her way to hell!
-What the hell are you doing?
-Taking you home with me, darling!
Thank goodness.
Why doesn't he pick up?
Where did he go to find gas?
Your driver is at the beach.
Get in, I'll drive you there.
I… can drive myself.
Can you?
I can drive it.
Are you sure?
BOAT CAPTAIN
Help me!
Is anyone there? Help me!
TANTAI
I DON'T KNOW IF HEAVEN IS REAL,
BUT I WANTED TO WRITE TO SAY HELLO…
I don't know if heaven is real,
but I wanted to write to say hello.
I want you to know I still remember you.
Seven years is a long time,
but for you up there,
it's probably just the blink of an eye.
They say
some people stay in your heart
longer than they're with you.
I just understood that saying today.
Those four months
changed my life forever…
so I wanted to write to ask this.
If we could change one thing in this life,
would you make sure we never met?
I wish I could know
whether our answers were the same.
Hey, kid.
This is your dad.
I'm working in the forests.
It's pitch dark,
but the sky is full of stars.
Should we call our baby Temfah?
If it's a girl, we could call her Temfah.
But if it's a boy,
could we call him Nannam?
Have you guys met each other yet?
Wait for me, okay?
I'll follow you there.
Please help. She's hurt.
She can't take a helicopter now.
It's safer to leave tomorrow morning.
Please stay here, miss.
At least there's electricity here.
Thank you for helping me.
Maybe if you just rest,
you'll feel better tomorrow.
Please take care of her.
We'll come back tomorrow morning.
Whose house is this? Why are you here?
My phone battery died.
Can I use your phone to call my family?
There are no phones here.
Do you have a phone charger?
Take a pill and sleep.
I'll see you off tomorrow.
If you need anything,
I'm sleeping out there.
Sorry.
That number can't be reached right now.
Miss Khim hasn't called yet.
She must be on the island.
Why did you let her go alone?
This isn't the first time
Khim has disappeared.
Maybe she's just out there having fun.
But I think this time,
she won't be as unfortunate as last time.
Go to Phuket now.
I need to hear from Saikhim tonight.
Yes, sir.
You don't need to worry.
She's not a little kid anymore.
If this company had
trustworthy people sharing the workload,
Khim wouldn't have to work so hard alone.
She went looking for trouble.
How dare he blame me for this?
Excuse me.
Why do you look like someone I once knew?
The world isn't that small.
He's dead.
You do look like you've seen a ghost.
Gla, calm down.
Gla, listen to me! Gla, calm down!
Please calm down.
Gla.
Gla, don't go yet.
Gla, don't run away again!
Gla, stay. Gla, don't run away again.
Gla, stay!
Please don't do this.
Do I seem that awful?
It hurts like I'm being stabbed
when you look at me like that.
Wanna know how much it hurts?
-Please let go.
-Khim.
Gla.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Didn't mean it?
You don't know what I've been through.
Gla!
Gla.
Wake up, son.
Hold on a bit longer.
Be strong, son.
We've been through so much.
Don't give up yet.
My son is still in danger.
The new kidney has prolonged his life.
But we don't know when he'll wake up.
Take this.
It's the compensation
we agreed to in our contract.
PAY GAOGLA CHAYODOM FIVE MILLION BAHT
I can't take it.
I'm not selling my kids.
But your son wanted to leave you this.
It's not worth it.
No matter the amount.
In that case, let me repay you this way.
I'll make sure Gaogla receives
the lightest possible sentence,
or that he at least gets to recover
outside the prison
till he serves his full sentence.
No matter what happens next,
I promise to look after him
like he's one of my own heirs.
I will protect him
just like I protect my own son.
I promise.
Dad.
Gla.
My son.
Bone marrow transplant is ready.
THE KIDAKARNS OF LUXE HOTELS
What doesn't kill us
makes us stronger, Saikhim.
The world isn't that small.
KHEM
About time you picked up.
What have you been doing? I'm here now.
Gla?
It really is him.
Who's that? Gla, can you hear me?
Gla?
Gla.
Gaogla!
Did you lie to me on purpose?
Did you?
Gaogla.
Gla!
Gaogla!
Did you lie to me?
Gla!
Why didn't you say it's you?
You're still alive.
Why did you lie?
Why are you acting like a stranger?
What are you talking about?
Stop lying to me.
I know the whole truth. Why did you lie?
Since when were we close?
I don't remember us
truly knowing each other.
What do you mean?
We used to live together,
but that doesn't necessarily mean
we really knew each other.
Some people can't be trusted.
What did I ever do to you?
It was you
who made me believe you were dead.
Yeah!
The Gla you knew is dead.
I'm not that idiot anymore.
Well, who are you now?
And why are you here?
To kill you, maybe.
It's too bad you survived yesterday.
What did I ever do to you?
Didn't you tell me
that what doesn't kill us
will make us stronger?
-Let go.
-You should have made sure I died.
Now I'm back to make you pay.
Let go!
Miss Khim? What's going on?
But that's…
Get me out of here.
Let's go!
What's going on?
Didn't Gla attempt suicide in jail?
Why is he still alive?
The medical documents said
he was brain-dead.
He can't possibly have survived.
I need to know what happened.
Mr. Sansern, please find out for me now.
I'll take care of it,
but you should get ready to travel now.
The Hong Kong event is tonight.
But I really must know what happened.
It's been seven years.
Where has he been?
Madame is waiting inside.
In there, sir.
It's me.
I'm back.
I've been waiting for updates.
How are things over there?
Paris wants us to pay
ten million euros in damages.
Very crafty.
The case is ongoing.
Our lawyers are buying us time.
I'm not giving up so easily.
These people want to use the law
to hamstring our business.
We must be careful,
even when we're here.
I'm trying to find legal ways
for us to launch in the market here.
It won't be easy,
but if we sign an MOU with the government,
there should be no problems.
If we could enter the stock market,
things would get better.
I don't regret
letting you follow your dreams.
Your father must be very proud
that you took after him.
You were on a plane all night
and just landed.
Would you have time to hang out
with your brother for one night?
I can't stay the night.
But I can have dinner here.
Let me go and say hi to him.
Do you think I don't know
where you've been hiding?
I brought you something.
I thought you'd be late.
Thanks for flying here
to take care of things for me.
Here. Wait.
I called this morning.
Who did you sleep with?
Aren't you sick of Thai women?
I didn't wanna come back
'cause you guys are all up in my business.
I figured you'd be tired of Western food,
so I had them prepare Thai food.
I got this for you.
You found time to think of me?
Next time, I'll fly you over
so we can pick something out together.
Hey.
A lady's perfume? Whose is it?
My sweet boy,
don't tell me you've been misbehaving.
I'd love to misbehave.
But I'm too loyal,
so I've got no time for anyone else.
No time or no attention?
You even forgot
to set your watch to local time here.
I did think
this breakfast looked over-the-top.
But it's actually our lunch.
No need to call.
Mr. Sansern said Saikhim is on her way.
She must be on her flight right now.
Then that's okay.
I was scared she wouldn't make it tonight.
Tantai.
It's her own hotel's grand opening.
Why would she miss it?
Looking for a plus-one?
What do you think? Is he cute?
Men aren't props
that you can use to boost your image.
No one values that sort of thing.
And we're here for work, all right?
As if you have no ulterior motive.
What's up with you? Aren't you hungry?
I didn't know you were so romantic,
Tantai.
Go on, show me.
How will you propose to Saikhim?
Practice.
Try it first. Pretend I'm Saikhim.
Don't be shy. Come on.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'VE KNOWN YOU 20 YEARS
AND LOVED YOU THREE…
He wrote a script?
So corny.
Khim.
Tan.
Wait. What?
What happened?
I was a huge klutz
and hit my head on the plane window.
I was calling you all day yesterday,
but your phone was off.
Were you busy?
I… lost my phone.
But I got a new one.
It's almost time.
I think you should get to your room.
-Sure.
-Let's go.
Khim?
In the end, that really was Gaogla.
And he seemed so angry.
Why would he be mad at you?
Because he didn't die?
You're the one who should be shocked.
Exactly.
He's been alive all this time.
Why have I heard
nothing from him for seven years?
So what was he like?
Does he still look kind of rough?
He seemed… kind of different.
Both his character and the way he spoke.
He was in prison for ages.
Maybe he was hiding
because he couldn't face you.
He's in the past now.
Even if he had lived,
you're way out of his league.
He should know very well by now
that he's not worthy of you, Saikhim.
Anyway, now,
you're in a serious relationship.
Ta-da!
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
You're getting a surprise tonight.
We're ready. We're so ready.
There.
I don't think the business reporters care
who designed this place.
Since this is a work event,
you shouldn't steal the spotlight
from Khim tonight, you know?
Khim doesn't like to mix
work with her personal life, okay?
If you get down on one knee
and propose to her here…
it's not a good look for CEOs.
Then you should shut up about it.
Hey.
I warned you because I mean well.
You should be grateful.
I'd rather you stopped interfering.
By the way, there's one more thing, Tan.
You should say this.
Don't use your script.
YOU: TEN YEARS FROM NOW,
IF YOU THINK OF ME…
Khim!
Khim?
Do you have more info on Gaogla yet?
The latest info I have is
what I've already told you, Miss Khim.
He was severely ill with brain death
while serving time.
There's no info on him after that point.
So does that mean
that his death was never reported?
I think he must have expunged
his own records somewhat
because for the past two or three years,
we've no idea where he's been.
As for his family, we can't even find
any info on them either.
-But that's…
-What's wrong, miss?
He's here.
Who is, miss?
Gaogla.
He's at tonight's event.
Are you sure it's him?
I think something weird is going on.
This will be huge news tomorrow.
The media around the world will talk
about Claire debuting her partner tonight.
Tan, do you know them from somewhere?
Not at all.
I don't really follow
celebrity news anyway.
But I think maybe that man might be
some sort of famous actor or athlete.
Khim, you don't mind them
stealing your spotlight, do you?
Well…
Khim?
Yeah?
This is great. We can celebrate alone.
You never told me you'd be here too.
It's a surprise.
You're the cutest.
You like the flowers?
I love them.
Khim?
Are you tired?
I've… noticed that you've worked so hard
on this hotel, you know?
Are you happy with it?
I'd love to know
what could make your life
even more complete.
I don't know.
This world is always
full of problems to solve.
I want to be a part of your successes.
I'd like to ask you to invest
as my joint venture partner for life.
Khim… I'm sorry.
It's all right, Tan.
I'll clean it up.
Wait, Tan.
-Yes?
-What a mess.
What's this?
It's nothing.
What's that?
I meant to be discreet.
I want to be there
for all your successes just like tonight,
to play a small part
in a dark corner like this.
Marry me.
Khim.
Let's go and watch.
Think of this as our celebration.
I almost forgot
there's someone I want you to meet.
Miss Khim?
This is Carl.
Carl?
Carl Raman. He's half Thai, half Kazakh.
His name comes from his Thai name, Gaogla.
It's nice to meet you… Carl.
Miss Saikhim runs this project.
It's all thanks to her that this hotel
turned out so pretty.
It's nice to meet you.
Let me congratulate the bride-to-be.
Excuse me?
You're a very lucky man.
Very lucky indeed.
I had no idea.
Congratulations, Miss Khim.
This makes me so jealous.
Who knows when I'll be so lucky?
Why should you be jealous?
Someone once told me that good men
are harder to find than rings.
Good men…
If I can have a good husband…
I don't want a ring.
People who say that stuff must be
so naive.
They're either optimistic
or just trying to look good.
All talk, no action.
-Don't you think?
-What do you mean?
How is it possible?
How did things reach this point?
He changed his whole name.
That's why we couldn't find him.
How did he up his game
enough to date Claire?
I don't know.
He wants to blackmail me.
Khim.
Are you okay, Khim?
You're all red. Did you drink a lot?
I'm okay.
I'll talk to him properly.
Wait, Khim!
Why did you send that?
You can change your phone,
but you can't hide from the past.
Deleted files can be restored.
I can't believe
I remembered your passcode.
If you don't want anyone to snoop,
be more careful.
Are you anxious?
Are you scared people will hear our story?
We don't have a story.
We just did something dumb
when we were younger.
Don't let go. Hey!
Pull me up!
Now you beg for your life?
Don't you remember
what you did to me then?
-I won't jump.
-Too bad.
Hey!
So you're making me pay?
You nearly got me killed.
I helped you!
So I'll repay you now.
Don't let me go.
Khim!
It'd be a shame
if your expensive purse got wet.
It may be worth more than you.
Gla!
Khim!
Tan!
-Tan.
-Khim.
Khim!
There.
Your phone's down there.
Khim!
Just forget it, Tan.
-Is this a pool party now?
-You…
Let's just go.
Sorry. Excuse us.
Wait, sir. Your partner left this.
Thank you.
Hey. What happened?
Is she drunk?
I don't know.
Maybe she's drunk on love.
He made you fall in. What a jerk.
-He came back to make me pay.
-Who does he think he is?
That's Claire's room.
Let's look for clues
and find out who this Carl really is.
Let's go.
Hurry, Fern.
Go ahead. I'll keep watch.
Okay.
Khim?
Hi, Tan. Are you finished with the press?
-Where's Khim?
-Khim?
She's in her room.
I tried the doorbell,
but I guess she didn't hear it.
I thought she couldn't get in
without her key card.
Khim!
What's wrong?
Go inside.
Khim!
I dealt with the press for you.
The reporters have all left.
She's still taking a shower.
Why don't you go get changed first?
She said she lost her old phone.
So why was it in the pool?
He came back to make me pay.
Hey, Tan.
Dry your hair first, oppa,
then dry yourself all over.
What are you up to?
Well…
I'm going to return Khim's phone.
Khim said she lost her old phone,
so how do you explain this?
Well…
I guess she's exhausted.
She's been working so hard lately.
That's why she's being weird.
Don't worry about that.
Wait. Tantai, maybe you're jealous.
Do you think Khim keeps a second phone
to chat with someone else?
That's nonsense. She wouldn't do that.
Go on.
Looking for something?
Satisfy your curiosity.
You rich people are nosy, aren't you?
You don't even apologize.
I guess your family doesn't value manners.
Actually, I think you're the one
who should be apologizing.
You humiliated me on purpose.
What? I thought you wanted to reminisce.
Isn't that why you've been bothering me?
Who did that?
Who bothered whom?
You did it last night.
Tonight, you invaded my room.
You know when we last drank together?
I still remember what it was like.
I don't know what you've been through.
You got richer, but that doesn't mean
you became a better person.
Maybe instead,
you became a worse one.
I don't know why you're so hateful,
but don't take it out on me.
I didn't do anything.
You're experiencing
what's called karma.
Khim? Do you want some hot food?
I could get you room service.
Can you hear me?
Why is she so quiet?
Maybe she's…
Khim?
Khim, can you hear me?
Tan's here. Get out of there.
Why are you blushing?
Khim!
What are you doing? Get out!
Back off.
What's wrong?
Do you think I'll hurt you?
I know… that you came back to make me pay.
Khim's not in here.
If you're so paranoid,
you must have a guilty conscience.
You must know
what you did to me was wrong.
Well, you're a nutcase!
Of course I'm afraid of you!
Be afraid of your own heart.
I think women like you are more dangerous.
Khim! Tan is here.
Come out now!
-What are you doing?
-I told you.
You should have killed me.
This time,
it's my turn.
You do have bad intentions.
I can't breathe!
Do you really want to kill me?
Hey. Wait!
Khim!
Khim! What's wrong?
Khim, what's wrong?
Khim!
Khim? What's going on?
Tan, help me. I can't breathe.
What happened to you?
Why is she so red?
She needs a doctor!
-Khim?
-Let's take her to the hospital!
Khim has a severe pollen allergy
and has to stay overnight.
Pollen? But… where did it come from?
They said she's allergic to some flowers,
but we don't know which ones.
So… is she awake yet?
She's feeling better.
She's moving to her own room.
If you have a date, you can go.
We can manage on our own here.
Didn't you tell me
that what doesn't kill us
will make us stronger?
-Let go.
-You should have made sure I died.
Now I'm back to make you pay.
Those bees…
Those flowers…
What are you doing?
It can't be a coincidence.
TWO YEARS AGO
It really was him.
You're still wandering around in my life.
Did you come back to kill me?
I wonder if Romeo and Juliet's love
was so heartbreaking
because it ended when they both died.
If misunderstandings didn't lead them
to kill themselves,
their love
may not have lasted very long.
They said you were dead.
I'm too stubborn to die.
So why are you here?
To watch my enemy die.
I've never wanted to hurt anyone!
But today, I wish you would die!
-Hey!
-Then we'd never meet again!
Who was that woman?
You nag more than Khim does.
Well, she doesn't know
that you're cheating on her.
If you get lonely or bored,
call me.
What's Prom doing?
Getting someone to investigate Gaogla.
Don't get involved. It could be a trap.
He wants us to get suspicious
so he can entrap us for snooping.
I won't get caught like you, dummy.
-Gloy.
-Don't worry.
I'm still around.
I'm destined to live a long life.
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit