THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
Why do you look like someone I once knew?
The world isn't that small.
KHEM
It really is him.
The Gla you knew is dead.
I'm not that idiot anymore.
Marry me.
This is Carl.
His name comes from his Thai name, Gaogla.
He changed his whole name.
That's why we couldn't find him.
I told you.
You should have killed me.
This time,
it's my turn.
Time doesn't always help us
love each other more.
Instead, time will teach us
that the more we love
and the more we get hurt,
the more love will make us
more wicked than ever.
Did you come back to kill me?
Khim? Are you all right?
Why aren't you asleep yet?
Are you uncomfortable?
It's been a horrible day.
I feel like
I'm in a nightmare.
You should sleep.
Okay?
When you wake up tomorrow,
you'll feel better.
How is she?
Please go ahead.
Are you leaving already?
Thank you for taking the time to see me.
Claire, no matter where you are,
think of me, and I'll fly to you.
Who knows when we'll meet again?
I owe you a surprise. Be prepared.
Look after yourself.
I wish we never had to part again.
I have to go now.
See you later.
Khim?
Having trouble sleeping?
Let's talk outside.
If Khim wakes up and sees this review,
she'll be furious.
The hotel just opened,
and it's already had a break-in.
This news could hurt us.
Keep this quiet.
Don't let Khim know.
She needs to get better first.
-Khim…
-We've been libeled.
They said we let an intruder
enter a hotel room.
This is a deliberate attack
on our reputation.
I have to fix this right now.
But Khim…
He's not dead yet?
Not only is he still alive,
but he's also a celebrity now.
The media is talking about him
dating a famous model.
How did he get outta hell?
Does Khim know?
She saw him yesterday.
He's become a businessman
named Carl Raman.
Last night's news has brought up his past.
He's the adopted son of the owner
of a major hotel booking site that we use.
He's now involved in a start-up.
It's a part of his Minimalist group.
How can this be?
That means his business competes
for profit with our hotels, doesn't it?
He must be leeching off some woman, Uncle.
He came back just to mock us!
He's getting attention as part of
a new generation of entrepreneurs
and is famous for a sharing economy model
designed to create a sharing society.
He lets people trade accommodation,
possessions, and even labor,
disrupting business around the world.
Now he has access to more rooms
than big hotels in our group,
and many countries are banning his app,
so he's forging a path in the ASEAN region
after a big period of growth in China.
He's the representative
that the PM's economic advisory team
is going to sign an MOU with, sir.
If they sign this agreement,
he can officially open
an office in Thailand.
Uncle, don't let him find a way
to compete with us here.
But wasn't that short-term rent
condo project that you wanted to run
in talks with his company?
I didn't know he ran it.
As for Miss Khim's plan
for a six-star island resort,
it will have to wait.
How come?
That island is Gaogla's.
What the hell? This is insane!
How did he get so rich?
Just this morning,
he attacked our Hong Kong hotel
on his hotel booking website
by publishing this review.
This can't be a coincidence.
He clearly came back to attack us!
Who does that ex-con think he is?
He's too big for his britches!
He thinks he can get
the government to back him?
You should kill his dream now.
He must be so conceited.
He still doesn't know his place
after all this time!
-Thank you for having me. Yep.
-Thank you.
Your review did better than expected.
They've asked us
to delete that post from our site.
They're good at avoiding blame.
They're offering us
a free hotel room anywhere in the world
if we don't talk to the media about this.
What do you think?
If they won't delete the review,
say the incident was a misunderstanding.
Don't let other guests believe them.
If you have any updates,
call me right away.
Okay, bye.
Khim?
Look at this.
Why do people care so much?
So who is this man, and where is he from?
He's clout chaser
who leeches off famous women,
craves the spotlight,
and wants to be noticed.
So are you mad that he stole your thunder
at the hotel opening?
Not at all.
Why would I be jealous of him?
Let's stop thinking of work
and start thinking about our wedding.
If Mr. Seen finds out from someone else,
he'll feel like we disrespected him.
Right. Of course.
Miss Khim!
Is it true that Gaogla didn't die?
Auntie Oon!
Yes, Miss?
Sorry, who died?
Is Dad home?
I have good news for him.
My goodness!
Mr. Tan, you proposed
to Miss Khim already?
Yes, I did.
I'm so happy for you, miss.
Mr. Seen will be so happy for you.
What are you so happy about?
Khim and I got engaged.
So I'd like to see Mr. Seen.
How can you celebrate
despite everything that's going on?
Her ex isn't dead yet.
She's replacing him already.
We wanted you to know.
If you're not happy for us,
you can just stand there and be jealous.
Come on, Tan.
Let's go.
She hid her ex-lover down a hole,
and he's come back to haunt her,
yet she still dares
to act innocent and deceive Tan, Mom.
Hey, I've got a feeling
that this is a time bomb
waiting to blow up Khim's life.
Please excuse me.
There's trouble at the hotel.
You're so gutsy
to diss them on their own turf.
Well, they invited me to stay.
Maybe they thought
you wouldn't dare take their deal.
There's nothing to fear.
He's really staying at our hotel?
Yes, we made a deal
so he'd let go of the Hong Kong incident.
I don't trust him.
Does he have an ulterior motive?
I don't know.
I only know he's staying with us,
and he hasn't said for how long.
If you're worried,
I'll have our people watch him.
Don't do that.
He'd criticize us even more
and say we're violating his privacy.
Let's not look for trouble
by waging psychological warfare on him.
For now, let's just make sure
our staff takes the best care of him.
Yes, miss.
Hey, bro!
-May I arrange your bags?
-Hey, bro!
It's okay. I can take care of my own boss.
He doesn't like to be disturbed.
If I need anything, I'll ask you.
Okay?
Just take care of this. Here you go.
Here.
You can just get these washed. Thank you.
We need your ID card.
My ID card? What do you need it for?
It's our policy to keep tabs on
whoever visits our guests in their rooms.
I see.
Right. Okay.
That shouldn't be a problem.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
I'll bring it back.
All right.
What a snob!
I told you to change your shoes.
My feet are just feet.
Why should anyone feel bothered by them?
Come here.
Keep this on.
The Hoteliers' Association has registered
a complaint with my ministry.
If we let any random person
turn their accommodation into a homestay,
we'll end up with unfair competition.
Yes, I understand.
Hotels have protested before.
ONE HOUR BEFORE
Other countries have banned my company.
Billion-baht investors don't want
random people to compete with them, right?
If we let random people without permits
gain direct access to tourists,
we can't regulate anything,
and if anything damaging happens,
it will ruin the country's image.
Please excuse me.
Laundry delivery.
Come on in.
-Take this. See you tomorrow.
-Thank you.
But the hotel doesn't want me
to come up here.
If they have a problem, they can call me.
Yes, sir.
Our service isn't just for renters.
Our app serves surrounding communities.
Every resident can play their part
in welcoming tourists who visit them.
Thai people are known
for kindness and friendliness.
It's a huge selling point.
I left money here. Look at that.
SIR, YOU FORGOT YOUR CASH
How many other countries could be
as good at hosting as Thailand?
For tourism to grow,
it has to be sustainable like this.
PLEASE MAKE UP ROOM
My goodness! I'm so sorry.
Hey. Stop it, please, honey.
Stop it, please.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Please don't disturb the other guests.
Please wait outside.
-I'm sorry.
-Sure.
We have to think carefully again
before signing the MOU
because if we don't,
we'd let those multinational investors
take all the commissions for free
while taking no responsibility.
Excuse me. Mr. Carl is here.
That's good timing.
Welcome, Mr. Carl.
Dad is here, isn't he?
Yes, he's meeting the PM's advisor
in the dining room now.
Have you brought someone
to Mr. Carl's room?
Did anyone see the guest leave?
What's going on?
I asked Mr. Carl to join us
for a straightforward discussion.
I actually like fair competition too.
Amateurs
and professionals
can't compete with each other fairly.
They're not comparable.
Nowadays, the safer your investments are,
the riskier they end up being
because the world changes fast.
If professionals can't adapt in time,
they'll keep falling behind everyone else.
The service industry
sells satisfaction.
It will never fall behind
as long as it can impress customers.
-What's wrong?
-Yeah, I know, right?
Look at this.
-MAKE UP ROOM
-DO NOT DISTURB
We don't know
if they want the room cleaned or not.
If they want us to clean,
and we don't do it,
will we be in trouble?
If they want privacy,
and we barge in, we'll be in trouble too.
-Hello?
-Don't go in there. It's a trap.
He's messing with us.
Don't fall for it.
He's such an odd person.
We found the VIP in the dining room.
The dining room?
Sir, when you last visited,
you said you liked our soup.
The chef made some especially for you
so you can have as much as you like.
We always focus on
going above and beyond what's asked of us…
because we want every guest
to feel important.
If everyone were equally important,
there wouldn't be double standards.
Working with my database,
I can give them what they want
before they ask.
We'd never make our guests
feel uncomfortable
or like they're an inconvenience.
I think wherever they are in the world,
they should feel right at home,
then they'll want to visit
again and again.
If we can't even do that,
so-called professionalism would be worth
absolutely nothing at all.
They said you were dead.
I'm too stubborn to die.
So why are you here?
To watch my enemy die.
Our past taught me
that people die three times.
The first is during our last breath.
The second is when our body decomposes.
We die the third time
when those we leave behind forget us.
Now I'm back to take your lives too.
You'll die on the inside
and live forgettable lives.
The world will forget you ever existed.
I'll make you want to stop breathing
without asking you to.
What happened?
He came back to insult me!
Why did you let him
wander around our hotel?
If no one snuck into
the psycho's hotel room in Hong Kong,
he'd have no reason to threaten us.
You're the person in the photos?
I just wanted to find out
how he became this person called Carl.
You weren't trying
to rekindle an old flame?
I want nothing more to do with him.
Even if you were interested,
would he care about you?
I heard that now,
he's way out of your league, right?
Be mindful of what you say.
But it's true, Uncle.
Carl's girlfriend is a huge star
who's famous all over Asia.
She's beautiful, rich, adorable,
and she's a nice person.
Dear me, I don't think he'd like
someone like Saikhim anymore.
Look, don't let Tanthai find out.
If he hears about your past,
maybe there won't be a wedding.
Wedding? What wedding?
Wait. Khim, haven't you told your dad?
Uncle, Tan has finally agreed
to become your son-in-law.
Congratulations, Khim. You did it.
Dad?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about the engagement.
It was very sudden.
It caught me off guard.
I'm happy for you, Khim.
You're even more grown-up now.
Tanthai will be
a great supporter of your career.
Thanks to him, I felt able
to step back and enter politics instead.
But we're not getting married
just because of that.
We're getting married
because we love each other.
Loving each other is good,
but it's even better
when you make each other better.
We shouldn't stay with someone
who drags us down, okay?
We weren't born
to make the same mistakes over and over.
You almost let Tanthai get away once.
Luckily, you changed your ways in time.
Dad, you sound like you're saying
that I'm not worthy of Tan in some way.
Khim,
you ran off with a man once.
Good men just can't accept that,
so don't ever let him find out.
Not even after the wedding.
Understand?
Who would have believed
that such an ugly duckling
could turn into that hot swan?
He might be even richer
than Uncle's future son-in-law.
If he were to become your son-in-law,
what do you think Uncle Seen would say?
Goodness! What on earth are you thinking?
Mom, you know Uncle Seen has compared
me to Khim since we were kids.
To him, nothing I do is good enough.
Mr. Seen, did you know that Prim
has just become the fashion director
of the magazine, Unique?
To be someone's employee,
you must work hard.
If you were half as talented as Khim,
I'd have given you hotel business to do.
But we all know
you're not good at anything.
Do whatever you want,
but make sure
no one talks about you being my niece.
Mom,
if I want to outdo Khim,
I have to find a better husband.
And now,
the only candidate
better than Tan is Carl.
If Khim knew
that Carl liked me,
she'd probably die of heartbreak.
Oh dear.
Listen, Uncle Seen won't like that at all.
For now, you're right,
Uncle Seen won't like it.
But in the future,
who knows?
Mom, think about it.
Uncle Seen cares about profit the most.
So, one day,
I believe he'll want to gain
money or influence via Carl.
Miss Khim, you asked me to find some info.
Here's what I found. Here you go.
Thank you.
What's Prom doing?
Getting someone to investigate Gaogla.
Prom knows that he's trying to entrap us,
yet he's playing into his hands anyway,
and he's putting our employees at risk.
If he catches us in the act again,
he'll expose us, you know?
The VIP's guest just came down.
The VIP is at the pool now.
That woman is Gaogla's guest.
Since she checked in at our hotel,
she's barely used any of our services.
She just keeps bringing her guests in.
I'll catch up with you.
Miss Saikhim?
It's okay.
What's he doing now?
Gloy.
Is that you, Gloy?
You still remember me.
Are you well, Gloy?
Probably not as well as you.
Don't worry.
I'm still around.
I'm destined to live a long life.
I guess you came to see him.
Go ahead.
Congratulations, bride-to-be.
I hope that this time,
it'll last longer.
Don't!
Gla!
I don't get why you had to come here.
Wait… did you come to tempt your woman?
My woman?
Look at you, wearing next to nothing
and swimming where she could see.
She came to look at your six-pack.
Is that what you wanted?
Are you satisfied?
Why should I be? Let's go.
Gla, you planning on staying here
for good or something?
Are you hungry?
If I were,
would we pick these mushrooms for lunch?
You're always on the move.
Why don't you
find a home somewhere to settle down, huh?
You have money
but act like a vagrant.
Having everything doesn't mean
that you must be rich.
Owning stuff doesn't make me happy.
All this stuff isn't
a measure of happiness.
Even our bodies aren't our own.
We're just borrowing them.
I've been wondering
when I'll leave this broken body behind.
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have been shot that day.
We both got hurt.
I lost my leg. You lost your kidney.
We each lost something.
I promise you
that someone will lose more than we did.
By the way…
I have news
from the bank I was talking to.
Look.
The bank is interested in granting
home and condo loans
for investment purposes
so that borrowers can rent out their homes
on a short-term basis
as a way for young people
to earn extra money.
They want to partner with our booking site
and make it part of their services.
You think it's worth it?
I know
that your investment's value
isn't calculated in terms of money.
You already know what you want
in return for your investment,
don't you?
I'm glad we sent you to study abroad.
Make the deal for me.
I sure will.
This project's profits will blow
these people's minds.
CARL RAMAN, ASIA RAMAN
Gla's real father is a Westerner.
But he doesn't know who it is.
After Gla was born,
Rakroy found out
her husband had another kid.
The worst part is she later found out
he wanted to have a second kid
so that he could give blood
to the first one.
Asia Raman.
I don't want Gla to get rich or famous,
not because I don't want him to succeed,
but because I want to protect him
from those awful people.
He's like a different person.
-Thank you.
Hello, Miss Khim!
What a coincidence.
Carl is staying here. Have you seen him?
No, I haven't.
Are you in Bangkok for work?
No, I'm not.
I flew here to surprise him
to repay him
for flying to surprise me in Hong Kong.
I see.
Excuse me, I have to go prank someone.
See you later.
-How are we?
-Gosh!
Is our patient better?
Let's see.
I'm better now.
I wanted to bring you a bouquet,
but I was afraid it would make you worse.
Honestly, I'm okay.
Are you sure?
You still need to rest,
so I don't want
us to go out unnecessarily.
We should go home after dinner.
I've told Dad about our engagement.
Tan, let me know
when you want your family to come over.
Khim,
I want to marry you soon
so I can get you out of that house
as soon as I possibly can.
Since the Hong Kong incident,
I've had to stay on my guard.
I never know
when Prom will use it against me.
If I slip up,
they're ready to pounce and hurt me more.
I'm sorry,
but I think your dad is to blame for this.
You and your cousins compete
because of him,
so your house is a war zone.
But I promise you
that our family will never be like that.
Okay.
Let's order.
Khim,
it's that couple.
Miss Khim!
I think we need a change of scenery.
Hey.
Is he staying at your hotel?
Why is he around so much lately?
I don't know if it's a coincidence
or if it's deliberate.
Having fun?
I always have fun when I'm with you.
What are you watching?
Right.
-Talk about the app.
-Yes. Please check out the Arsa app.
It's a good app,
and it helps lots of people.
They seem down-to-earth.
Plus they're open
and not precious about privacy.
I think they make a good couple.
Don't forget to download it, everyone.
See all their fans?
Can you see what's behind us?
They don't have to hide
from the paparazzi who stalk them,
unlike other celebs.
Stalk them?
What's Prom doing?
Getting someone to investigate Gaogla.
I'll be back.
Khim!
-When did he leave?
-About half an hour ago.
Is this wise, sir?
Open the door!
Prom!
-What are you doing?
-Finding out what he's planning.
Don't get involved. It could be a trap.
He wants us to get suspicious
so he can entrap us for snooping.
I won't get caught like you, dummy.
Open the door!
Prom!
You don't know him like I do.
Why should we be afraid of him?
If he wants a fight, let's give him one!
Prom!
-Well?
-We caught him, bro!
We got her cousin this time.
Deal with the snoop.
I sure will.
What's wrong?
We have a very important guest.
Just my luck.
I have to clean up this mess.
Answer it.
Did he answer?
The phone's ringing. What now, sir?
Don't worry. Ignore it.
What a waste of time. We found nothing!
Your first mistake was forgivable.
But if you keep making mistakes…
you're a lost cause.
I should get that.
Hello.
Thank you.
Prom, get out of there now.
Someone's coming upstairs.
You're running a whole operation?
Hey, my boss asked me to tell you
that he's touched by how much you care,
but he asks you to stop harassing him.
This is too threatening.
He won't stand for it.
We're moving out right now.
What are you looking at?
Officers?
Please perform a search.
My boss's valuable item is missing.
Maybe he took it.
Don't get cocky.
If you don't find anything,
can you pay the price?
Please allow us to search you. Go ahead.
-May I?
-Go ahead.
There it is.
They did steal it.
You're trying to frame me?
So you're the larcenist.
Teach him a lesson
so that he doesn't do it again.
You are under arrest
for breaking and entering and for theft.
You're conspiring to pin charges on me!
Are you getting revenge?
Are you?
Last time, I went to jail
because of your dirty tricks.
Now we're even.
-Let's go.
Come on, sir.
Scumbag!
-Gla!
-Come on, sir.
Go back to hell!
I'll make you pay!
Remember that! Let me go!
Dad?
Why was Mr. Chartchai fired?
What did he do wrong?
You'd rather have Prom fired
to settle the case?
But Mr. Chartchai followed Prom's orders.
He was doing his job.
We're just making him the scapegoat.
Do you want to be the scapegoat?
Will you take all the blame?
You took in that tramp.
If you never got involved with him,
today wouldn't have happened.
We have to clean up after your messes,
and you still haven't learned anything?
If I'd been the one who'd died that day,
everything would be better now, right?
Are you still hungry?
That sushi looks good. Hey!
Bro.
I got him back for you.
Tomorrow, we'll find out how they'll pay.
Isolate them so they have no choice
but to attack each other.
Yeah.
Bro, I found a new place for you to stay
in case you need privacy.
Listen, the bed is very soft. Enjoy it.
Give me the keys. I'll drive.
Okay. Go and enjoy that bedroom.
So he finally signed the agreement.
He's clearly announcing himself
as our enemy publicly.
He's expanding his company in Thailand.
He's clearly defying you on purpose!
It won't be easy.
Now I know
why he came to stay at our hotel.
Why?
He's interested in
the traditional house opposite our hotel.
I saw that his telescope was aimed
at the other side of the road.
I looked through the telescope
and saw that it was focused on that house.
But at first, I didn't suspect anything.
And then I saw this.
He drew the plans for that house on this.
He even wrote the phone number.
I checked and found
that it's really the number of that house.
My theory must be correct.
He's interested in that old house!
He thinks he's defeated us.
But actually,
this round ended in a draw.
That's right, Mom.
Prom, you hit him below the belt so hard.
Actually, we might be jumping
to the wrong conclusion.
It's better than going along with him.
If he really wants this old house,
we'll buy it first.
That will teach him.
Uncle?
We should use it for my condo project.
Do you think that's a good idea?
Wait. I'd like to help too.
I'll find out
what he wants to use that property for.
I'm good at punching below the belt.
We managed to turn the tide our way
because I dared to take a huge risk.
Step aside if you can't handle it
'cause it's a big boy's fight.
Lots of people on the Internet are sharing
stories about Carl this morning
because last night, Claire livestreamed
while he prepaid for iced black coffees
to treat people
who couldn't afford to buy them.
Then people went to find
the free iced black coffees
and bought more for other people too.
These two are getting a lot of praise.
They call Gaogla a holy man.
Some call him a clean living guru.
Lots of people have downloaded
his Arsa app already.
That's the boat captain
who picks up passengers behind our hotel.
Last night, Gaogla hired him via the app,
so I questioned him.
I found out that Gaogla is using this app
to generate his own hype.
Gaogla is making us look like demons
while everyone sees him as a holy man.
Gaogla developed the Arsa app
to build a world based on sharing.
It encourages city residents
to be kind to each other
by sharing their possessions
or even their time.
He has made time more valuable
by having people sacrifice it to do tasks
that others ask them to do,
such as calling cabs,
going shopping, waiting in lines,
fixing cars, watching over patients,
and helping with homework
in exchange for labor costs or Arsa points
which can be collected
and used to request help from others.
NAME: KASALONG SANGCHAI
HELLO, KASALONG SANGCHAI
Attention, please.
This is the final call for flight…
Claire.
Hey! You came to see me off at the lounge?
Hey, you make me wish I weren't leaving.
We used every second of our time well.
Take this.
Keep it and think of me.
You've gone nuts.
Who grows mushrooms for their girlfriends?
Huh?
Eat them and think of me.
Don't miss me too much. We'll meet soon.
While I'm gone, be good. Don't misbehave.
All right.
Thank you.
You're the cutest.
Hey! I'm so glad to meet you at last.
I'm Primprao, Saikhim's cousin.
You nearly became my cousin.
Wait!
I heard that last night,
you got even with my big brother,
so today, I've come to
call a truce.
A truce?
I know they treated you so badly,
but I'm not like them,
so maybe we could be friends.
I can't fake it.
I'm too lazy to be two-faced.
I'm not faking it either.
Everything I say comes from the heart.
If you don't believe me,
do you want to test me?
If you get lonely or bored, call me.
I thought she would never leave.
Look at that pouty face.
Do I look stupid enough to fall for that?
Those people must be desperate enough
to try that basic move on you.
I got a prescription. Take these.
You're doing nightly remote work meetings.
Time difference is bad for the body.
Don't live recklessly.
Take good care of your body!
Are you even listening?
You're even prettier in real life.
Dad?
Khim and I are getting married.
You know very well
that she only sees you as a pile of money,
yet you still let her trap you.
Dad, why are you here?
Gaogla has been in the old house a while.
He hasn't come out yet.
Our people saw
his assistant waiting outside.
My theory must be correct.
He wants that house.
Why should we care?
If we keep making a fuss,
we'll always be one step behind him.
We don't have to care.
He lives his life. We live ours.
What if he opens
a competing hotel opposite ours?
What then?
Do we let him attack us first?
That's why I suggest
opening a condo first.
I'll do it!
You can't just do
that sort of thing so easily.
If you're scared, do nothing.
Let Prom do it.
We don't let spineless people
drag our business down.
Wait. Did you forget something?
-Well…
-Please go ahead.
Is her family pushing you
to get married soon?
Not at all.
Khim and I made the decision together.
Do you know Carl, the startup businessman
who's trending right now?
He has a sister.
I think she's better for you.
It's more like you want me
to leech off a woman.
Well, these things should be
win-win situations.
What?
Where are you going?
LITA
What a bunch of nonsense.
Hello. Urgent work?
-Hey.
-Okay. Excuse me.
Hey.
Did it go well, bro?
I totally forgot.
I prepared two sets like every year.
What should we do with the second one
since he's still alive?
We can't dedicate the blessings to him.
That would be rather strange.
Just give it to the monks.
Maybe if we share the blessings,
we'll get even and be rid of each other.
It's tasty, right?
-Yeah.
-I know some other good places to eat too.
I get it, bro. I do.
What do you get?
When there's something nice to eat,
and you have no one to eat it with,
it's really heart-wrenching.
That's all love is.
Lonely people know this.
You gotta get through
the loneliness somehow.
What's with the drama?
Well, isn't it true?
You want to talk to them,
but you don't get to.
I know you don't know who to talk to.
Your girl is never here to talk to.
But it's okay.
I think this one's tastier.
Mom, your taste is awful.
Don't set me up again.
Your taste is getting too expensive!
You only want someone rich.
If it hasn't happened yet, it won't.
So you want me to just accept
any man you send my way?
I can't do that!
I've studied too hard to settle.
I can't just come home
and sell homemade cream like you, Mom.
Well, what's wrong
with selling homemade cream?
You sound like
you haven't learned your lesson!
Come on, Mom.
How many faces have you ruined?
I've smoothed things over
with so many of your clients.
How much have you wasted on this product?
Come on, Mom.
Please don't risk going to jail for this.
If someone reports you again,
I'm not bailing you out anymore.
One more thing.
If you want a good son-in-law,
please don't give me
anything else to be embarrassed about!
Gosh!
May these creatures be free.
May they be free from suffering and death.
I dedicate the blessings I receive
to the souls of the departed
and to all enemies from past lives.
May they forgive me
and let go of their grudges.
Your whole life is sinful.
Do you think
freeing some animals can absolve you?
Did you follow me?
Knowing your record,
I'm the one who should ask you that.
What a holy occasion.
I was about to share blessings with you.
Are you asking for some?
You can't even stick to the Five Precepts.
You have no blessings to share.
Extraordinarily sinful women like you
don't have any goodness left, do they?
Hey!
What are you doing?
-Hey!
-You know what?
I've never wanted to hurt anyone!
But today, I wish you would die!
Then we'd never meet again!
-Go away!
-Hey!
-Just go away!
-Let go!
-Miss Khim!
-Careful!
-Let go!
-What is it?
-That's him!
-Don't!
Hey!
Let's go, Auntie Oon.
I don't want to do any other bad deeds.
Saikhim!
-Saikhim!
-Gosh!
Miss Khim.
Gosh, I can't believe
he's actually still alive.
As far as I'm concerned, he's not Gaogla.
His looks aside,
he's completely different.
Gosh, but it seems like
he's holding a huge grudge against us.
This is nothing
compared to what he did to me.
Miss Khim,
people who aren't a good match
are doomed to break up one day.
If it were true love,
you never would have been separated.
I never used to regret
meeting him in this life.
That was before today.
I can't call it lost love.
Just knowing each other was hard enough.
Here you go.
We're trying to create a new way
to experience tourism.
Hey! Bro!
-What happened?
-I fell in the water.
I'm lucky Pod helped me.
Hey, how did you fall in?
He was trying to catch some fish.
What?
Whoa! You're about to get married.
You're still interviewing candidates?
What would Khim think if she knew
you were two-timing her, Tanthai?
-Back off.
-Answer me first.
She's partnering with the bank.
Right, I guess that means your dad
wants a daughter-in-law, doesn't he?
Sort out your own life, Lita.
I've seen you with countless men.
Hey, Tanthai, don't change the subject.
Who was that woman?
Excuse me.
-Yes?
-Do you have CCTV?
I lost something.
Yes, miss. What did you lose?
My friend's boyfriend.
I lost my friend's boyfriend.
I guess he was stolen just now.
-Right.
-I just need evidence to expose him with.
-Lita…
-Don't touch my phone!
Don't call Saikhim about this.
Don't be ridiculous.
You look so guilty.
You must be scared
she'll find out you're cheating.
Khim is rational.
She doesn't get jealous randomly like you.
Yes, she's too rational
to suspect that you're cheating on her!
We're about to get married.
If you're jealous of her for that,
try not to show it.
If she finds out that you betrayed her,
you'll never marry her in this life,
the next, or any other life.
-Give my phone back to me.
-No.
-Give me my phone back.
No? Fine.
-Give me yours.
-Hey!
-Lita, what are you doing?
-Give it to me now.
-Give it to me.
-No.
-What are you doing?
-Just give me my phone back!
This isn't over yet, Tanthai.
Lita.
I'll get it for you.
Be careful.
-Hey!
-Tan!
Thank you.
Put it away in the car and turn on the AC.
Yes, ma'am.
We need someone to give us Wi-Fi.
Let us know if you can share your Wi-Fi.
Will someone really share Wi-Fi with us?
People should share what they can.
Who would share this sort of thing?
Pod, you have this great food.
Do you ever share it with anyone?
-No.
-All right.
We'll trade your goat's milk
for someone's Internet connection.
We ask for what they have,
and we give what we can.
-Yeah.
-That's not too difficult.
Listen.
If someone around here is interested,
they'll hit Accept, and we'll just trade
the goat's milk for their Wi-Fi password.
No one replied. You're full of crap!
Hey! Chill out, little dude!
You're like a moody teenager.
-What's your real age?
-Seven.
You're seven?
The same age as my child.
If it had survived,
it would be annoying like you.
Dad!
What is it? Miss Khim, what is it?
Start the car.
What?
Hey! Why did you follow us?
Prepare to pay for what you did.
Hey! What are you doing?
Hey! Don't!
You nutjob!
You're totally nuts!
You must feel so guilty
about all your bad deeds
that you're scared of empty tanks.
Are you okay?
Start the car.
Gosh.
I thought we'd have no milk left
to trade for Wi-Fi.
So you had to fire someone
to get them to settle the case?
He's rotten to the core.
He pretends to be a holy man.
I wasn't convinced
that he could run a huge business
without caring about money.
Tan, what have you heard?
Well, nothing, actually.
I've heard nothing.
Taste the soup for me.
Come on, taste it.
Here. Careful, it's hot.
-Is it good?
-It's good.
So Tan, what did your family say
about our wedding?
We should have
a small wedding, don't you think?
More people, more problems.
I think the wedding should be
about just the two of us.
I think so too.
Marriage can't guarantee
that people will truly love each other.
Some people show their true colors
after they get married.
I didn't mean you, Tan.
I'm just observing
what people are like these days.
We don't need to get married
to prove our love.
You understand me, and that's all I need.
Did I scare you?
I heard that you check into
random lodgings on your app.
My friend owns this place.
When I heard you were staying here,
I got you some room service.
How can I be sure
your people won't search my room again?
I could've surprised you in there,
but I chose to wait outside
right here.
My friend's a flight attendant.
He travels abroad a lot.
So he rents this place out.
He doesn't even stay here much anyway.
Maybe "friend" isn't the right word.
I'm actually his personal trainer.
About that room service,
there's more to it.
When you exercise your muscles wrong,
they get tense just like this.
You should try a relaxing massage.
When we get married, would this be
a good marital home for you, Khim?
Why wouldn't it be, Tan?
I'm just wondering
if you'd rather live in a big house.
Not at all.
I can live anywhere
as long as it's just the two of us.
Really, Khim?
Should I have you try staying the night?
-Well…
-Stay here tonight.
We'll be married soon.
Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna make coffee.
Would you like some?
Khim.
I'm not finished yet.
Why did you change the subject?
That might be Lita.
I should pick up.
She's been calling all afternoon.
Khim, I think it's probably nothing.
I should get it, or she'll be mad at me.
I won't be long.
Hi, Lita.
Are you okay?
You've been calling all afternoon.
Khim, have you spoken to Tan today?
Did he say he saw me?
He's with me now. He didn't mention it.
Really?
And… did he act unusually nice?
Like, did he go out of his way to be nice?
Well…
He cooked for me.
I knew it.
He's covering up
what he did this afternoon.
What's going on, Lita?
You're being dramatic.
Khim, you're about to get married.
Try acting like a jealous wife.
Is he being so nice to you
because he did something to hurt you?
Figure out what he's feeling guilty about.
If you can't figure it out,
don't marry him.
Okay, bye.
What's wrong, Khim?
Such tense muscles.
When did you stop going to the gym?
Let me relax these tense muscles.
Where did you see Lita today?
This afternoon?
I was having lunch with my dad
and a client and ran into Lita.
Which client?
I can tell you, but you don't know them.
By the way, about tonight,
are you staying here?
Is someone staying in the place next door?
Didn't you tell me
it's usually empty?
Stop changing the subject.
If you're not ready to stay the night,
you should just say so.
Well…
I…
Hey!
I started boiling water
but forgot to turn on the extractor fan!
It's okay, Khim.
Come here.
Please send someone up here.
It's okay.
-Yes?
-I'm sorry.
What the hell?
I nearly had him.
The smoke alarm went off,
but I've shut it down.
Hey. I didn't know you were staying here.
And I didn't know you were here.
So that alarm just now was…
That was mine.
I was boiling water but forgot about it.
I guess everything's fine now.
What's going on?
Prim!
Why are you here?
The same reason as you, I guess.
Did you two trigger the alarm?
Did it get that hot?
Gosh. Don't do anything extreme next time.
You frightened the whole building.
It's safe. The alarms have all stopped.
Thank you.
Sorry to bother you.
I need to rest. You should leave.
Hey!
You're just kicking me out?
Since when did they know each other?
KIDAKARN (5)
GROUP CHAT
PRIMPRAO
I'm not coming home tonight.
She's nasty.
She moves so fast.
TIME FOR ROUND TWO
Tonight, I'll try clean eating.
It might be good for my health.
You're still here?
I want a bath too.
Women like Saikhim don't deserve
good relationships.
You watch your boyfriend at all hours.
Are you scared he'll get away?
No, I'm scared he'll want something
more casual like you do.
Don't tell me you came to see Gaogla.
What if I did?
Are you jealous?
We can use this video to expose them
for using the app
as a front for sex workers.
Deal with this father and daughter pair.
If you can't handle it,
I'll deal with them myself.
Show your true colors.
Stop faking and playing dumb.
I'm starting to wonder
if you care about Saikhim's feelings.
Not at all.
I don't care about those people.
Go and watch them.
I must know what they are to each other.
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit