THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
It's not an award, Khim.
It's a punishment for us both.
If you want to get revenge on me,
leave other people out of it.
This is Rarin.
Rarin?
But everyone said that my mom died.
Your dad wouldn't let us see each other.
Dad, explain to me
what the hell is going on!
She was the one who left me and you first!
You want to hurt me?
If you do, you've succeeded.
I'm in pain. Are you happy now?
-So let's get divorced.
-Give me your shares if you wanna remarry.
You wanted to flirt with your man?
Sorry.
I'm the wrong one.
I don't know what happened
between you and him.
But I think
it's for the best
that you're trying to stay away from him.
WHEN THERE ARE DIFFERENCES…
If you hate each other,
you still care about each other.
If there's no love left,
even if you see each other,
you'll feel nothing.
I want him to get what he wants
to prove we no longer have
feelings for each other.
Hello?
Your dad asked to see me today.
He's very worried about the graft probe.
Really?
So… any updates on the divorce?
Did he use your dad's case as leverage?
It's gone nowhere yet.
It probably won't be easy.
What? So what will you do now?
If he tries playing dirty…
I will too.
Hello?
WOMAN OF THE YEAR, MS. LITA THONGMA
How did this get here?
Mom!
-Mom!
-What?
What is it?
Where did you get this award?
That? Saikhim's partner sent it to us.
You broke it, you clumsy girl?
You're lucky he fixed it.
-But Mr. Seen said…
-I said no!
As for Mr. Songseen,
tell him to go to hell!
Tanthai knows I want it,
so he sent it to us.
And this photo album,
he sent me it as a gift
to show off to everyone with.
He said he wanted me to be proud of you.
I understand now
why Saikhim chose to marry this man.
It's because he's so sweet and so nice.
He saw that I was upset
about not being invited to the event,
so he sent me photos
and videos that he took himself
to make me feel better.
Where are you going?
Accept your award first.
Hi, Ms. Lita. Come on.
Congratulations.
Let's get a photo together.
Another round of applause, please!
It's kind of a pity.
I wish I had such a perfect son-in-law.
Jeez, what good deeds did Saikhim do
to deserve such a catch?
He's so great!
Mom, why is your daughter so unlucky?
Auntie Oon?
What? You're back, Miss Khim?
Are you hungry?
Have you eaten?
Yes, I have.
Hey.
-But how come…
-Auntie Oon.
You should go to bed.
Don't worry about me.
All right.
What? Miss Khim?
You need anything? You should've called.
I just wanted to see
if you were asleep yet.
I wanted to hear you snoring
before I fall asleep.
Aw, Miss Khim.
Today,
I went to see my mom.
She was with her new daughter.
I felt jealous of them
because they seem so close.
But
I really wanted to brag
that while she has a new daughter,
I have you too, Auntie Oon.
I shouldn't even feel upset
that someone stole my mom
because
I stole you
from your daughter too, Auntie Oon.
Thank you for staying here with me.
Though I don't have everyone,
you never make me feel
like someone's missing.
I'm so lucky to have you, Auntie Oon.
-Next…
-Say hello to Madame.
-Hello, Madame.
-Well, hello, dear.
-Come on.
-Come on in, dear.
Listen, my dear.
This girl here,
that boy, Carl, found her for me
to help me type up my recipe book.
These kids are volunteers.
They come and work for me
in exchange for my food.
They don't often get to eat
good, nutritious food.
Now, look over there.
That group there, cutting the grass,
they're helping me out
in exchange for a meal.
Actually, this Arsa app that Carl made,
it really is good, dear.
Gosh, it's made my life much easier.
You know how they say
that technology makes people unkind?
I don't think that's true at all.
I'll argue with anyone who thinks that.
This thing has made society
so much better, my dear.
You know, I think Carl is very talented.
He can do anything he dreams of.
I'm a big fan of his work.
But everyone who comes here
wants something in return, don't they?
Yes, dear.
But when Carl comes
to sit there and work every day,
I like that.
It's like he's come to keep me company.
And it stops me from feeling lonely.
Well, isn't that nice?
And what if one day,
he doesn't want to just work here,
but… he wants to come here to make money?
How would he make money?
I don't understand.
I have to go back for a meeting.
-I see.
-I'll come again another day.
Of course.
I think you should take all this with you
and eat some, all right?
I'll have Chor wrap this up for you.
It won't take long.
-Chor!
-Yes, ma'am.
Come over here.
Take all this
and wrap it up nicely for her.
Hurry up.
Yes, ma'am.
Good. Yes, wrap it up nicely.
I want you to see the truth.
I'm sorry it has to be like this.
-Chor?
-It's ready, ma'am.
My goodness!
-So impatient.
-So slow.
-Here.
-Give me that.
Here, dear.
Take it and taste your own cooking.
Go on, dear. All right.
Bye, dear. Go ahead.
Wait. Hold on a minute.
Did someone forget
to take something with them?
What thing?
What is it?
Well, this must belong to Carl.
He'll probably come back for it.
May I see?
But that's the plan of this house.
What? Let me see.
Be careful.
Carl, is this yours, dear?
-Where did you find it?
-Don't you dare ask!
You come here every day,
hoping to turn it into a hotel, don't you?
That's not it.
Of course it is!
We thought you came here
with good intentions,
but you just want to make a profit!
No wonder you helped us
deal with the expropriation!
Chor!
Carl, if you want to take this property
and turn it into a hotel,
I'll give it to you.
Madame!
What? I told you to be calm.
But please wait until I'm dead first.
Once I've died…
Give me that!
I'll change my will to bequeath
this land and this house to you, Carl,
because I don't have
any kids or grandkids anyway.
But I need one thing from you, Carl.
I'd like you to take
a portion of the hotel's profits
and give it to Chor here, dear.
Who'd accept your money, Madame?
Come on now.
But I don't want
to take your house, Auntie.
Carl,
I want to give it to you because I know
that you know that this land
has some value,
and you'll use it to do something good.
If it were someone else,
I wouldn't trust them at all.
Consider it my dying wish, my dear.
I don't need to keep it.
But I do worry about one thing.
I'm worried about Chor here.
All right, dear?
Don't cry.
Did it get here because of the other day?
Make him read them.
I want his answer today!
That day, I couldn't find the designs.
I thought I'd lost them,
but they ended up here.
Because you didn't divorce her.
I think you should sign
her divorce agreement soon
before Madame Asia takes
your company and shares back.
So she's playing hardball.
Hey.
She wants to expose us,
so I'll leak the marriage certificate.
Take care of it.
-What?
-Hey!
-Sorry, we're busy today.
Hey! Where are you going?
You won't even say hi?
Maybe next time. This is really urgent.
-Hey, wait!
-Let go!
Hey, you're being so rude!
You messed with me first, Saikhim.
Hey!
What's so urgent?
A divorce agreement?
Uncle, did you know
those two signed a marriage certificate?
I thought he was dead!
So I stopped caring.
Who drew up this agreement?
Miss Khim must have found a lawyer.
She didn't come to ask me.
If those two are still legally married,
Khim can't get remarried yet!
So that's why
they have to get divorced quietly.
A quiet divorce
without any demands?
No way.
He pinned a corruption charge on me.
I'll get the best revenge on him.
What if he makes demands too?
In comparison,
it'll hurt him more than us.
Even that house and land
can be ours again if we want them.
Miss Khim is back.
And Mr. Tanthai wants to see you, sir.
I'm asking for permission to marry Khim.
We picked an auspicious date,
which is six months away,
so I'd like to ask you
about the bride-price.
That's a huge concern
because I raised my daughter very well.
For my daughter,
200 million isn't asking too much.
Two hundred million?
You're kidding, right?
The bride-price should be worthy
of both our families' reputations, right?
Dad?
Two hundred million isn't too much
compared to the opportunities you'd lose.
I believe
there are others
who would dare to pay more.
He's acting like
he doesn't want to give you to me.
That's not true.
Did I offend him in some way?
Or is he unhappy
that I didn't bring my family
to speak to him?
I'm an adult now.
I don't have to wait
for Dad to give me away.
Though Dad isn't thrilled,
I'll still marry you.
Then I'll find a solution with him
so you two don't fall out over me.
Wait till he's in a better mood,
then we can try again.
I should go.
What are you trying to do?
Don't you want me to get married?
How can you get married
when you haven't divorced Gaogla?
How did you know?
Don't tell me he told you.
How could you hide
something this big from me?
I caused this problem.
So I'll solve it myself.
I'm going to negotiate with him
about the divorce.
Negotiate?
It's not negotiation
if you're divorcing him for free.
He almost ruined your whole life!
You should at least
get marital property as compensation.
The 200 million you want
for lost opportunities
is just extortion, isn't it?
As if he'd give me anything.
You're so manipulative.
And we put him through so much.
If he gives you nothing,
don't get divorced.
Stay married and bleed him.
Didn't you hate that he leeched off us?
Now you want me to take his money?
I can't help it.
He refused to know his place.
Serves him right!
I'm marrying Tan.
I won't let this
get in the way of our marriage.
You dated Tanthai
without divorcing Gaogla.
It's like you cheated on him all along!
You betrayed him so horribly.
Even when all this is settled,
who knows if he'll accept your past!
Gaogla already knows you inside out.
You have nothing to lose.
I want this divorce.
I can't live
with that man in my life anymore!
Bro.
The new divorce agreement.
She wants marital property.
She wants to bankrupt you now.
So she wants to be this dog's tick.
She wants to bleed you dry?
We'll teach her a lesson.
Get her to talk to me face to face.
This has to end today.
You talk like a snob,
but you actually want to bankrupt him?
I played no part in this.
Gla sent you a message.
If you want a divorce,
you have to talk face to face,
or file for divorce.
I'm on my way.
Are you leaving work? Shall we go now?
Right.
Look, I have to go to an event
with the Hotels Association right now.
I guess I can't come with you.
But didn't we decide
to announce our wedding together?
If you don't come, what will I do?
When I'm done,
I'll catch up with you right away.
It's really important.
Khim!
-Yes?
-Then I'll wait at the restaurant.
All right.
Carl, how did you find this place?
It used to be a garage.
I'm renovating it as a temporary lodging.
I might start renting it out soon.
It's pretty cute.
I'm sure your taste is very original.
Do you think you could live here?
If you can, of course I can too.
But I've got some bad news for you.
Mom has some urgent work,
so she can't take the recipe book photos.
And she's flying home tomorrow.
Are you mad at her?
She doesn't seem to like me much.
She's usually more approachable than this.
I don't know what she's upset about.
I have an idea.
Let's have a farewell dinner with her.
You have to get back in her good books,
or you won't be able to face her again.
Tonight?
What? You're flaking tonight?
Yeah, okay.
It's better to sort out the divorce first.
Hey, Tan is already here.
Don't worry, Khim.
I'll handle this for you.
Is this another dirty trick?
Lita!
Did she say where she went?
No. I thought I'd see her here too.
I thought the bathroom was here.
I'm going to the bathroom!
Call Khim for me.
Let's see if she picks up.
No answer.
Why has Khim been weird lately?
Something fishy is going on.
How is it my problem?
Your partner's missing. Blame yourself.
Mr. Ton, you forgot something.
Get in there.
-Get in there right now.
-Why?
Hey! I'm going to…
Hush, Lita!
Ton is out there.
I don't want him to know
we're talking in here.
Be quiet.
I can't breathe.
Are you drunk?
I'm here to finalize the divorce.
You said you wanted nothing,
but now, you want hundreds of millions?
My dad sent those divorce papers.
I had nothing to do with them.
I came to confirm
I want nothing from the divorce.
You're giving up hundreds of millions
just to marry this guy.
So you really love him?
More than I loved you.
So prove it.
Prove you love him more than yourself,
and I'll divorce you tomorrow.
How should I prove it?
Stay here like before.
Sleep together once and part ways.
You love him enough to be that wicked?
If you love him enough,
you'll sacrifice your dignity.
This isn't about dignity.
You love him too much to betray him?
Only evil people would make
disgusting offers like this.
So killing your own child wasn't evil?
What do you mean?
When you left me,
you did whatever you dared to.
Your betrayal knew no bounds.
You did all sorts of evil things.
You respect other men more.
What do you think I am?
How could you treat me like that?
How do you want me to make it up to you?
Just tell me.
I'll do anything but this revolting thing!
You threw me in prison
and got rid of the baby.
How can you pay me back
if not with your life?
Who told you I got rid of the baby?
My miscarriage was…
it was a tragic accident.
You wrote to me in prison
to ask for a divorce
and told me, didn't you,
that you couldn't be
with a poor man like me?
I miscarried a few days ago.
I couldn't let it be born
to a dad like you.
I don't want to sink any lower.
Now I know we're too different.
You're a narcissist.
You're selfish.
You couldn't divorce me, so you killed me.
What do you mean?
Come here.
You didn't dare face me,
so you tried to kill me to get rid of me.
Here's the proof.
I kept it to remind myself
how much you hated me.
I became a problem,
so you signed my treatment refusal form
so they'd let me die
because you were afraid I'd go on
to expose your failures?
What are these?
I've never seen them before.
You mean your dad did this too?
Just admit it.
You wanted to kill me
because you couldn't face living with me.
You let me wait for death
so you could go back to being
good old Miss Saikhim.
But I survived.
Khim.
I heard that during my coma,
my wife betrayed me.
And now you're desperate for a divorce
'cause you're afraid
your man won't accept your sordid past
after you pretended to be an angel.
And when you lied
about working in the forests
while you were doing illegal work,
you betrayed me too.
I was entrapped!
Your dad got Khem arrested
and tricked me into saving him
to pin charges on me and throw me in jail!
Dad said you sent him photos
to blackmail me.
You didn't want to look after me.
You wanted to blackmail Dad.
Every word your dad says is a lie!
If you believe him,
you must think I'm evil beyond redemption.
-So you cut me and the baby off!
-I don't know what's true anymore!
If you're not fooling yourself,
you know the truth.
For seven whole years,
you've been so relieved I was dead.
That's not true!
I missed you every single day.
Never have I seen you feeling happy
that I survived.
If I'm repulsive,
you're even worse,
so you never feel a thing.
Just one night
in exchange for a lifetime with him.
Isn't it worth it?
I can't do that to him.
Trust me.
You're more shameless than that.
If you hate me,
why do you harass me?
These things…
don't have to involve love.
Did you forget
how our story began?
You want me to feel guilty
around Tan for the rest of my life?
You want to blackmail me?
If tonight never happened,
I could still blackmail you.
You think you're so noble?
I may be wicked,
but I'm not as evil as that.
Don't you want a divorce?
Why are you playing hard to get?
Why are you scared?
We're all grown-up now.
If you feel guilty,
it should be because of me, not him.
If we're not divorced,
we're not hurting anyone else.
You lost your chance.
That's not my problem.
You don't want a divorce.
You just want to mock me.
Maybe he's got business to attend to.
Carl isn't usually like this, Mom.
To really get to know someone,
it takes more time than this.
Aren't long-distance relationships
normally like this?
I think you shouldn't commit to anything
until you know this man well enough.
-I gotta go.
-Okay.
What was that?
What did they say?
Jeez!
Dude, Lita is so heavy.
-Both her drinking and her body are heavy.
-We were overdue for a meetup.
-Careful. Gently, dude.
-Mind her head.
Sir, I sent you her address.
Jeez.
-Let us know when you get home.
-All right.
-Let's go.
-Jeez.
We'll all be home soon.
Is she safe?
Miss? You're home now, miss.
Miss?
-What?
-You're home now.
Sir? It's okay. I'll do it.
Lita, wake up. You're home now.
Come on.
Hey, Lita.
-Thanks, sir.
-Is she your partner, sir?
Well… yes.
-Please give her this.
-Sure.
Lita, wake up now.
Oops.
Lita.
Open your eyes.
You're being so reckless.
Come on. Go inside.
What? Why are you here?
I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't mean for that to happen.
Please don't be mad at me, Tan. Please?
-Okay?
-Okay.
You're home now.
Are you sure?
Hey…
Whoa, you're the sweetest, Tan.
Why wouldn't I love you?
Hey. What did you say?
Hey!
You're so nice.
How could Khim do that to you?
I don't want you to be someone else's.
Hey!
Lita! What are you doing?
Come on.
Enough. Lita, get inside.
You wrote to me in prison
to ask for a divorce
and told me, didn't you,
that you couldn't be
with a poor man like me?
You're a narcissist. You're selfish.
You couldn't divorce me, so you killed me.
-You did this, didn't you?
-Gla!
-Miss Khim.
You framed me! Khim, don't listen to him!
I did nothing wrong.
You can't pin this on me!
They want us apart!
I promised Khim.
Why would I break my promise to her?
-Don't mess with us!
-Stay out of this!
Stop it!
Are you nuts?
I became a problem,
so you signed my treatment refusal form
so they'd let me die
because you were afraid I'd go on
to expose your failures?
Just admit it.
You wanted to kill me
because you couldn't face living with me.
What the hell's going on?
What have I done?
If you feel guilty,
it should be because of me, not him.
If we're not divorced,
we're not hurting anyone else.
How much must you hate me
to do this to me?
I just want you
to be unable to love again.
You selfish people don't deserve love.
Ask yourself this.
As a mom, what did you do to your kid?
What do you mean?
You can't love anyone but yourself.
So now you have no one left.
Not even your dad.
You think he cares a lot about you.
But he's not honest with you.
He took your mom away from you,
saying only that she wasn't worthy.
I guess you know now
that it's you who isn't worthy of us.
I didn't mean it.
I didn't mean it!
I didn't mean to betray you.
Miss Khim!
Hello, Miss Khim?
Miss Khim? Hello, Miss Khim?
Miss Khim?
Miss Khim, is something wrong? Miss Khim?
Seven years ago,
you put Gla in prison, didn't you?
What's wrong this time?
When he hanged himself in prison,
You forged my signature
to tell them not to revive him.
You used me to kill him.
How could you do that?
I know everything now!
I know why he accuses me of killing him.
You took him from me on purpose, right?
If I hadn't done it,
you'd still be farming on a hill now!
Is that what you want?
Even if my life were ruined,
at least it would be my own life!
You want a ruined life, do you?
These past seven years,
you've had a good, luxurious life.
Everyone has envied you, haven't they?
Did I do the wrong thing?
Tell me.
After all this time,
what about your life made you so unhappy?
These past two days,
you announced your engagement, didn't you?
Don't blame me.
Even if you could trade your current life
with the one you had then,
when you had a crappy husband,
I guarantee that you'd never trade them!
No one knows what I need better than I do!
If you regret losing him,
don't marry Tanthai!
If you still love him so much,
just don't divorce him!
Is there still anyone left for me to love
after all you did to them?
Are you blubbering so much
because your heart's broken?
You took everything away from me!
From Mom to Gla!
Whenever I love someone,
you always take them from my life
so I'm deprived of love
unlike other people!
And are those people worth loving?
Don't preach to me, Dad!
Do you know how to love others?
If your love were real,
you wouldn't lie to me or control my life.
You wouldn't take
your disappointments out on me.
You wouldn't let me become a murderer!
Are you done yet?
You want to try it, do you?
If you didn't have your dad in your life,
how would you live?
Let's try it.
If you didn't even have me,
you're the one
who'd have no one left.
Even if you went back to him,
he'd never feel the same about you again.
Khim!
Is she your partner, sir?
Well… yes.
-Please give her this.
-Sure.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
Please don't be mad at me, Tan.
Okay.
Whoa, you're the sweetest, Tan.
Why wouldn't I love you?
Where did I put it?
How did I get home last night?
What?
This way, please.
What's this?
I'm the one
who should ask you what that is.
How could you do this to Saikhim?
You had someone follow me?
Wasn't it you
who provided evidence
for Gaogla to report me?
You wanna mess with me?
I never wanted to be
a part of your revenge plots!
Why did you involve me?
I'll give you
one last chance to redeem yourself.
Ruin Saikhim's wedding.
I'm going to swindle Gaogla.
I'll have Saikhim
take marital property from him.
They won't be able to marry.
An ideal result
for backstabbing best friends like you.
Last night, I was just drunk.
We didn't do anything more.
And I've never wanted
to steal my friend's partner.
Really?
I don't think so.
Based on these photos,
you threw yourself at Tanthai.
What if I refuse to obey you?
Saikhim will see these photos.
And I don't know
if she could bear
staying friends with you.
Then I'll admit to her
what happened last night.
And then what?
I'd love to know.
How will you look Tanthai in the eye?
Would you dare?
You've come this far.
Now go all the way.
Make Tanthai leave Saikhim.
Then you get Tanthai.
It's a win-win situation!
Tan doesn't love me!
He loves Saikhim!
Love? So what?
No matter how good Tanthai is,
he's not the best choice for Saikhim!
Khim must have better than the best!
I'm giving you two weeks.
Ruin Saikhim's wedding,
or she'll see these photos!
But Gaogla doesn't love Saikhim anymore!
Why would you make her go back to him?
Love?
Can you live on love?
Love between stupid kids
only exists in soap operas!
Mr. Songseen!
I don't care if you hate me.
But why would you ruin Khim's life?
Are you still a father?
No. You have no heart!
Calm down, miss.
Damn it, Mr. Songseen!
Where were you?
Why was your phone off?
Why are you here?
To talk about important things.
You mean last night?
So last night,
I went to talk about the divorce.
But Gaogla accused me
of killing the baby.
Do you remember when he was in prison,
and I begged you to tell him I miscarried?
An actual divorce?
He said he doesn't wanna rehash things.
He doesn't care anymore.
He doesn't want to explain anymore.
No matter what you think of him,
he doesn't care anymore.
He doesn't love you now.
I want to know
why he accused me
of asking for a divorce first.
Why did he accuse me of killing the baby?
He said that?
When I wrote him that letter,
I actually said I would wait for him.
He's the one who dumped me first.
You remember, right?
Your letter never reached him.
What does that mean?
Your letter was switched out beforehand.
I later found out
that your dad seized your real letter.
What Gla read was a new letter
that your dad wrote.
What? Why didn't you tell me?
Well, I found out later
that the letter Gaogla read wasn't
the one that I brought.
You knew?
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted you to get over that man!
And… when he said…
that he didn't love me anymore?
He didn't say that.
I said it so you'd get over him.
Why?
Your dad
would pay for me to study abroad with you
if I could break you two up.
Do you realize what you've done?
Khim, Gaogla isn't a good match for you.
I don't want him to ruin your future.
Are we still friends?
Why did you betray me like this?
Khim!
Don't let this man come between us!
Khim?
-Khim?
-Khim!
Wait, Lita.
What's wrong with Khim?
What did you talk about?
Was it last night?
Khim!
What's going on?
Why are you fighting?
She acts like I'm not her friend.
Is this about last night?
What did she tell you?
Khim!
If she were really my friend,
she wouldn't go behind my back
or hurt me like this!
So all this time,
she wasn't honest with me.
Khim!
Why did you do this, Lita?
Why did you tell her?
What do you mean?
About last night,
you know I'm not into you.
I love somebody,
and we're getting married.
Why did you do this?
Damn!
Make Tanthai leave Saikhim.
Then you get Tanthai.
It's a win-win situation!
Are we still friends?
Why did you betray me like this?
About last night,
you know I'm not into you.
I love somebody,
and we're getting married.
I didn't think I'd see you here.
We don't know each other.
But I know Carl, your partner.
Are you two friends?
Is "friends" the right word?
Let's call this a word of caution.
I don't want to see you get hurt.
Why would I get hurt?
Well,
I don't want to tell you and have you
waste brain cells worrying about it.
But this really is kind of a big deal.
You should know.
It's about
Carl's ex-wife.
What?
You do know that Carl…
was married?
My Carl was married?
Well, not was.
He still is. They're not divorced yet.
That's impossible.
Why would I lie to you?
I mean well.
I don't want you to look stupid.
Carl's ex is a respectable lady.
Carl must have tricked you,
and you believed every word, right?
Where were you last night, Carl?
Did you forget our date?
I had some business to do.
I had a conference call with America.
I stayed here. I didn't go out.
You didn't think of calling?
Why are you making it a big deal?
Whose is this? Why is it here?
What are you hiding?
Are you seeing someone else?
I've never seen that before.
Is this your wife's?
Are you married?
Is this your wife's lipstick?
Who told you that?
Your eyes did.
How could you hide
such a big secret from me?
I haven't divorced her yet.
But she and I ended it long ago.
So whose lipstick is it?
So you're dating me
to sneak around behind your wife's back?
It suits you
that I fly back and forth all the time.
No wonder Mom warned me
to be careful with you.
I can't believe you tricked me.
Why are you so cruel to me?
Claire!
Your mom's flying home today.
I think you should see her off.
You don't know if you'll meet again.
Shall we deal with everything else later?
I understand
that you and Carl have problems.
If you need my help, tell me right away.
I'm ready to do everything to help you.
What I did to him was…
even worse than this.
I don't know who started all this trouble.
But I'm here for you.
Thank you.
I…
I have no one else left.
Everyone around me,
I feel like
I don't know who any of them really are.
That's good.
You don't have to care about anyone.
Just care about your own feelings.
I understand now
why you walked out of Dad's life.
You're meant to love certain people,
but you're not meant to stay with them.
If you understand that,
when you love someone,
you won't force yourself to do things.
But when
you're not with the person you love,
it doesn't mean you have to hate them.
I feel reassured
now that you have a good partner.
About last night…
You weren't working, right?
I just found out
that Dad forged some documents
and caused trouble for me.
And Lita knew about it.
Hey, did Lita admit this to you?
It happened a long time ago.
Lita said that she did it
because she wanted to study with us.
About last night,
you know I'm not into you.
I love somebody,
and we're getting married.
Why did you do this?
Auntie?
Are you going to the airport now?
Yes. Claire said she can't see me off.
I don't know what's wrong.
She just disappeared.
But when she called,
she didn't sound so good.
I'm worried about her.
Please put my bags in the car.
Miss Claire.
I have an idea.
Let's get Tan to see you off,
and I'll wait here for Miss Claire.
I'll call you when I know more.
Thanks.
I have to go.
Let's go.
I can't let Mom see me like this.
She'd fret and want to stay.
Miss Claire.
Is something seriously wrong?
Have you been tricked by a close friend
to the point that you
can't trust anyone at all?
Yes, I have… and every time they lie,
they all say they're doing it
because they mean well.
Carl lied.
He's married. He has a wife.
They were together last night.
How do you know this?
I uncovered his lie.
And he said he's not divorced yet.
Really?
Mom tried to warn me so many times,
but… I didn't think it would be this bad!
He said they're not together.
All men always say that.
I'm so stupid, aren't I?
I should've known
he moved here with his wife.
What kind of woman leaves men like him?
I think she must be clinging onto Carl.
If you wanna say yes now, you're too late.
I want us to talk like adults.
I want to know.
If we turned back time,
would you really want us to stay together?
Even if all that didn't happen to us then,
I think we still
wouldn't have made it to today.
Look at you now.
If you had to trade
everything you have now
to become that old Gaogla again,
you'd always choose
the future that you have now.
Admit that even if we were still together,
we'd have to break up one day anyway.
Why are you saying this?
Think about it.
Maybe we never really loved each other.
We barely knew each other.
We just got involved
to look after a baby that…
that didn't even mean
to be born as our child.
Why can't we just forget it?
Wanna trade places with me?
I had to fight to survive.
See if you can forget days like those.
Try living in prison.
My dad and my sister starved
to save money to help me.
I was so ashamed to face them
because I'd made the world despise them.
You wanna try living my life?
Then you'd see
why I can't forget those days.
I'm not so obsessed with you
that I can't forget you.
I just remember
the pain that you brought me.
You know what?
In my sleep, I said my murderer's name.
Khim.
Even while I was dying,
I kept thinking of you
while you were having a good time
wherever you were then!
My recovery was long.
I couldn't walk or eat.
I couldn't even open my eyes!
For years, I saw those images
when I closed my eyes.
When I was awake, I couldn't tell
between reality and nightmare.
For years now,
I've been scared to fall asleep
and never wake up again.
Don't die, Gla!
Try living my life,
or go through half what I've been through!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
And you dare preach to me
about letting things go?
I didn't know what you went through.
Don't make that face like you pity me!
If I could choose to do anything,
I wouldn't go back to change our past.
But I'd make you suffer instead of me.
If we could trade places,
I'd do it.
Could you stand it?
If I'd known you were suffering so much,
I would've come back.
But back then, everyone said you died.
-I gotta go.
-I thought you and the baby were gone.
And I was left to live on in pain.
Live on in pain?
You said you live on in pain?
In your beautiful, luxurious life?
If I could make it up to you,
what should I do to make you happy?
Is there still a way
for us to end this amicably?
You really want a divorce?
Give me my time back.
Give me back
the time that you spent with other men.
Try living and breathing as me.
Tell me what you want me to do.
Before becoming someone else's wife,
make it up to me.
If I do this,
you'll sign the divorce papers
and let me go, right?
You have to sacrifice your time.
You have to be at my beck and call.
If you feel nothing when you're with me,
it means we're nothing to each other,
and I'll sign the papers,
and you can go away,
and marry anyone you want.
If it's not what you asked for last night,
I can do it.
That depends on you.
If you can resist me when you're with me,
then I don't have a problem.
Tell me what to do.
TIME BANK
Just tell me.
From now on, you'll stay with me
and do what I ask you to do.
Your duty is
pleasing me till I'm satisfied.
MAN: YOUR FLOWERS ARE HERE
Start by helping me
make up with Claire today.
You have to fix
all the problems you caused
and make Claire take me back.
Is this little favor too much to ask?
I came to check on you.
I know that you're upset,
so I had someone investigate your partner.
So is it true?
He was married once.
But there's something else
that you should know.
He married that woman
because he got her pregnant.
She was just a spoiled brat
who met him in a dating app.
He agreed to marry her
to look after the baby.
I heard that
they didn't live together for long,
and Carl had to travel for work.
She had a miscarriage
and couldn't bear being poor,
so they grew apart.
Since then, they haven't seen each other.
Carl went abroad.
He changed his whole name
when he got adopted,
so they couldn't contact each other.
And that's why
they never managed to get divorced.
But he met up with his wife yesterday.
They were probably arguing
about their marital property.
Carl didn't tell you
because he didn't want you
to worry about this.
It looks like
they don't have such a close relationship.
They haven't gotten divorced yet
'cause they're protecting their interests.
So it was because they had a baby.
No wonder.
Is something wrong?
Carl told me that he made the Arsa app
because he was inspired
while he was interning at a call center.
A kid was left at home, and they called,
asking Gla to find their mom.
And Carl thought
the mom must have gone to work.
He wanted someone to look after the child
so that they wouldn't feel
alone or abandoned.
Carl must have really taken
his deceased baby to heart.
Carl's very sensitive about kids.
Whenever he sees kids,
he always helps them or protects them.
It's like he wants
to do the duties of a dad
for the kids who are still here.
Can I talk to the baby?
Sure.
Hey, kid. This is your dad.
I'm working in the forests.
It's pitch dark,
but the sky is full of stars.
What's your real age?
Seven.
The same age as my child.
If it had survived,
it would be annoying like you.
His heart isn't at ease
because he couldn't protect his own child.
You didn't think
he was such a good guy, right?
Actually, he…
he really deserves compassion.
You should give him another chance.
He told me
to start dating him with zero love
and keep loving him more
instead of loving him 100% first
because if he disappointed me,
all that love would disappear.
I guess he knew
his wife would be an obstacle.
But he made me love him so much,
I'm too deeply in love to back out now.
You have to make that woman meaningless.
I guess that Carl probably
stopped loving that woman a long time ago.
That's true.
I'm sorry I was so stupid.
We should solve these problems together.
I hope you're satisfied.
Here comes the food.
We have all your favorites.
I'm telling you,
the food from this place is so amazing.
Much nicer than what you've had.
You're meant to love certain people,
but you're not meant to stay with them.
If you understand that,
you won't force yourself to do things
when you love someone.
If you're not with the person you love,
it doesn't mean
you have to hate each other, right, honey?
Your brother's raising money
for the app, isn't he?
He wants to expand the app
to reach more users, that's all.
He's not spreading his wings
outside my company with new investors?
We're just looking for more partners.
We haven't closed deals with anyone yet.
Papers, ma'am.
Don't you dare disrespect me.
Look at that old house.
Your brother flattered the owner
and got the deed transferred in his name.
Doing that
is basically betrayal.
That plot of land
must belong to my company alone!
If you betray me, I'll kick you out.
If you didn't have me,
people like you guys wouldn't be here!
Madam, the doctor's here
for the house call.
Who wouldn't be here today without Gla?
How many more years
will she hold on to him?
This is hurting everyone enough.
Is the board here already?
Yes, they're here.
Did you hand out those documents?
No, I heard the meeting agenda changed.
How could that be?
Who changed it?
I've quit politics.
I want to come back
and manage things around here
because Saikhim has to prepare
for her wedding soon.
She probably can't focus
on her CEO duties.
She wants freedom.
She wants to live how she wants.
I can sympathize.
You know, a woman
doesn't get to be a bride so often,
so I want her to fully commit
to the choice she made for herself.
I'd like to take the opportunity
to announce here in this meeting
that from now on,
I'll manage everything here myself.
Dad meant to humiliate me!
He's angry that you didn't
finalize the divorce like he asked.
He wants me to beg for Gaogla's fortune?
He doesn't want the money.
He just wants to waste Gla's time
to get revenge on him.
Dad wants revenge
for making him lose his job?
How is that fair on me?
Why should I fight with everyone
when Dad wants me to?
You'd never take my side anyway.
-Wait, Miss--
-Forget it.
You'll always choose Dad.
You've put up with me for long enough.
Pick me up at the garage now.
You have to sacrifice your time.
You have to be at my beck and call.
Khim!
Let's talk now.
Khim, why didn't you answer my calls?
Are you still angry?
If you're still on Dad's side,
you're really not my friend.
Why are you so angry?
Wait… do you regret losing that man?
I don't regret that.
But I'm hurt
because no one is honest with me.
Khim!
But I did what I did
because I really wanted the best for you.
I don't want you
to get hurt because of him!
You've already seen what he's really like.
When he got rich,
he totally forgot where he came from.
I see.
Dad invited you to the meeting too?
He must have some project
to have you look after.
I won't stand in the way of your success.
-Where to?
-FCT Tower.
I like light roast coffee in the morning.
If you don't know something, ask.
You have to please me. Make an effort.
Why the long face? Just sit and breathe.
The tower's right there.
Would it be faster to walk?
You think I wanna be stuck with you?
Being around me seems
to make you desperate.
What is it?
You have to tidy the garage today.
I'm going to move in.
Don't let me see you.
This is awkward enough.
You have to finish before I get back,
or I won't count the time you spent.
Hey, so you want me to be your servant?
We're husband and wife,
but you're cheating
with your lover all the time,
so I have to reclaim my rights.
If I really filed for divorce,
you could go broke.
-I'll--
-Honey.
Now your job is to make my life easier.
I'll give you lots of stupid tasks to do.
You'll do all the unnecessary stuff,
so I'll have time
to focus on other things.
I don't care enough to think about you.
Do something useful with your time.
Just don't bother me.
What's going on?
I can't help it.
She has to work for that divorce.
Nah, you're just trying
to make her want you back.
Mind what you say.
I'm making sure she has no one left.
So Gla isn't just stalling
because he doesn't want a divorce?
Don't worry. Time won't make us
love each other more.
When you're here, make an effort.
You have to live and breathe me.
You see?
This is why I said
it'd never work out for us anyway!
If you're over a woman,
you have to sever all ties.
I hope Carl means what he says.
I don't want to be stupid anymore.
What's wrong?
Give me the keys!
A car's tailing us.
No!
Something happened!
What is it, Khem?
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit