THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
Return to England immediately.
End of discussion.
I'm pregnant.
Can you please tell me
how I should begin?
Stay here today.
The clinic will see you tomorrow.
We'll go together.
Give me back my car's ECU,
or I'll tell my uncle
that Sakhim ran off with you.
My mom is renting this house.
They won't look for you here.
Miss Khim ran away from home yesterday.
May we search your property?
You asked me how I would raise the kid.
This is how.
I'll raise it where I grew up.
We haven't found her.
We're trying to trace her phone signal.
I think Gaogla is using that kid
to manipulate Khim
to defy us, actually, Uncle.
If we dance to his tune,
he'll have the upper hand.
Do we have better options?
Why don't you try cutting her off, Uncle?
For such greedy people,
women without money are worth nothing,
and Saikhim is no exception.
If you act tough…
and actually cut ties,
Saikhim will realize
that what that man loves is your money.
Gla! Wait, is it really you?
It really is you!
Wow. What are you doing here?
From a distance, I wasn't sure it was you.
Up close,
it's obviously you.
Wow, it really is you!
What happened to your face?
-Who did you fight with?
-Easy!
I'm just heading home this way,
and I thought I should eat.
Whoa, if you turn up like this,
Dad will die of shock.
Are you going home now?
We can go together.
She's coming with us.
I see! Move over.
So you're the one
who's going to the Well-Being School?
Hey, it's me, Gloyjai.
The same Gloyjai
you spoke to on the phone.
So let's go straight to the plantation.
By the way, this is my older brother.
His name is Gaogla.
Gla, since she's coming
to our plantation too,
you drive her there, okay?
I'll follow you.
Sure.
See you at the plantation.
Drive safely, all right? Be careful, okay?
She's your sister?
Yeah.
She thinks you're a guest
going to the plantation.
You have a plantation,
a homestay, and a little sister.
Is there anything else
I don't know about you?
You'll know when we get there.
I'll bring you home
to meet my dad.
I'll introduce you to everyone.
Wait. Hey, what will you introduce me as?
My partner. I'll say we're having a baby.
That's crazy!
If you say that,
what will they think of me?
Can I say
we had a one-night stand and eloped?
Are you nuts? You can't say that either.
You don't want me to lie
or tell the truth.
So define our relationship.
Well…
-Dad.
-Why come back?
And who's that?
-Well…
-Hello, sir.
Dad!
Vroom.
She's here to take the course.
She's from Bangkok.
-Actually--
-Listen, Dad.
I asked Gla
to drive her from the market.
They happened to meet.
It's not his problem.
Why involve him?
You, Gloy,
bring our guest inside.
Of course.
I'll take those.
There.
Come with me, please.
Right this way.
Right this way. Let's go.
Turn right here.
Come on.
All right. Here we are.
This is our school.
There are boards for the kids to write on.
There are the boards.
There's an upper floor too. See?
What a state you've come back in.
What did you do this time?
Didn't you say
you wouldn't be stuck here anymore?
I got a woman pregnant.
I knew it!
If nothing had happened,
you wouldn't have come crawling back!
I wanna bring her here to raise it.
You good-for-nothing.
How would you take care of them?
So you won't let us stay?
Damn right! I won't!
The kid can stay.
But you can't stay!
Go and change your ways first.
Then come back and be its dad!
Come on. This way, please.
Come. I'll take your bags.
I thought you weren't coming.
You didn't answer my calls.
I'll show you around, okay?
This way, I'll show you
lots of pretty places.
Let's go.
Why are there so many kids here?
Right, I forgot to mention
that apart from teaching self-reliance,
we do homeschooling.
These kids' parents aren't here.
The kids were sent here
to live with their grandparents.
Let's go.
Dad decided to provide daycare
while their families are working.
In the evening, they all go home.
We take care of all the kids
whose families can't cope alone.
I'd like you to give me sole custody.
I can raise just one kid.
So this is how it is.
Let's go over there.
Come on.
It must be nice to live here.
See this house?
It's called a mud house.
A mud house?
Dad teaches mud house construction
and lessons on self-reliance.
Here,
we teach people to live with nature,
spend less money,
live simple lives,
and focus on what's important.
By the way,
what's your name?
You can call me Khim.
Khim.
Khim, you did a great job
driving alone all this way.
But don't worry.
I promise it's very safe around here.
-Let's go.
-Wait.
So… about your brother…
You mean Gla?
Are you afraid of him?
You don't have to be.
He never hangs around for long.
He comes and goes.
Right.
So, did he grow up here too?
Yeah, he did.
But he moved out a long time ago.
He might be a bit rebellious and chaotic,
but don't hold that against him.
I guess he doesn't see
beautiful women that often,
so he can't contain himself.
By the way, you'll learn about food today.
Dad will show you
how to harvest veggies to cook with.
Are you ready?
-Yeah. Okay.
-Come on.
In a world like ours,
we never have to go hungry.
To be self-reliant is to know
how to live on what we have.
This is duckweed.
Some people call it Asian watermeal.
Psst.
I scooped it from the pond just now.
It may look weird,
but it's very beneficial.
It's high in protein.
So today, I'll toast some duckweed
for you to have a taste.
To begin,
you spoon it up to drain it
just like this.
And then,
we take all this filth and throw it away.
By the way, honey, it's even better
when anyone wants favors
because we can give them these blessings.
Yes, we give them these blessings.
And we give them these blessings.
We can give them
a whole basket of blessings.
Hey!
Watch it, Gloy.
Well,
I guess Dad taught you a lesson.
Come on, man. Who did you get pregnant?
Dad almost lost it, you know?
Back off, kid.
Keep your nose out of my business.
Hey, I'm not sticking my nose in it.
I'm just curious, that's all.
So, your girlfriend,
who is she?
She's not an exotic dancer, right?
What?
With your reputation,
if exotic dancers don't want you,
then who would?
-Damn.
-What?
Don't go yet. Let's talk first.
Gla!
I want to talk to you!
Damn.
Guess we can't stay here after all.
Your dad's unhappy about it, isn't he?
I can tell he knows the truth.
Let's stay for now.
We'll leave tomorrow.
Where else would we go?
Admit it.
You're not ready to take care of this kid.
I'm not the one we should worry about.
I can go anywhere.
I just don't want you
to struggle in these eight months.
Once it's born,
we can go our separate ways.
If I don't take care of you properly,
your dad will mock me.
-You jerk!
-Dad.
You can't be trusted!
What, Dad?
-Damn it. I'll teach you!
-Hey! Dad!
-What are you doing here?
-Dad, enough.
-Dad!
-You…
What are you doing here?
Wait, mister!
What's going on?
Did he molest you?
-You little--
-Wait!
-No.
-Dad! Listen first!
Why? Well?
-Please calm down.
-Dad!
-No!
-Mister…
You depraved sex addict.
You sowed your wild oats everywhere!
Mister, please calm down.
Were you molested?
No, he didn't.
Hey, Dad, you're out of line--
-Out of line?
-Dad!
How dare you talk back?
And why did you come in here?
Why can't I be here?
She's my woman!
-What?
-She's the woman I got pregnant.
You're his woman?
Did you abduct her?
Dad!
Who do you think I am, Dad?
You're so young.
How did Gla fool you into this?
Or did you come willingly?
She just happened to get pregnant
with me, that's all.
It just happened?
Look, she's pregnant.
How dare you say, "that's all"?
She's my girlfriend.
What's wrong with having a baby together?
We love each other
and want to have a family together.
Come with me.
What about your parents?
Can they accept this?
I can feed my family, Dad.
We'll take care of this
despite what anyone says.
You took advantage of someone's daughter.
No parent would forgive you for that!
Dad, you're under no obligation
to do anything for us.
We'll never be burdens to you.
Come on.
Gla! You're hotheaded and impatient.
You good-for-nothing.
What have you ever done right?
I don't think you'll manage
to take care of anyone.
Come on.
Why did you lie like that?
If I'd told the truth,
he would've dragged me
to beg for your dad's forgiveness.
Do you want our unborn baby
to lose its dad?
Now I'm not so sure
that you can cope with raising this kid.
But this is the only place
where your dad won't look for our baby.
And what'll happen when I go home?
We'll just say we broke up.
Hey. Wait.
So if I stay here,
I have to pretend to be your girlfriend?
Just pretend, you know,
like one of those TV dramas.
For up to eight months?
I can't manage that.
You don't mind being pregnant,
but you mind living with me, right?
No, I don't mind.
Don't do this for me.
Don't be my girlfriend.
Just be our baby's mom.
That's what I'm afraid of.
So let's be roommates. Let's share a room.
I'm a gentleman. I'm not easily tempted.
We know that's not true.
Say something else.
I'm not your type
just like you're not my type.
Does that sound better?
Finished your shower?
Good water pressure?
Take your shower.
You're the one who dodges the question
You're the only one
who dodges the question
You're the one who dodges the question
Will we survive?
The power went off.
Don't worry. I forgot to tell you.
We have blackouts here some nights.
So… what do we do?
We do this.
Afraid of ghosts?
No.
Why are you so scared?
Don't.
It's a prayer book.
It keeps ghosts away.
Pray. Find inner peace.
Avoid unwholesome thoughts.
Don't overthink or complicate things.
Try go behave virtuously.
Tame your heart.
Think of your parents' faces.
Making fun of me?
Having nice dreams?
I'm back.
Hey.
There it is.
Rich kids can't live
without these things, can they?
They have to…
Give me that.
I'll take care of it.
Gloy?
Hi, Khim. You're awake already?
Are you hungry yet?
Can I help?
Since you're not a client,
Dad says you don't have to do the course.
You can just live with us.
Right now, the kids and I
are preparing to cook.
What's on the menu today?
There's no fried chicken
and no grilled chicken on the menu.
We call it the potluck menu.
-The potluck menu?
-Yeah.
Today, everyone has to find
ingredients to cook with.
Once in a while, we trade these eggs
with our neighbors instead of shopping.
Hello there.
These kids have to speak to them,
get to know them,
and trade with them,
taking whatever they're given.
They either give us
veggies from their gardens,
or their animals.
You see, Dad teaches us
to appreciate the value of food.
It's not easy to grow
or to raise each food item.
That's why we shouldn't waste food.
Come on.
Sometimes, instead of eggs,
we offer our time in exchange.
Around here, we don't have
convenience stores.
Instead, we give away, harvest,
and consume what's "conveniently" there.
We're not just cashless.
Actually, some days,
we don't use any kind of money at all.
Look, honey.
This is the potluck menu.
It depends on what we can find each day.
We have to consume
what we have and what we can find,
not whatever we want.
Kids, wash your hands.
You don't mind this?
Actually, I think it'll be great.
Okay.
Get in line.
Get in line first, kids.
Come on.
We collected these veggies.
This is Uncle Kaew's tofu.
Sir?
Did you forget something?
What did I forget?
You didn't add these.
Okay, add them.
What are those?
Would you like some?
-You'll share them with me?
-Yes.
All right. I'll have some.
Don't.
It's crunchy.
You like to eat tadpoles?
Baby frogs.
-What?
-You like them?
-They're everywhere.
-Go to her.
Go on.
Ew!
I ate… frogs?
Yeah. Tadpoles.
Well?
You trust me with our kid yet?
I can imagine how it will grow up.
Not as deprived as you thought, right?
These kids' lives are better than mine
even if their parents aren't here.
Dad makes everyone here happy instantly
with no exceptions.
We don't have to be rich or ready for it.
If everything had to be ready in advance,
these kids would never have been born.
In that case,
our unborn child doesn't need
a mom like me, right?
Of course you're needed.
You just have to accept
that our lives can't always be perfect.
No one here was raised by their parents.
We'd be waiting a long time
for the whole family to be reunited.
Here, you get the love you need.
You don't have to be a good student.
If you can get dressed and wipe your butt,
you can be happy right now.
Being happy with what we have is the best.
Yes?
I want to ask you for a favor.
I'd like to take a year off
to find myself.
Don't sugarcoat it.
Say you don't want
to go back to university.
You probably know about my problem.
I want to use this time
to solve it myself.
How will you do that? Explain.
In my year off,
I'll have my baby.
After the birth,
I'll give him sole custody
and go back to university.
You have the nerve to have the baby?
What about how that makes me look?
Do you care more about that man
than your own future?
Has he brainwashed you again?
Dad.
Life may have taken unexpected turns,
but maybe that's okay.
Who said it's okay?
You're losing an opportunity of a lifetime
for this nonsense?
And all for what?
And you think my life is good right now?
Better than being a delinquent!
This obsession is clouding your mind.
You've dominated my whole life.
Is that so different?
Of course it is.
Who the hell is that bastard?
He's not even honest with you.
He's using your unborn baby to trap you.
He loves your money.
He doesn't love you.
If you're stupid enough
to let him leech off you,
run into his arms.
With a daughter this stupid,
I wouldn't mind being childless.
I wonder.
If you weren't my daughter,
would he want you?
So…
I guess you still won't forgive me?
Of course not.
At least dogs can be tamed.
Children who disappoint you
aren't worth having.
You haven't changed, Dad.
Did you know that when I was little,
I would pretend to be asleep
so that you'd pick me up
and take me to my bed?
But you never did that, not even once.
Forget picking me up.
You probably don't even want
to look at me anymore.
I understand now
why I've been so unhappy for so long.
It's because you
set the bar too high for me.
That's why life is hard.
I have to be a good student,
I have to go to a Top Five university,
I have to live a life
that others would envy,
and I mustn't embarrass you.
It's too difficult, Dad.
I'm so tired.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
I understand now
why I've been so unhappy for so long.
It's because you
set the bar too high for me.
That's why life is hard.
I mustn't embarrass you.
It's too difficult, Dad.
Everything…
that I've done for you…
has it really hurt you this much?
I'm a bad father, aren't I?
Okay, this square is your house.
That's Gloy's team's house.
This is my team's house.
We all have to stand on the houses.
-All right.
-Okay? Don't stand on the cement floor.
We all stand on the houses.
-Are you ready? Are you?
-I'm ready!
Go!
-Hurry!
-Go on!
Stand here.
-There.
-Can you fit on?
-Did you all make it?
-Yeah!
Both teams made it.
It's a draw!
Yay!
Clap your hands.
It's a draw.
-What's the game called?
-Come on.
-"Come In."
-All right.
-Come on.
-New round.
-Now come in.
-We'll fold the houses in half.
-All right?
-Can we play too, Dad?
Right. Okay. What do you think?
-Sure. Let's play.
-Gloy, count them.
-Count the players.
-Wait.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four, five.
Dad is out. Too many people.
-I'll be the referee.
-Okay? Good.
-Now fold the houses in half.
-All right.
-There.
-In this round, the houses are smaller.
-Half the size.
And we have more players.
You all must stand on the houses.
Are you ready?
-Ready!
-Ready? And your team?
Ready?
Go!
Both teams made it.
Another draw.
Get ready.
See, everyone?
Whether our house is big or small,
it's not a problem.
As long as we love,
support, and care for each other,
we can always be together.
Serves you right.
Not so hard.
You thought you were so tough.
Stay still.
You still wanna show everyone
that you're a tough guy?
When the baby's born,
I'll show you that I can lift you both.
By then,
I might not be here anymore.
It's a long way off.
I can pick you up when you're nearly due.
Take good care of it, okay?
We can both take care of it already.
This stage of pregnancy is important too.
We need you here.
Good job cheering me up.
You can change your mind and stay with us.
Right.
Would you really leave me and the baby?
I know you're not a cruel person.
You're just scared, right?
It's late.
Let's go to sleep.
We have to get up early.
THE WELL-BEING SCHOOL
Khim.
Are you okay?
Gla…
Khim, have some water.
Whoa, this is serious.
What? What's serious?
You're seriously into her.
I saw you running around.
Okay, you guys take care of the kids.
Think of it as parenting practice.
Where's Dad?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe he went to deliver veggies.
You called me? Which one is he?
Right. It's this gentleman.
Chrysanthemum tea from our own plantation.
Mom had it when she was carrying Gloyjai.
I looked up chrysanthemum blossoms.
They can soothe mouth ulcers
as well as light-headedness.
I guess this might be good
for your nausea.
Please sit.
Mr. Songseen,
I want to talk about our kids.
I'll take responsibility
for the damage to your daughter's life.
If you don't mind,
my son wants to marry Saikhim.
Is it the bride-price?
Take it back.
You think your son is a match
for my daughter?
Even if he died and were reborn,
I doubt he'd be enough.
If you can't love your own daughter,
let me adopt her.
Your own son grew up a degenerate.
You think you'd be
a better father than me?
My daughter would end up
a good-for-nothing like him anyway.
A parent's word is sacred.
Whatever we keep saying they are,
in the end, that's who they'll be.
Do not preach at me!
I'm not preaching. I'm just warning you.
From now on,
no matter what happens in her life,
I will make her proud of herself again.
Then, at least,
they'll be better parents than you.
…all right?
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
No problem.
Do you crave something special
that'll soothe your nausea?
This is enough for me.
Do you want that?
-Hi there.
-Hello.
-One set, please.
-Sure.
I'll buy you a drink.
Two bottles of water, please.
Sure.
That's Dad's car.
Where is he?
I'm doing the deliveries today.
Why is he here too?
Maybe he's around here.
Try calling him.
Sorry. That number can't be reached…
His phone's turned off or dead.
Where has he gone?
It's late and he's not back.
If he wasn't delivering veggies too,
then where did he go?
Why did he leave his car at the market?
-Gloy.
-Yeah?
Find the spare keys.
I'll search the car for clues.
Sure.
Gla!
What?
What's this number?
Why did Dad write it down?
That's a Bangkok number.
Maybe he went to Bangkok.
Okay, I'll call the number.
Hello.
Luxe Hotel.
He must have gone to see my dad.
How does my dad know yours?
Dad asked me to grab your ID card
and make a photocopy of it.
I guess he figured it out.
This is bad.
If they meet each other,
Dad will get hurt for sure.
Hey, the minibus is coming.
Dad!
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you, of course.
You went to Bangkok?
You should be at school by now.
Go on!
Dad!
Uncle?
You went to see my dad, right?
Yes, I went to ask his permission
for Gla to marry you.
Dad!
He would say we're beneath him.
Why did you go looking for trouble?
You abducted her,
got her pregnant,
and whisked her away from home, right?
He told you that?
You're not dating like you claimed.
Did my dad insult you?
Did he hurt you?
Are you hurt?
Hey.
You have the cheek to care?
He said he has no daughter to give away.
He's cut off his own daughter.
It's all your fault.
He told me that he disowned you
for daring to keep the kid.
Khim?
Is it true?
Why didn't you tell me you spoke to him?
I've only ever looked after myself.
I've never had to take responsibility
for anyone else's life.
If you're willing to take my baby,
I'd like to leave it here with you.
I wouldn't ask more of you than that.
But I'm sure that you all would take
better care of it than I could.
So I decided to have the baby.
And after the birth,
if you couldn't go home,
where would you live?
I'll have it figured out by then.
For now, I need time to readjust, please.
Well?
Do you see now?
You see what happens
when you let emotions run your life?
You wanted to care for the baby,
but you didn't help her,
and now she's alone.
Your decisions
break her heart, you know that?
Khim!
You don't have to feel guilty
because of me.
You've done enough to make it up to me.
I do want to take care of you.
But I know your future is better
than being stuck with me.
So I didn't commit to asking you
to live with me.
I don't want to drag you down with me.
If you don't mind,
let's live here together.
I'm serious.
It's not just the kid.
I can look after you too.
I'm not rich,
but I promise that with me,
you won't go hungry, you'll sleep well,
and most importantly,
you'll be happy from now
until the day you die.
But you said I wasn't your type.
I'm not into rich girls.
You aren't one now.
If you don't have expensive tastes,
I can look after you.
So what do you say?
Would you live here with me?
Who would I be to you here?
You'd be my lady.
And the mother of our child.
You're being so sweet and silly.
Will you regret it later?
No.
I won't regret a single word
that I've said today.
Let's go home together.
What are you doing?
Don't couples take each other's photo?
-Khim?
-Yeah?
Hey!
Khim,
we've come this far.
We…
Gla!
Dad asked me to stay with Khim.
Hey! How come?
Well, well.
There.
Dad said that if you're not married,
you must never sleep together, ever!
Got it?
Khim.
-Let's go, Khim.
-Stop!
Wait. Don't you dare run away together.
Dad would kill you for sure!
Go on. Go and sleep at home.
Khim.
Go to bed.
-Good night, Khim.
-Good night.
Go on. Hurry up.
Why won't he leave?
I don't get you. You're so rich.
You're well-educated.
Why is your taste in men so weird?
Rich girls like you
don't marry guys around here.
What a party pooper.
See you in our dreams, then.
Sweet dreams.
Leave my daughter alone.
Don't use this baby to manipulate her.
You can't even survive on your own.
How can you look after a woman?
I admit that I don't have
the resources you do.
Although I can't afford a gilded cage,
I can give her the sky.
You should think about it.
Between a gilded cage and the sky,
which would a bird rather have?
Even if I had nothing but my body,
you still couldn't beat me
because you never let her be free,
so she flies back to me, the scumbag.
Yeah!
So we mix in the husks with our feet.
And we check that the husks
mix nicely with the mud.
We scatter the husks all over,
and we keep on stomping
so that the husks
and the mud blend into one.
-Khim?
-Yeah?
Will this really make
more people notice us?
Yeah.
We upload these to Facebook,
and we get people signing up.
This way, people will hear about us
not just in Thailand,
but around the world.
But how can we upload them?
We don't really have fast Internet here.
We have to go
and use the Internet at school,
or the Internet cafés in town.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Tell me what else I can get you
aside from the Internet.
Really?
I can do even better.
Gla!
How dare you come back?
Khim, watch out!
Go back the way you came!
Back off, Khim.
Hey!
Hey, Gla! That's enough.
Gla, come on!
Do you want to see a doctor?
It's okay.
Just don't let Dad know.
Why did they have to do that?
It's what happens when they hate you.
But don't be afraid.
They wouldn't dare come to our home.
Don't tell me. I know who it was.
Gla's former accuser.
Do you know about Gla's record?
That's why people in town are afraid
of Gla being back here.
So what happened back then?
I've heard that it was an assault case.
Do you think Gla and I look alike?
Okay, but you're wrong.
Gla and I have different dads.
Gla is from Mom's first marriage.
When he was younger,
Gla looked such a lot like a Westerner,
and people teased us
about my dad being Gla's stepfather.
Some people were even saying
Gla was someone else's love child.
Hey, you have to practice
so you can get better.
You should be able to use it
with closed eyes, like it's part of you,
then you can work.
Hey!
What's up, daddy's little boy?
Ignore them. Come on, Gla.
Going hand in hand to get a DNA test?
Just look in the mirror.
Then you can tell who your mom slept with.
-What did you say?
-Gla, don't.
Didn't you hear me?
I'll say it again really clearly.
Your mom slept with an adulterer.
Is your face a blessing,
or is it a curse
that betrays your mom's shamelessness?
-No, Gla. No!
-My family is not your business!
Out of my way!
Gla, don't.
Don't let me see you again.
Gla almost got that scumbag killed.
He dared to stir up trouble
because his dad was a local politician,
and we leased their land to plant on,
so he thought he could insult us
however he liked.
Gla was charged with attempted murder
and sent straight to a juvenile hall.
He just couldn't stand
seeing Dad get insulted like that.
Because of the incident,
they made us leave that land.
Dad sold everything we had
to pay for that guy's treatments.
Then we moved out here.
Back then, Mom and Dad struggled a lot.
Mom was sick,
but she refused to get treatment.
So Gla blamed himself
for making us go so broke.
By the time he was released,
Mom had died.
Mom left Gla in Dad's care
during his suspended sentence.
Why are you running off?
You'll have no future if you drop out.
School is useless
if we stay poor like this!
You wanna be the degenerate
they say you are?
Wait and see.
I'll save our reputation.
At least, I'll make sure
you and Mom aren't ashamed I'm yours.
None of us has to be stuck here, Dad.
This is not where our future ends!
THE WELL-BEING SCHOOL
Dad wanted Gla to come home.
But Gla didn't want to.
Instead, he wanted to save our reputation.
So he went to Bangkok
to make money and send it home,
hoping to help Dad live
with his head held high.
But Dad never believed
that Gla would do honest work,
so he was worried
that Gla would get thrown in prison again.
That's why Dad has never spent
a single baht that Gla sent to us.
He put it all into Gla's account
because he didn't like
how Gla used money to prove himself.
Ever since, Gla has not dared to face Dad.
Dad wants Gla to go back to school.
But Gla thinks diplomas
and degrees aren't important.
He thinks that if we focus
on making lots of money,
no one else will look down on us again.
So he makes money
by working in that garage.
Dad and Gla have different perspectives.
But actually, both of them
always make sacrifices for other people.
Dad would do anything
to protect our family.
As for Gla,
he chose to move away from us
to build up a fortune for us.
Except for the way they look,
the two of them couldn't be more similar.
It's like Gla inherited
almost everything from Dad.
Especially his dedication
to his loved ones.
Khim.
I'm sorry.
There are no parts,
so your laptop can't be repaired yet.
It's all right.
While I'm here, I won't be needing it.
I'll buy you a new one.
Sure.
While you're here,
can you use this instead?
Hey, this was with you?
You left it with me, so I kept it safe.
Thank you.
This one is really important to me.
When I go somewhere I like,
I try to capture the atmosphere
in a sketch in this book.
This book
is like a book of all my happy thoughts.
All the things I love
are in here.
That's good.
I have a place for my happiness too.
Really? Where?
I keep it here.
And in here.
From now on,
you'll probably have
a lot more to put there.
From now on,
your head is going to get so huge.
And your heart will grow really large too.
That's good.
I can't believe
we can just build a whole house ourselves.
It's so easy.
It saves you money,
and you don't get into debt.
People spend 20 or 30 years
paying off their houses.
They could have lived like this.
Okay, Khim.
It's a bit dusty.
So I stomp on this?
Yeah, step on the husks to mix everything.
Yeah, stomp hard.
Yeah, keep stomping.
Come on. Stomp harder.
-Yeah. Stomp it.
-Wait a second.
Come on.
-Here. Yeah.
-Wait!
Are you teasing me?
Stomp hard.
Look, Khim. Push it in like this.
All right.
Come on.
-Lift?
-Lift, Khim.
One, two, three.
Yeah.
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
It happens.
-That's it?
-Yeah.
Can I try?
Sure.
Are you mocking me?
No.
-You're so muddy.
-Wipe it off.
I'm wiping. See?
It's everywhere.
-Wipe it properly.
-There. I'm rubbing it off.
-Khim?
-It's gone.
I don't think so.
-What?
Khim.
-Where are you going?
-Let go.
-Whoa, you're making fun of me.
-Don't come any closer.
-Mocking me?
-Don't.
Sorry. Don't!
Khim! Where are you going?
-Mocking me, are you?
-Take that!
Mocking me?
Hey, what soap is that? It smells great.
Sit down.
Is it vanilla?
Hey!
Now it smells like oranges.
And it's a long-lasting fragrance.
It smells delicious.
Yeah.
-Hey!
-Whoa!
I know what you're thinking.
Don't even think about it.
Let me wash.
There.
This one, right?
All right. It's your turn.
-What?
-It's your turn.
Do your worst.
Do it. Don't be gentle. I don't mind.
We all think of someone
when we listen to music,
when we read books,
when we watch movies.
The truth is
one day, we could turn into
mere memories of the times we shared.
Don't be so scared.
Maximize every second of happiness.
From now on,
there'll be no Saikhim Kidakarn.
There'll be only Saikhim Chayodom.
I'll never love you less.
I'll only love you more every day.
He fooled her
into signing a marriage certificate.
He wants to hit the jackpot.
-Hey, Khem!
-Gla!
If he's arrested,
Saikhim has nowhere to go.
Do you want me to bring her back?
What now, bro?
It's too late to get the money out.
We need to talk, okay?
The university has received a complaint.
It's about your scholarship approval.
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit