THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
They said you were dead.
I'm too stubborn to die.
So why are you here?
To watch my enemy die.
What's Prom doing?
Asking someone to investigate Gaogla.
Don't get involved. It could be a trap.
He wants us to get suspicious
so he can entrap us for snooping.
So you're the larcenist.
Teach him a lesson
so that he doesn't do it again.
I'll find out
what he wants to use that property for.
I'm good at punching below the belt.
Should I have you try staying the night?
-Well…
-Stay here tonight.
I promise you
that someone will lose more than we did.
I've never wanted to hurt anyone!
But today, I wish you would die!
Hey!
Technology exists to help
make our lives easier.
But it never makes our love lives easier.
We could meet someone easily
or fall in love easily.
But it's harder to build relationships.
You're still here?
I want a bath too.
Clean living? More like dirty-minded.
Wait, Khim.
Khim?
What's wrong?
Sorry, I have to go.
But what about…?
You want an aromatherapy massage?
TANTHAI TULANONT, CHIEF FINANCIAL OFFICER
PRIMPRAO
Look what I've found.
I guess Gaogla and Tanthai are doing
business deals together.
Tan's doing this?
Impossible.
Hey, you.
Hey, you!
What the hell? He's already asleep?
Khim, you're about to get married.
Try acting like a jealous wife.
Is he being so nice to you
because he did something to hurt you?
Figure out what he's feeling guilty about.
If you can't figure it out,
don't marry him.
A NEW LOAN FOR HOMESTAY PROPRIETORS
A NEW INVESTMENT
Did you know
Tanthai's invested in Gaogla's company?
Tan doesn't really talk to me about work.
Doesn't he know
that you and Gaogla are enemies?
I can't let our personal problems
interfere with Tan's work.
When we asked him to invest in our hotels,
he didn't care.
Does this mean Tanthai doesn't respect us?
He must not want us to know
so he kept this quiet.
Gosh, I guess he's taking Khim for granted
if he doesn't care how this affects her.
But he's not the only one at fault.
Khim is keeping something from him too.
You can't tell him
that you're Gaogla's ex.
So is there any man
who will be honest with my daughter?
You keep getting duped by them.
Gla!
So you want me to accept the bank's offer?
Okay.
Then we'll see
if we can put fear in their hearts.
We couldn't have got to them
if there were no profit involved.
There's no way.
They want me so badly.
You know what they just did?
They invited me to go yachting with them.
He's supposed to get married soon,
but his dad is throwing him at me.
Women like Saikhim don't deserve
good relationships.
Yeah. You never know.
Maybe she'll never get married.
Hey, Khim. What are you doing here?
I came to visit you, Tan.
Call me in advance next time.
I was just leaving. You nearly missed me.
I just happened to be in the area.
Are you on your way to work, Tan?
Today's a holiday.
I have a little work meeting.
Is it very urgent work?
Maybe you should hang out at my place.
I'll be right back after work.
It's okay. You should get to work.
Khim.
I'll call you right after work.
Don't worry about me.
Of course work is more important.
You can't compare love with work, Khim.
I'm negotiating with Carl's company.
It's my dad's project, Khim.
We don't know if we'll partner with them.
I didn't tell you
because I noticed
that you have a problem with him.
I didn't want to upset you.
So… why are you telling me now, Tan?
I wanted to tell you myself.
I don't want you to worry
or get upset by something
that someone with bad intentions said.
Thank you, Tan.
Now you're the only one
who's still honest with me.
I heard you've seen the Kidakarns.
How did that go?
They must be shocked you're still alive.
I don't know. I didn't care.
What?
Didn't you want to move back here
to get revenge on those people?
It's just a coincidence.
I don't care about those people.
So this relationship must be very serious
if it's made you get over Saikhim.
Ever since that day,
Saikhim lost all meaning to me.
Didn't you get her cousin arrested?
Weren't you trying to mess with her?
Don't worry about old flames.
Who would dare do something
that you didn't like?
What if I said I didn't like Claire?
Would you dare dump the girl?
That's easy.
There's nothing I wouldn't do for you.
I hope that's true because I'm so tired
of people who don't mean what they say.
Claire is very sweet.
I'll introduce her to you.
You're infatuated with her.
You're so obvious.
I'm head over heels.
Love stinks, doesn't it?
Any updates on the old house
that I asked you to check out?
I spoke to the owner.
And? Could it be our first boutique hotel?
It's quite pretty.
But I think it could be more than that.
What could be better than making it
a hotel to mock our competitors?
A new hotel
opposite the Kidakarns' hotel.
Not only will we get rich,
we'll also get to insult those people.
I haven't thought that far
because the owner doesn't want to sell it.
I asked you to work for me,
not run a charity!
You still can't prioritize business?
I'm starting to wonder
if you care about Saikhim's feelings.
Not at all.
I don't care about those people.
And I won't condescend
to compete with them.
Then maybe you're focusing
on your application too much,
so you're not dedicated
to following my orders.
Do you still care about me?
I guess there's a lot
I still have to teach you
just like your first day in this job.
I even had to teach you to put on a tie.
Aren't you afraid of losing…
what your dad left behind for you?
Don't you want to take over from him?
You're lucky to be his son.
You should live up to this life,
not throw it away.
Khem.
Hey.
What are you wearing?
A collar.
Someone tried to put a leash on me.
Anyway, what are you doing?
Madame asked me
to throw out your dad's stuff.
Hey, bro.
The interesting part is
there are documents she wanted to destroy.
I tried to put them back together,
but I couldn't read them,
so I searched your dad's computer.
Bingo. I found these files.
Take this stuff.
I used a translation app
and found that it's your dad's will.
I thought there wasn't one.
Well, there is.
Your mom's name's in it too.
MR. ALEKSAY, MRS. ASIA, MR. NATHAN,
MS. RAKROY BOONRUEANG
Your dad wanted
to give you a portion of his estate.
But Madame chose not to use this will
because she didn't want you to take it.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
She adopted you herself
to disinherit you
from her husband's estate.
She wants to keep your inheritance
all to herself and her son.
So that's the price of her kindness.
I'll never let any woman control my life.
We got all of it.
I told her I'd get rid of it.
If that will is real,
she's more dangerous than I thought.
Tan has admitted
he's doing business with Gaogla.
He said that, and you believe him?
That woman you saw is Gaogla's sister.
Tan isn't interested in her.
But I'm more worried about Tan
getting conned by those people.
If he's not interested in her,
maybe he's interested in her money.
Money is the great leveler.
You sound like you don't know Tan.
So you'll just let this go?
Listen.
Stop being an angel all the time
as if you're scared he won't love you.
When you're a woman,
the meaner you are,
the more they love you.
Got it?
But if you're mean,
and you only attract that sort of guy,
that's not so good.
Will he ever leave you alone?
If we build new condos,
I'll reserve a penthouse
for you to decorate.
Where are these condos?
What?
Hasn't Saikhim told you?
We're building condos opposite our hotel.
I want you to decorate…
our marital home.
I hope they find a cure
for your wishful thinking.
To make a full recovery,
I need someone to make me better.
Serious question.
How did you get so conceited?
You'll see.
Eventually, you'll end up with me.
We're a good match
'cause we know each other's flaws.
I can't believe
you can stand people like him.
Really? Do I look like I can stand him?
If he were the last person on Earth,
I still wouldn't want him.
Thank goodness. Don't let your guard down.
Prom is in there.
Let's go somewhere else.
He'll definitely yell at you.
Let's go.
You fooled Khim today,
but you can't fool her forever.
You should worry about yourself first.
Wait. Hey!
Damn. What a stupid double agent.
He doesn't know
he's getting Gaogla's sloppy seconds,
and he's his errand boy too.
Look, honey.
Dad?
I got your vegetables.
If I eat any more of them,
I'll be able to photosynthesize.
Why did you send so much?
I want to feed you the good stuff.
It's for the seventh anniversary
of your death and rebirth.
You were given a new life.
Take very good care of it.
Gla!
Don't die!
Stay strong!
Don't die, Gla!
I used a translation app
and found that it's your dad's will.
She wants to keep your inheritance
all to herself and her son.
I want you to be careful.
You were lucky to wake up.
Jeez, I know.
You have to be very grateful
to your adoptive mother.
She helped give you a new life.
Without her,
you wouldn't be there now.
Is she still kind to you?
Don't worry, Dad.
I'll never forget what she did.
I'll pay her back double
everything she's done.
Hi, bro.
I checked your Mac.
This morning, Madame called
to pressure me about the boutique hotel.
She said she'd find an architect
to renovate that house.
Boutique hotel?
She sent us a project plan that she likes.
It's saved on the laptop.
I'll bring it to you.
SEARCHING FOR JOB HUNTERS
ACCEPT
KASALONG SANGCHAI
Hello.
I'm looking for a housekeeper.
Could you take care of my place
while I'm away?
Yes, I can.
Three or four hours should be enough.
I'll be back tonight.
Please tidy up the place
and put my clothes away.
I'll send you all the details.
All right.
CARL RAMAN, CANAPAYA RESIDENCES
Since they're aristocrats,
are you gonna kneel to them?
I don't want them to think
we just want to buy their house.
I want this to feel like a family visit.
I don't want to push them too soon.
Hey, bro.
Maybe they need money
and want to sell the house.
Say that, and they'll be insulted
that we're throwing money at them.
We won't be greedy capitalists
like the Kidakarns.
We will never look so desperate for money.
That's so rude.
I spoke to your sister about the project.
Gloyjai is new to investing.
Please feel free to give her tips.
No problem.
I'm sure you two will get along.
Yes.
We brought Indian gooseberries.
They're indigenous and medicinal.
-They're for you.
-Gosh!
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, my dear, for bringing me these.
My dad has a plantation in the North.
He raised me on medicinal food.
Really, dear? Look at that huge basket.
We can't possibly eat all that.
The hotel opposite us over there
just brought it to us.
They had their people speak to me.
They want to buy my property
and build new condos here.
-I'll take this.
-All right.
Come on.
Let's go, kids.
New condos?
That's right, dear.
But let me tell you something.
I don't think I'll sell it to them
because I think
I will end up dying right here, my dear.
Why would you say that?
Anyway, you boys are here now.
-All right. Chor?
-Yes?
Why don't we
make Indian gooseberry chili paste?
Then they can taste it.
Does that sound good?
-Yes, ma'am.
-All right?
Yes, ma'am.
Have you ever tried that, boys?
I can't wait to have some.
Well, wait just a moment.
-Let's go.
-Let's go and make some now.
-Yes, ma'am.
It's not his first name.
His birthday?
His ID card number?
One more attempt left.
Are you avoiding me?
I know you're in there.
He's not here.
He left it open to tempt me.
Password?
Jeez. Don't send him a notification!
Damn! I'm screwed!
HI, SOMEONE TRIED TO LOG IN…
Someone tried to use my Mac.
It was in that room this morning.
Who went in there?
Hello.
Miss, are you at my condo?
Well… I got here
and happened to run into your girlfriend.
My girlfriend?
That's right.
A petite woman
who looks rich and pretty,
and… she's wearing revealing clothes.
She's not my girlfriend.
Don't worry. I'll deal with this.
Damn!
Hello. What do you want?
What are you doing at my place?
Well, didn't you say
that we could keep it casual?
Are you backing down?
When did I ever say that to you?
Are you doing something to my Mac?
No, I must have touched it by mistake
when I put my stuff down.
Stop playing dirty to get intel on me.
Don't you Kidakarns know
how to fight honorably?
-Look…
-Remember this.
Your condos will never happen.
Get out of my place right now.
And return my key card.
If you keep interfering,
I'll ban your friend's place
from the system
for security issues.
Wait. What?
Damn it!
Okay, I give up.
They haven't learned.
How dare they try to steal your laptop?
So we're fighting cornered dogs.
This game is unexpectedly brutal.
Fortunately,
we have the upper hand.
Here it is!
-Bring it out.
-Come on.
Bring it out quickly.
Good.
-Put it down.
-May I sit here?
-Please sit, my dears.
-Thank you.
Go ahead and sit. Look at this.
You see this?
Our Indian gooseberry chili paste.
-You see that?
-It looks delicious.
Eat as much as you can, my dears.
When you finish eating this,
could you please tell me
if you like this recipe?
If you think it's good,
I'll add it to the recipe book.
Here, ma'am.
What is that?
Well, it's my recipe book.
My family's recipes are in this section.
May I see that, Auntie?
Yes, of course, my dear.
There you go, dear.
Take a look at my recipes.
GREEN CURRY PASTE, 100 GRAMS
If you want to publish a recipe book,
I can help you, Auntie.
-Really, dear?
-We'll type the recipes one by one.
Then we'll proofread them
to make sure nothing's missing.
My goodness! Thank you so much, dear.
But would you boys really have time
to do all that for me?
If I get to enjoy all this delicious food,
I'm perfectly happy to help.
Okay, let's do that. Now eat.
-You need your strength to help me write.
-That's a deal?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Great.
You watch your boyfriend at all hours.
Are you scared he'll get away?
No, I'm scared he'll want something
more casual like you do.
I guess your whole family knows now.
Clean eating can't save you
if you still behave like this.
People with clean records don't burgle
other people's homes.
You have double standards.
You're sacrificing yourself
for industrial espionage.
What a good person.
If you're coming and going so freely,
what if you enter the wrong apartment?
When I spit something out,
I don't try to eat it again.
Gla!
Who are you talking to?
Who do you think?
My name is Carl.
What does he want now?
What…
what is it, sir?
I called to thank you.
I need another favor, miss.
I'll be working in Shanghai all week.
Do you usually cook for yourself?
What do you need, sir?
I left lots of organic vegetables
in the fridge and some boxes.
If you'd like to use them,
please go ahead.
They're from my dad's plantation.
I don't want to let them go to waste.
I'm offering them to you,
and in exchange, while I'm away,
you can look after my mushrooms.
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
Since you started helping me out,
I've felt so much better.
Let's see how much better you'll feel.
ALREADY CHARGED
If only I could bring you
as a spare battery.
When I'm tired,
I think of you, and I feel stronger.
I don't know where that energy comes from.
I want you near me so you can recharge me.
In that case,
I'll fully recharge you right now.
What?
I just got home.
I need more time to recharge.
I'm still tired. What should we do?
Can I charge my spare battery?
#DOMEAFAVOR
#BONAPPÉTIT
I don't think Mr. Carl is alone.
He's with a woman.
But that's Saikhim!
What's she doing there?
Go and watch them.
I must know what they are to each other.
Yes, ma'am.
Today, we're talking about adopting
Carl's room booking system.
So our clients can go there
to view the product details,
the room prices, and the available dates.
APPLICATION ARSA: NO NOTIFICATIONS
I'm voting for you early and often.
This year, you're going to win for sure.
The Woman of the Year prize.
If you don't win, I don't know who will.
Whatever. Let's see who I'm up against.
Look.
See? We're competing against each other.
I can't compete with Khim.
Gosh! Well, forget it, then.
Okay, we don't need the prize.
When it comes to boyfriends, at least,
you'll outdo Miss Khim for sure
because her dad is so overprotective
that it'll be hard for her to get married.
Listen, Mom.
Khim is about to get married.
What? She's getting married?
Yeah.
To her second husband?
And yet you still haven't had
a serious boyfriend?
Well, don't give up yet.
Destiny is a great leveler.
Your soul mate
is right outside the door now!
-Hey!
-Turn and look.
Don't tell me
you set me up with someone again.
I keep telling you not to do that!
I didn't ask this one to come.
A client heard you qualified
for Woman of the Year
and thinks this guy's your perfect match,
so I offered him my services.
What on earth, Mom?
Deal with him yourself.
I'm sick and tired of your taste. Bye!
-You…
-Bye!
Good grief!
Well, what a sight for sore eyes!
Is this Lita's place?
I'm sick of this! Why must she meddle?
If he's basic,
I'm better off alone!
Gosh!
Whatever, Mom.
Lita!
You have a visitor!
Come down here right now!
I should leave.
I was stupid to come.
TANTHAI, 12 CALLS
Why so many calls?
Gosh!
I'm sorry I didn't call you in advance.
Am I interrupting anything, Auntie?
Gosh, it's no problem.
Listen, you can call me Mama.
You don't have to be so polite.
And you are…?
I'm Tanthai.
Well, goodness me!
Even your name is gorgeous too.
What do you do?
I work in a bank.
By the way,
here you go.
Well, goodness me!
No wonder you look so distinguished.
This way, please.
-Since you're here, let's not waste time.
-Sure.
Come here. This way, please.
-Lie down, please.
-Hey.
Just lie down.
We're going to make you
even more handsome.
When Lita comes down here,
you're going to make her squeal!
Glasses off.
If you work at a bank,
your transfers must be so fast.
Pardon?
You must be a sugar daddy.
Hey, would you lend me 1,000 baht?
What?
Look, I've been meaning to ask
if you'd help me vote for Lita
in the Woman of the Year contest.
Lita is afraid she'll lose
to her best friend who also qualified,
so I'm encouraging everyone
in the province to vote for her.
-Excuse me, Mama.
-Sure.
Where are you?
Hello?
-Hello?
Where are you going? Where?
-Mom!
-What?
Bro!
Jeez, you should've told me
you were coming.
If Mom had wheedled you any longer,
you would've got yourself a mother-in-law.
You didn't answer my calls.
So what's so urgent?
Dad and Khim.
What did you say?
It's about Dad and Khim.
I can't hear you. Say it again.
It's about Dad and Khim!
You mean your dad wants
a richer daughter-in-law than Saikhim?
How dare he?
Don't tell Khim, okay?
If he doesn't ask for permission
for you to marry her,
Khim will figure it out anyway.
Dad doesn't mind. He just isn't sure.
If Khim thinks negatively about my family,
she may not want to marry me.
Will you buy my silence?
I'll vote for you.
I'll spend 10,000.
Don't you want it?
Woman of the Year?
Can you be my bodyguard?
Make my mom stop setting me up with men.
If you can get rid of the guy
who's coming today,
I promise you
that I'll take this thing with your dad
with me to the grave!
Hello!
I have an appointment.
-My goodness!
-Hello, ma'am.
You can't see.
Can you see now?
That's the guy.
Ma'am.
-That guy?
-That's right.
I heard that you just moved here.
Yes, I'm the new principal
at one of the schools.
Gosh! Really?
Then you must love kids!
Honey, let's take pictures together.
-Look straight ahead.
-One, two, three.
-Smile a little. One. Two.
-Oh dear.
-Three.
-Gosh! Please turn this way.
Get closer. Put your face closer.
Goodness! Please look straight ahead.
Is this short enough?
That's enough!
Tell me, Mr. Principal,
have you been to the farmers' market?
-Do you live alone? Who cooks for you?
-Well, I…--
Gosh, now you mention it, I'm so hungry!
-What should we order for dinner tonight?
-My goodness.
If you get hungry,
you can eat here with us anytime.
I have such a headache!
It's so hot today.
Honey, can you give me a massage?
-Hey.
-Massage me.
Massage me really hard.
That's so good! Keep doing that!
We're finished, Mr. Principal.
All done.
I should go now.
Well… thank you, sir.
Damn it! Just go upstairs to her room!
Hey, mister.
Your bank transfers are fast,
and you move fast when it comes to women!
Move fast in what way, Mom?
Wait, Mr. Principal!
You forgot your change!
You made a promise.
Keep it, okay?
Miss?
I wouldn't be surprised
if you fell for such a perfect guy.
Mom!
What do you mean?
The way you look at him like that.
Do you think I can't tell?
Rich guys like him
Well… it was just an act
to teach you a lesson.
Do you think
I'd actually get serious with him?
Whatever.
You keep wanting
something you've never had,
so you'll never be happy
with what you do have.
And if you still feel jealous,
that's a sign that, deep down,
you're still less than Saikhim.
Women who are smart and impressive
should be more confident!
And you, my baby,
are too good to steal from someone else.
If they don't love us,
we have to love ourselves.
Mom, I love Khim.
But sometimes, I can't help comparing us.
Everything comes to her so easily.
And it makes me so angry
that Khim keeps making me feel
like I'm a villain.
No one's life is so easy.
Even Khim has her own problems.
The universe sends good men to love her
to make up for her dad's wrongheaded love.
Saikhim had no one else to love her,
so she had to be a good girl all her life
to make her dad proud.
As for you,
no matter how chaotic you are,
I never criticize you.
When someone loves you freely,
and you don't have to ask them to,
you're very lucky.
This is why
Khim is less fortunate than you are.
Since you are more loved than your friend,
share some love with her.
And if you don't want to be
the Villainess of the Year,
stop being jealous of Saikhim.
Let your friend
have a good relationship for once.
Actually, you know what?
Soft-spoken men like him,
if you really spend time with them,
they turn out to be so boring.
He seems too serious.
You, my baby,
should have someone really exciting.
We are a family of fierce women, baby.
Mr. Seen?
-What?
-I've found a flaw in Gaogla's Arsa app.
People are using it
as a front for illegal activities.
-How?
-Tourists are seeking local guides.
It makes it hard for us to regulate them.
And people are using personal vehicles
to provide public services.
It's just like the other app
that got banned.
Ban this one too.
Put them out of business.
I've published exposés of these issues.
The backlash should follow soon.
Good. Hit them hard.
Make them move back home.
Gla! Look at this.
The media is boycotting our app.
They say it lets young people
do problematic jobs.
Find out who released these stories.
Check and see who's behind them.
I asked you to come back early
because of this backlash.
By the way,
a TV show wants to interview you by phone.
Do you have a statement?
I'll do the interview myself.
Things might calm down.
-Yeah, okay.
-Hey, bro, wait.
You have to go and see Madame first.
She says it's urgent.
I told you, didn't I?
There's a flaw in your app,
so they're attacking you now.
No, they don't dare to fight face to face,
so they ambush us instead.
Would you still say
the Kidakarns aren't our competitors?
You said you wouldn't let personal grudges
interfere with your work life,
but that's impossible now.
You were too careless.
I admit it.
I underestimated those people,
so they've ganged up on me.
Wait.
Someone else has tried to mess with us.
The other day,
I sent a messenger to your place
while you were away.
I found out that the housekeeper you hired
is quite something.
Deal with this father and daughter pair.
If you can't handle it,
I'll deal with them myself.
I'll do phone interviews
with anyone who asks today.
A hotel guest contacted
a massage therapist in the area.
Good.
Send her up.
-Ann.
-Yes, sir.
-I've hit the Accept button.
-Go on up.
Yes, sir.
Let's see if he can resist
this massage therapist.
If we can prove
the app is used for sex trafficking,
it will get shut down.
I can confirm
that our app verifies users' identities
via a registration process.
All of our users can be verified.
Our app is
built on helping others and being kind.
We don't allow
illegal hiring practices or child labor.
She's still in there, Uncle.
I guess it's not just a massage.
We can use this video to expose them
for using the app
as a front for sex workers.
That volunteerism stuff
is just advertising.
Uncle, go on that news show tomorrow,
and we'll use this video to expose them.
But in the end,
this woman is just someone we planted.
Plant or not,
we get to play with our prey.
We have shown
that the app has a security flaw.
That Gaogla
acting all holy
when he's actually a phony pimp.
Who's fooling whom?
If the truth comes out,
Uncle Seen will have to clean up the mess.
Damn! Whose side are you on?
I can confirm
that our app verifies users' identities
via a registration process.
He has leveled up.
He's not as basic as when he tricked Khim.
Prom, your stupid plan can't hurt
a crafty guy like him.
Even you can trick him into bed,
so he can't be that smart!
Keep this evidence secure.
I'll humiliate him in front of the media
so he won't be able to work in Thailand.
Coming to see Tan?
What about you?
Don't tell me you came to see Gaogla.
What if I did? Are you jealous?
Be careful. Don't let him brainwash you.
Why are you here?
Don't even bother
if you've come to make it up to me.
Hey, Khim.
What are you doing here?
Wanna come in?
Yes.
I came to warn you.
Tomorrow, Prom will leak news
to damage your company again.
-Why are you telling me?
-To show that I'm on your side.
You can betray even your own family,
and you think I'd trust you?
Let the scandal happen
and trust me later if you want.
But believe me, this time, the evidence
will leave you powerless.
If you're worried,
you could talk to Prom about hush money,
or if you agree to let go of
the property opposite our hotel,
maybe Uncle Seen will decide
not to expose you after all.
-Yeah, Khem?
-Bro, I've checked.
Today, a tourist used our app
at the Elite Hotel.
I tried to verify
the user's volunteerism history.
It's like a brand-new user.
Maybe it's a fake account
made to accept jobs fraudulently.
I have a bad feeling about this, bro.
A fake job hunter? So we've been deceived.
I told you so.
I have to take care of this.
Tell your family that this time,
I'm fighting them kamikaze style.
Khim.
I researched wedding dates.
A monk found us auspicious dates
in six months and at the end of the year.
I left something in my car.
I'll just go grab it.
Sure, honey.
Where are those CCTV images?
Here they are, sir.
I WATERED THESE
Nice weather, right?
Yes.
Have you picked the wedding date?
If you haven't picked one yet,
why don't we order some dinner first?
All right.
I'll be right back.
Are you having a great time?
-What's wrong?
-Nice poker face.
What the hell is up with you?
You must be angry
your true colors have been exposed.
I don't care about that
because I realize that I'm basic.
I'm not good at faking.
I can't deceive like you do.
I'll never sink as low as you.
You're the one who messed up.
Why are you taking it out on me?
Yeah, I messed up
because I underestimated you.
You're so awful.
You have so many tricks up your sleeve.
If I'm awful,
then you must be evil!
Khim! What's wrong?
Show your true colors.
Stop faking and playing dumb.
What do you mean?
Have you seen her true self?
She's actually a real piece of work.
She says awful things
and thinks awful things.
You're such a good person.
So there it is.
Eventually, the dark side had to come out.
You're a coward face to face.
Behind my back, you're so brave.
Mr. Carl!
You know what?
She's good at killing people
who feel sorry for her.
What do you mean?
Wait and see.
I'll drag your lies and deceit
out into the light.
And you'll see that this woman
is so evil on the inside.
Why are you so quiet? Why don't you speak?
If you're silently cursing me,
I feel nothing.
One day,
you'll know the taste
of a lover's betrayal.
What happened, Khim?
Why are you two fighting all of a sudden?
He started it.
And why were you two so rude?
What happened between you?
It's just business.
My dad exposed his business.
No wonder he's so angry.
Today, a tourist used our app
at the Elite Hotel.
I tried to verify
the user's volunteerism history.
It's like a brand-new user.
Maybe it's a fake account
made to accept jobs fraudulently.
KASALONG SANGCHAI
She's good at killing people
who feel sorry for her.
What do you mean?
Wait and see.
I'll drag your lies and deceit
out into the light.
And you'll see that this woman
is so evil on the inside.
Why are you so quiet?
Why don't you speak?
If you're silently cursing me,
I feel nothing.
One day,
you'll know the taste
of a lover's betrayal.
Are you still awake? I need a favor, miss.
I'm moving out of this condo,
but I don't have enough time,
so I want to ask one last favor of you.
I'd like you to supervise the movers.
If it's not too much trouble,
please do this one last favor.
No problem. I'll help you out, sir.
Thank you.
Today, Songseen is doing a TV interview
about our app's illegal activities.
Find out which channel and which show,
and tell them I'm coming too.
Now we'll have some fun.
Miss Khim, Gaogla has offered to appear
on TV with Mr. Seen tonight.
APP CREATOR CARL RAMAN
TO FACE TOURISM MINISTER
I think this dispute is going to be
more complicated than we thought.
Dad isn't wise to his tricks.
APP CREATOR CARL RAMAN
TO FACE TOURISM MINISTER
I'm lucky you let me
appear on the same show.
This is good.
I think this will benefit the public.
I look forward to hearing
what you say in response
and how you'll fix this issue.
If my system is the problem, I can fix it.
But if the problem is people's attitudes,
we all need to work on that.
Today, I hope
that we can win some people's hearts
and help broaden their minds.
Smug, aren't you?
Don't embarrass yourself live on air.
We'll see who loses face
and goes home empty-handed.
Ready? Five.
Four. Three. Two.
Hello and welcome to today's episode
of Untangling the News.
We'll be talking about a very hot topic
that's trending at the moment.
It's a famous application
that has raised the question,
"Should this app be used in Thailand?"
Let's talk about ethics.
This way, please.
Today, we welcome to our show
Mr. Songseen Kidakarn,
the Minister of Tourism and Sports.
He's very concerned about the ethics
of this application.
Also joining us today is
the creator of the Arsa app,
Mr. Carl Raman. Hello to you both.
-Hello.
-I'll jump straight into it.
Recently, certain images were published
by a user of this app
who asked a masseuse to come to a hotel.
But the images don't seem to depict
an ordinary massage therapist.
You can see for yourself.
Let's take a look.
There. Those are the images in question.
Many people who see them may think
that perhaps this is
not massage therapy.
If that's true, this is an illegal way
to use the app, isn't it, Minister?
Well, we've all seen the images.
Frankly, I'm concerned
that this app is being used
as a front for finding illegal work,
and the app doesn't appear to implement
any preventative measures against this.
Superficially, the app seems
to let people help each other.
But since it's not regulated,
there's no way to know
if the jobs are inappropriate in any way.
The app is also used
for swapping lodgings.
We can't investigate or control
the quality and standard of the hotels
to make sure they meet tourists' needs.
-It can cause some damage.
-Do you say this as a hotelier?
Well, business aside,
I'm focusing on the country overall
because we had to win back
the trust of tourists
so that they'd visit us again after COVID,
and that wasn't easy at all.
Now we have to face this issue too.
I think it's like salt in the wound.
The minister has had his say.
And you, Mr. Carl?
What do you say to the minister,
to the public, and to the viewers?
I admit that we're now seeing
fake accounts using certain services,
but they're the minority of accounts.
Our main goal is to have
volunteers spreading kindness
and taking the time to make extra income.
But if someone abuses the system,
we can cancel that volunteer's membership.
I want everyone to see the app's benefits
which meet the needs of city people.
In what ways?
Let me ask you on behalf of the viewers.
Could you give us examples
or show us how it works?
Yes, I can.
Today, I wanted to move to a new place.
But I had to appear on this show.
I just needed someone
to help me move my stuff.
-You see?
-I see.
This is the volunteer
who's helping me move my stuff.
We'll see
You know, the details here are very clear.
You can see the user's photo,
first and last name, and phone number.
Let's show the viewers what it looks like
inside the Arsa app
that we're talking about.
MRS. KASALONG SANGCHAI
I want everyone to see
that honest, helpful people still exist.
Now let's check and see
if this user is who they say they are.
If this volunteer is not
Mrs. Kasalong Sangchai as they said,
my company is happy
to change for the better.
So, Mr. Carl, are you saying
that you have
a verification system that ensures
that no one can covertly
engage in illegal activities on this app?
That depends on the intentions
and the judgment of the users.
It's like any ordinary dating app.
If both parties are willing
and give consent,
we can't tar them with the same brush
as the con artists.
So you still insist
that you created this app
to help other people.
Yes, and I think
a lot more people can benefit from it.
Older people with no kids or grandkids
can get someone to help them
with tasks they can't do themselves.
Kids can find someone
to help them with their homework.
Also, older people and disabled people--
Sorry, may I interrupt? We're digressing.
Of course there are advantages
and some good ideas,
but we're concerned
about how it affects our nation.
If the app has no oversight,
criminals could infiltrate it.
That's my concern.
The minister has a point, Mr. Carl.
I think if people dedicated
a bit of their time to others,
this app could make this city better
because no one would be left behind.
That's the app's view.
I'm speaking as
the Tourism and Sports Minister.
I'm talking about the intention
behind creating my app.
All right, everyone.
Let's calm down. It's getting intense.
Let's take a short break.
Please don't miss the next segment
because the volunteer we mentioned
will visit Mr. Carl here in our studio.
But for now, let's take a breather.
Excuse me. The moving truck's nearly here.
Right. Okay.
Remember, when the moving truck arrives,
cut to the live show again.
I'll take a camera downstairs
to wait for them.
You kept digressing from the issue.
I couldn't just let you accuse me.
Mind what you say.
Remember, he's a minister.
Welcome back.
And now,
our volunteer is ready, and we'll see
who registered as a user of this app.
-May I?
-Please go ahead.
Of course it'll be the same person.
If he's so confident,
he must have planned it all, right?
We'll see if that's true.
Please calm down.
We're about to find out the truth.
Let's show the viewers the screen.
I repeat,
if she's the same person,
she must be a housekeeper named
Mrs. Kasalong Sangchai, aged 45.
It says here
that she's from Chiang Rai Province.
Let's find out
if she's the same person.
Let's meet her in real life.
Let's watch the live footage right now.
Here she is.
Why are we here?
To see my boss, of course.
You betrayed me?
You impersonated someone to trick us.
Come on.
Thailand's waiting.
But why would she hide her face
behind her purse like that?
From what I can see, it's not her.
You know, our app can use phone numbers
to verify our users' identities.
You could try calling her.
All right, let me call this number now.
Let's see if she picks up.
Her phone should be ringing.
-Khim.
-We can see her face.
So did this person create a fake account
to impersonate someone
for fraudulent purposes?
We'll have to ask her who she is
and why she's job hunting fraudulently.
If she has bad intentions,
I'm ready to press charges.
This is incredible.
We've really hit the jackpot.
But Minister, don't you think
she looks like a certain someone?
She looks familiar.
Isn't that your daughter, Minister?
Maybe she wanted to have fun with our app,
so she used someone else's account.
She's got a good background.
I guess we can't call her a criminal.
What do you think, Minister?
Stop filming.
Stop filming!
Everyone, stop filming!
Whoa, he's good.
Don't be shy. Come out.
Be polite to the reporters.
Don't you have manners?
Come on!
Stop filming!
Stop filming now!
Why are you filming?
You wanted an exposé.
Here it is. What are you afraid of?
They're playing dirty.
They're scapegoating us!
No filming! Do you hear me?
-Please film it!
-No filming!
I said, no filming!
Let's watch these developments.
This is live from outside our studio.
Her face… there she is.
-I said, no filming!
-Film it!
You tricked people. Now pay the price!
-Stop. Get away!
-Go in there!
-Hey! I said, no filming!
-Please stop.
-Film it!
-I'm sorry.
A lot is going on out there.
Let's come back to the studio.
This incident has left me
almost speechless.
But we've almost
run out of time for today.
So let's shift the focus over here.
Before we go,
do you have anything to add, Minister?
The app developers
why they caused a scene today
and who they intend to hurt.
I've told you the intention
behind the app.
It's the impostor's intentions
that caused this incident today.
I think we know now
whether the problem lies with the app
or with the impostors who use it.
Well, dear viewers,
our topic today is super intense.
Do stay tuned.
I'm sure there will be a sequel,
but for now, sadly,
we're out of time.
Thanks to both our guests. Thank you.
Thank you.
And we…
we'll say goodbye for today.
See you next time. Goodbye for now.
Well? Are you proud of yourself?
She came to my place in disguise.
She came onto me first. You didn't know?
I guess she's still not over me
so she keeps trying to rehash our past.
Get a hold of yourself.
My poor father-in-law.
He must be so ashamed.
Dad, don't listen to him.
You've gone too far.
You entrapped me.
I've been tricked, Dad.
You've had a quiet life.
Why did you look for trouble?
Your people played dirty with me first.
You used that masseuse against me.
You're lucky I didn't expose you too.
That's enough!
You think this is enough to defeat me?
I'm just happy to humiliate you
in front of the media.
I'll destroy your facade.
I'll show everyone
that you're nothing special.
Do it.
Then I can be your former son-in-law.
You treated me like mangy dog.
Maybe you're just a tick on that dog now.
Well, my little girl?
Happy now?
Let's talk properly.
You've gone way too far.
Why didn't you tell the whole truth?
You lured me towards you.
You've used me all this time.
In the end,
do you just want to humiliate me?
Are you happy now,
or do you want to ruin me more?
I'm not easily satisfied.
Let me tell you something.
Getting revenge on you alone isn't enough.
What did I do to you?
What made you want revenge on me?
I've also asked myself
what I ever did to your family.
I've asked myself that for years.
If you just started asking that,
you're not doing enough.
If I'm the problem,
hurt me, but why would you hurt Dad?
Your dad is the one who put me in prison!
How does it feel to be accused too?
What your family did to me,
I'll do it back to you all.
But it might hurt you worse
if you never learn.
If you want to get revenge on me,
leave other people out of it.
What did I do to you?
What made you want revenge on me?
If you don't seize this chance,
your life will never get better again.
Tell him to go to hell!
If you feel uncomfortable staying here,
you can come and work with me.
Mom, this is Miss Khim, my idol.
But everyone said that Mom died.
What did you make all these plans for?
If you want to be cruel, do it properly.
Go in for the kill.
All these ghosts are coming back to life.
You want to make me hurt?
If you do,
you've succeeded.
I'm in pain.
Are you happy now?
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit