THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
I'll have my baby.
After the birth,
I'll give him sole custody.
With a daughter this stupid,
I wouldn't mind being childless.
You see what happens
when you let emotions run your life?
You wanted to care for the baby,
but you didn't help her,
and now she's alone.
My son wants to marry Saikhim.
You think your son is a match
for my daughter?
From now on,
no matter what happens in her life,
I will make her proud of herself again.
Then, at least,
they'll be better parents than you.
I can't imagine waking up
without her there with me.
We've made happy memories so easily.
They'd be hard to come by
if she ever left.
I've held his hand
and sat in his lap.
How will I ever hold anyone else
without thinking of him?
The sunset view
from this house will be so pretty.
All right, let's put a big window here
so we can enjoy the view every day.
What's this house being built for?
It'll be our marital home.
Since we'll be living together,
I want to finish building it very soon.
I can't wait.
Wait a second.
I never said I'd marry you.
What? Then how would we live together?
Just like we do now, of course.
No, we have to move in together
as soon as the house is ready.
I'm not ready yet.
Can't we wait?
Are you backing out?
We're a family. We should live together.
We'll be the parents of our child,
but we don't have to be married.
No way. Who does that?
You don't want to marry me?
Don't people who get married
love each other?
But… we…
It's too soon to get married.
No, it's not. We're pregnant!
It's actually too late!
Don't you like the food?
I do like it.
Gloy!
Make something different tomorrow.
-All right.
-Good.
Don't worry about it.
Don't people who get married
love each other?
But… we…
we…
It's too soon to just move in together.
What's wrong with them?
They seem so agitated.
It's your fault.
You keep getting in the way.
They're trying to be intimate,
but they can't.
We're the third wheel.
Yeah.
Dad?
What's this?
It's mosquito repellent.
Take it to your girlfriend.
Stay with her all night.
No one will interrupt.
All right, Dad.
Wait, Gla.
Put this top on.
It's cold tonight.
There. Go on.
Good night, Dad.
Stay all night, okay?
LOVE
Gloyjai bought this at the market.
I didn't know you had one.
Dad gave us orange peels
to keep mosquitoes out.
-Are you okay?
-Just stop.
Light it yourself.
Hey, what are you doing?
You finish it yourself.
INTERVIEW WITH AN EXECUTIVE
Now I see why you hesitated.
If you don't want to do it,
no one will make you.
INTERVIEW WITH AN EXECUTIVE
What? Why are you back already?
Khim, take a look at this.
More guests are coming Friday,
but we have no rooms left.
Look at this.
Dad asked me to ask you
when you'll move into the new house
so that guests can stay here.
I'll start moving my stuff.
I'll try and get it done by Friday.
Okay then.
The house is so pretty.
Pretty enough to live in?
I'm about to move my stuff here.
You said you didn't want to.
Well, the guesthouses are full,
so I had to move out of mine.
Do what you like.
I don't care if you move in.
You might feel weird sleeping alone.
You said this would be our marital home.
When I go somewhere I like,
I try to capture the atmosphere
in a sketch in this book.
This book is like a book
of all my happy thoughts.
All the things I love
are in here.
Don't people who get married
love each other?
But… we…
It's too soon to just move in together.
So this is the real reason.
Auntie Oon.
Auntie Oon!
-Hello.
-My goodness! Hello, my dear.
I've missed you so much.
Auntie Oon, did Dad really fire you?
Yes, of course.
It's my fault.
I didn't take good care of you.
That's not true.
I'm sorry, Auntie Oon.
You've worked for our family for decades.
Now you're struggling because of me.
It's all right.
Anyway, how have you been?
Have you been doing well?
At first, I needed time to adjust.
But now,
I like it here.
All right, anyway,
I'll take you to our plantation.
Then you'll see what my life is like.
-Okay.
-All right?
Shall we go now?
My car is over there.
Auntie Oon, you remember Gla, right?
Right.
Hello.
I've prepared your accommodation.
Please make yourself at home.
-All right.
-Let's go.
Don't worry. I'll take that for you.
You must be so tired.
Come on. Let's go home.
Can we run an errand here?
What errand?
Now that Auntie Oon is here,
I'd like to take the opportunity
to do the right thing properly.
I wanna get a marriage certificate.
Auntie Oon, you're like Khim's other mom,
so I would like you
to witness our happy occasion.
I was wrong to have been so careless
that I made you feel taken for granted.
I understand why you've been
reluctant to marry me.
We've made lots of mistakes.
This is the first time
we'll do everything right,
like other couples do.
Let's not say, "love,"
because all this time,
I've been ruled by emotions, not reason.
But now,
I'll try living mindfully.
Marry me, Khim.
I won't make you regret
giving up your future
to be with someone like me.
Today is the first day
of the rest of your lives
as lawfully wedded husband and wife.
I wish everlasting happiness for you both.
From now on,
there'll be no Saikhim Kidakarn.
There'll be only Saikhim Chayodom.
And she's mine alone.
May you be connected
like a column and a beam
that bear the weight of a whole house.
Life can be tough sometimes.
If you forgive each other,
you'll be stronger together.
Here you go.
Please love and take very good care
of Miss Khim for me.
May you love and stay loyal
to each other for a long time.
Make your house a home,
and everything will be all right.
Here you go, Gla.
I'm giving it back.
It's the money you've sent home to me
since you started working.
Keep it.
It's for your family.
No, Dad.
Just take it.
I won't, Dad.
If you don't want it,
keep it for my grandchild.
I want you to.
Thank you.
Everyone, shall we take photos?
Yeah. Come on.
Let's do this.
How shall we do this?
-Dad, go there.
-Where do I go?
-All right.
-Auntie, go there too.
All right.
Let's go.
Is everyone ready?
Uncle Seen doesn't seem bothered
that his daughter ran away.
I think he's trying to get over it.
He's lost face,
but he can't let anyone see that.
That's why he has to keep busy with work.
He's avoiding thinking about his problems.
Do you like it here?
It's much nicer than I imagined.
Really?
In that case,
come and live with me.
You could raise my baby
like you raised me.
Isn't it too soon?
You've known him a couple of months
and now you're married.
Do you know him well enough?
I haven't known him for long,
but he knows me even better
than people I've known all my life.
He might seem a bit too direct,
but he never leaves my side
when I'm in trouble.
He takes care of me like I'm a princess.
But I won't tell him that,
or he'll be so smug.
Auntie and Khim,
you can stay at our house.
Oh dear. Am I inconveniencing you?
Not at all, Auntie Oon.
Tonight, you can stay with me.
Please go ahead. You can have our room.
Oh dear. What about the bedding ceremony?
We're not standing on ceremony.
We're not superstitious.
It doesn't matter where we sleep.
Then I'll put your bag
in our room, Auntie Oon?
That won't be necessary.
I'll do it myself.
No, don't, Auntie Oon.
Stay with me tonight
so that we can stay up and chat.
All right. I'll take your stuff there.
You don't have to.
I'll leave you to it.
Auntie Oon…
Hey, should we offer a course
on how to spin cotton thread for weaving?
It might draw more female guests.
Gloyjai could teach them.
Should we try offering this course?
Look.
We have to follow the Middle Way
and not do too much or too little.
Stop talking about work.
Come and take a rest.
Can you stop acting weird?
I'm not.
This is what I'm like.
Sure, this is natural.
You're as stiff as a mummy.
If you're not already dead,
I guess you're not interested.
Good night. I'm sleepy now.
See if you can fall asleep.
What's wrong?
-Nothing.
-Nothing?
Nothing.
What's wrong?
I had sleep paralysis all night. It hurts.
Last night, I went to sleep
on top of your arm.
Are you okay?
I'll massage you.
Feel better?
What are you doing?
Kissing practice.
You'll feel less awkward,
or you'll get punished.
Stop it.
Stop it. I haven't brushed my teeth.
Really? Now we're under the covers too?
I haven't brushed mine either. Come on.
Look. It's the Way of the White Elephants.
It's only visible a few months a year.
It also depends on the lunar cycle.
In English, it's called
the "Mill Key Way" or something.
Pretty, isn't it?
Around here, this is the nightlife.
Do you have to leave so soon?
I wish you'd stay longer.
I have to visit my family.
In that case,
I'll come and visit you there.
Please look after yourself, Miss Khim.
That will be my job.
I'll look after her.
Stay in touch with me.
Don't just disappear.
I'll call you every day, Auntie Oon.
Have a safe journey.
I will.
I'll take my bag.
Allow me.
All right.
I can take it from here.
-It's all right.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Ma'am.
-Goodbye.
Don't wait for me. I'll be all right.
Let's go.
Hello, dear. Take this.
Come on, ma'am.
THE WELL-BEING SCHOOL
Gla.
You have a visitor.
Khem! What are you doing here?
Gla! Bro, I've missed you so damn much.
I came to congratulate you.
You eloped and disappeared on me.
This is Khem.
He works at my garage.
He catfished you with my photo.
Hold on.
Without me, you two would not be together.
You came here just to be snarky?
Actually, there's more to it.
I'm thirsty.
Can I have some water?
What's wrong?
The cops froze the garage's account.
We might not make it out of this mess.
So I brought this.
VEHICLE REGISTRATION
What now, bro?
It's too late to get the money out.
Leave the stuff here. I'll deal with it.
Go and lie low a while.
Don't let the cops find you.
The garage is closed, and I have no money.
Where can I go?
What's wrong?
He's just visiting us.
Are you sure?
What else don't I know about you?
What exactly do you guys do at work?
VEHICLE REGISTRATION
We put license plates on tax-dodging cars.
We've been hiding this evidence.
I have no degree and no expertise.
I can't make a good living
with a legit business,
so I prey on rich kids
who import cars illegally.
When your cousin got into trouble,
that was because of me.
So that's how you earn
the money that you send home each month?
The garage has been shut down,
and the cops are searching it.
Khem and I can't go back.
You did it because you had no choice.
We don't have the same opportunities,
nor do we have the same needs.
Now that I know this, what should I do?
Do I have to be able to accept this too?
I know I did bad things.
But we can't change our past.
I wish I was born worthy of you,
but I can't change that.
I promise to change my ways.
You don't have to forgive me.
But can you give me
a chance to prove myself?
I promise I won't make you regret
choosing to be with me.
Then just try harder
to think of the baby from now on.
I promise.
I won't do business illegally again.
Take my car.
You can keep it or sell it if you want.
Think of it as your share of our garage.
As for the money that was seized,
we traded it for our future.
What about you?
I guess I'll start over.
I can't take risks like I used to.
I understand.
We've been through a lot.
I know you're happy,
and it makes me happy too.
Look after my bro.
Where's Gla, honey?
He didn't milk the cows.
Right. He went to see off his friend.
Where the hell to?
By the way,
Gla said he'd visit the bank first.
Honey, go and check something.
Is his passbook missing?
All right.
Well, honey?
The passbook's missing.
Gla must have taken it.
Did he take it, or was it his friend?
I knew it.
This colleague of Gla's seems suspicious.
Wait. Dad!
What?
Hey, Gla!
What are you doing here?
You closed it?
Where's the money?
I gave it to Khem for his own garage--
And how will your family survive?
How?
Do you plan
to leech off your wife forever?
I never thought you'd prioritize
someone else over your family!
Are you angry?
Well, shouldn't I be?
I didn't give all the money to Khem
for no good reason.
Khem has to look after his mom.
Giving him the money
when he has to hide from the cops
is the least I can do.
And what about us?
We still have our house and our work.
I gave him all the money
'cause I got a power plant surveying gig.
I'll cross the border with the engineers
to the forests of Laos.
I want to make all that money back
before our baby is born.
To make all that money,
how many trips would you need to take?
How long would it take?
I'll be right back.
Then I'll go again.
By the time the baby's due,
I'll have done three or four trips.
So that means…
we'll be apart from now on, right?
I wanna lead our family.
I want our child to be proud of me.
So when are you leaving?
Next week.
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
I'm a new man now.
You should be happy.
That bastard I used to be
never even gave you a ring.
Don't mourn him.
Good men
are harder to find than rings.
If I can have a good husband,
I don't want a ring.
He fooled her
into signing a marriage certificate.
He wants to hit the jackpot.
Miss Khim seems to be infatuated with him.
I don't think she realizes
how he's manipulating her.
He's using the law as a tool.
He's so devious.
Miss Khim probably just wants to be loved.
When someone treats her very nicely,
they take advantage of her easily.
Goodness only knows
when Miss Khim will come to her senses.
Maybe when I'm dead.
She can forget it.
She won't inherit a single baht.
Mom, why is Auntie Oon back?
I heard that Seen had her brought back.
But Khim isn't here.
Why bring Auntie Oon back?
Maybe Saikhim will be back soon.
I heard that her partner
is wanted by the police.
If she's desperate,
she'll come home with her baby.
Come on.
She's caused such a scandal.
Uncle Seen wouldn't welcome that baby.
Even without Saikhim here,
Seen would never care about us anyway.
But what if we changed our strategy
and brought Khim back for him?
Then would Seen appreciate us?
Mom!
I'm sick and tired
of being compared to her all my life.
Why would you bring her back?
So that you can take your revenge.
That delinquent's time has come.
She deserves to be mocked
and shamed by you.
I think Seen
loves to win.
If we can put Khim back in her cage,
we might be able to win back his favor.
That should be easy.
Let's put her husband in jail.
She won't stand a chance.
Should we try it?
Maybe your uncle will reward us
with something nice in return.
Khim?
Khim.
Are you okay?
Medicine must be taken
with caution during pregnancy.
Instead, try this
lemongrass and ginger tea.
Does it help treat the common cold?
See if it works.
If it does, I'll brew more.
I set up a Wi-Fi router
at Dad's house for you.
By the way,
I'll leave the flashlight
and batteries there…
so when it rains and the power goes out,
you can find your way to the bathroom.
I heard that pregnancy makes you
go to the bathroom often.
Now we're prepared.
And I almost forgot.
Morning sickness is worse
if you wake up hungry.
From now on, when you wake up,
eat some of these snacks right away.
Don't get up before that, okay?
I've stocked up for you.
They're in this bag too,
so you can take them anywhere.
Wait.
Hey, how many months will you be working?
You act like you'll be away for years.
You got sick
even when I'm here to take care of you.
What will happen while I'm away?
By the way…
I saved Dad's number
to your emergency speed dial.
If you need anything, call him.
Just press this.
I know you're worried about me.
But
you don't have to be.
Just focus on your work.
I'll be waiting for you.
All right.
MOTHERS AND CHILDREN
Sorry.
Lita.
We need to talk, okay?
The university has received a complaint.
It's about your scholarship approval.
Let's go to my office.
We don't have to buy that yet.
It's too soon for that.
Let's buy it in advance.
Who'll take you shopping while I'm away?
There's still so much time.
We can come again later.
Don't you like it?
It's just too soon for this.
You can just wear it to stop dirty old men
from trying to seduce you.
Whatever. If you like it so much,
you can wear it yourself.
Khim.
Don't you like shopping together?
Think of it as our honeymoon.
Let's go home.
Gla.
Stay calm.
This way, Khim.
Gla! Don't run away!
Come on.
Khim.
This way, Khim.
Hurry.
Don't be scared. I know my way
round here with my eyes closed.
I didn't bring you here out of fear.
I just don't want him to remember you.
I know what it's like to be hated
for something that's not our fault.
We've both been criticized
for things we can never change.
Who'd dare mess with rich people like you?
I've always been taught
not just to do well, but to do my best.
When I was the top student in the class,
Dad would ask me
who was the top student in my year.
The price of being Dad's beloved daughter
was being mocked by other kids.
I couldn't make friends with anyone.
I was a freak.
The more I tried, the worse it got.
Here comes the kid with connections.
If she weren't rich,
she couldn't have transferred this term.
I heard her dad's rich.
Hey, everyone.
-Donate some--
-Hey.
What's this box for?
Donations for orphans, huh?
Your wristwatch alone
could sponsor a kid easily.
-So why would you ask us for donations?
-Yeah.
Go ask your dad for donations.
-Go on.
-Go and ask him for money.
If you don't wanna donate, don't.
Can I sit with you?
You're Saikhim, right? I'm Lita.
You know my name?
Yeah.
Actually, I'm one of the recipients
of your dad's scholarship.
Why are you sitting with me?
Well, I'm like you.
No one likes me either.
One, two, one, two, three,
one, two, one two, one.
-Get ready for "Mock the Sky."
-Ready.
Three, four.
Look at the bear, such a cute bear
Look at the bear
It's such a big bear
Look at it waddling
Lala lalala
Talala
What the hell is this?
Well, you guys think of me as a clown.
Here I am, clowning for you.
Don't you like it?
You're so fake.
You've always been phony, Saikhim.
Hey, Miss Rich Girl.
-What are you doing?
-Show us your dance again.
You're not as pure
as you want other people to think.
Hey. Wait.
I think Miss Rich Girl
isn't dressed properly.
Sort it out.
Sure. It's my specialty.
-Come here.
-What are you doing?
-Stay still.
-Let go of me!
-Take it off.
-What are you guys doing?
Hey, that looks good.
Take lots of photos.
Stop it!
Let go!
-You're a bully!
-You're nuts!
You rabid dogs! Stop biting people!
What psychos.
Khim…
if they don't like you,
don't make them, but hold your head high.
I asked Dad for advice.
He only said
that I should live a life
that others would envy.
But in reality,
I don't think anyone envied me.
I think they pitied me.
At least, there was one person
who wanted to be my friend.
That was Lita.
But after everything that's happened,
Lita will probably be cut out of my life.
You see?
Being me is no better than being you.
You just didn't have friends.
Your life's still much better than mine.
I worked as an usher in this cinema
for years just to watch movies for free.
I'm used to the darkness here
because I worked here.
This is why I envy you.
You envy my shabby little life?
At least you got to live.
All I ever did was study.
My dad never understood me.
You've been much happier than I have.
And now you have to share
your family with me.
I really can't be as optimistic as you.
I wasn't trying to flatter you.
My life has been full of opportunities,
but I…
don't have inner strength.
You deal with life's ups and downs
better than I do.
I don't have that life skill.
That makes you
the gift that heaven sent me.
Am I a gift or a curse?
You're a reward.
It's because you say these things
that I fell for you ever since that night.
Well, it's true.
Deep down, you're a good person.
You just don't always show it.
The more you say,
the harder I fall for you.
While I'm away,
don't be so cute around anyone else.
If you do, everyone will fall for you too.
You're so romantic sometimes.
Here's the outfit I wore
at my first piano recital.
Look.
I got a haircut that day.
That's my usual barbershop.
They're my buddies.
That day, I went
to try on that piano recital outfit.
My word.
Very high fashion.
It's pretty.
Look.
That day, I got a haircut
to go to a party.
Check out the fashion.
That was the height of fashion.
I thought I deleted these.
You guys look quite in love.
Now I know I was wrong.
But you used to love her very much.
We all pay for our mistakes.
They say
that at first,
men love you 100% and count down,
but women start at zero and count up.
I guess it's true.
You used to love her completely.
But now you don't at all.
As for me, I didn't think I'd like you.
But the more we're together,
the more my feelings grow.
One day,
you might start loving me less
like you did with others, right?
Who said that?
I'll never love you less.
I'll only love you more every day.
What if you stopped loving me?
What would happen?
I won't stop loving you.
How can you be sure?
When I'm with you, my heart beats harder.
If I got tired of you,
it'd be when you stopped
making my heart beat.
If I stopped loving you,
it'd be because I'd died.
I'm not in a hurry to die.
I wanna love you forever.
Don't flatter me.
What?
Wait. Let's take some photos.
Let's not. Why should we?
Come on. I'll look at them while I'm away.
One. Two.
Three.
Use your phone too.
-No, one phone is enough.
-Give me that.
I'll count to three, then you kiss me.
One. Two.
Three.
I hacked Miss Khim's phone
and found this photo.
Take care of it.
Yes, sir.
Uncle.
Have you heard about your son-in-law?
What did you say?
I'm sorry.
I meant the man Saikhim is with.
His garage customizes tax-dodging cars,
so it's being raided.
If he's arrested,
Saikhim has nowhere to go.
Do you want me
to bring her back?
I worry that if he's arrested,
he'll involve us to save himself,
and he'll take us down with him.
Please let me handle it.
Maybe we'll finally get him
out of Saikhim's life.
-Khim?
-Yes?
Gla!
Take good care of yourself.
If you can't reach me, don't panic.
The phone signal might be bad
in the forests.
Dad, look after her and the kid.
Work hard.
Don't worry too much.
Gla! Get in the van.
We should go.
I'll be right back when work is finished.
Start the van.
What? You're not asleep yet?
We checked for signal already.
One. Two.
Three.
Hello, ma'am.
Hi.
Are you visiting our school?
I just came to check out some land.
I was passing through, so I stopped by.
Then please come in.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
Our school is a training center
that teaches self-reliance.
Please take a look.
I'll show you around.
This way.
THE WELL-BEING SCHOOL
We try to make everything ourselves here.
All the Four Requisites,
food, shelter, medicine, and clothing,
we make them all ourselves.
Just like all this cotton.
We're going to weave it
into clothes to wear.
Hello, ma'am.
That's my husband's family.
I moved here to join him and his family.
And how far along are you, sweetie?
Over three months.
You don't look Thai,
but you speak Thai very well.
My husband has a business here.
I often fly over here, so I'm used to it.
Right.
-Khim?
-Yeah?
Let's invite her to stay tonight.
You're welcome to stay, ma'am.
This is a community where people exchange
their thoughts on lifestyles.
If you like it here,
stay as long as you like.
Hey, where's your husband?
He crossed the border to work in Laos.
He hasn't come home yet.
Being alone doesn't scare you?
When you know how to live with nature,
you have nothing to be scared of.
And would you like to have
a son or a daughter?
I'd like to have a son
because I want him to be like his dad.
How about you? Do you have kids?
I have a son.
But he's nothing like me.
Ms. Asia has a son, but he lives abroad.
Really?
How old is your son?
I suppose he's younger than my son.
I'd say they're the same age.
My son is quite immature.
He's just started to grow up
now that he's about to become a dad.
Your mom is so beautiful.
Thank you.
She passed years ago.
She never saw her kids' success.
GAOGLA
Please excuse me.
Dad, that must be Gla.
Khim is smiling from ear to ear.
Good.
Khim, I walked all the way
to the source of the water today.
They mentioned building
a tunnel to divert the river.
It sounds like a difficult job.
This afternoon, the van broke down.
When they heard I can fix cars,
they were so impressed.
My boss wants me
to supervise the machinery next time.
My goodness. You're so clever.
And it's only your first trip.
Every time I turn on the lights,
I always think of you.
I think of you every day too.
And when I look at your drawing,
I really miss our home.
Be strong for the baby.
It's only your first trip.
Hey, Khim.
Can I talk to the baby?
Sure.
Okay, you can talk now.
Hey, kid. This is your dad.
I'm working in the forests.
It's pitch black,
but the sky is full of stars.
Khim?
Should we call our baby Temfah?
If it's a girl, we could call her Temfah.
But if it's a boy,
could we call him Nannam?
Do you think it would like that?
Khim, ask the baby.
Put the phone closer.
Hello? Baby?
Put your hand up if your name is Temfah.
No one replied.
What? Was there no kicking?
We should pick another name.
Then it must be Nannam.
Nannam, can you hear me, son?
Anyone there, Khim?
The baby doesn't like it.
I'll think of other names.
How about Tonkhao?
Isn't it cute, Khim?
Mommy says no.
You don't like it?
When I'm free, I'll think of more names.
When you get back, we can think together.
THE WELL-BEING SCHOOL
Uncle! Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
-Oh no. You have a burn blister.
Get the gotu kola leaves
that I crushed in the mortar.
-Hurry.
-All right.
Come on, honey.
Just put it right there.
-Does that help?
-That's better.
I think you should sit down.
I'll clean this up for you.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
I'll clean that up.
Gla asked me to look after you,
but in the end,
who's looking after whom?
You raised Gla, and now he's grown-up.
Now it's time for us
to repay your kindness.
You know, don't you, that Gla
isn't my own son?
Gla's real father is a Westerner.
But he doesn't know who it is.
After Gla was born,
Rakroy found out
her husband had another kid.
The worst part is
she later found out
he wanted to have a second kid
so he could give blood
to the first one, who was ill.
Is that really true?
He acted like Gla wasn't human.
He saw Gla as a spare part.
So Gla's mom
took him and ran away
to save him from those people.
Later, I married her
and adopted Gla
so they could change their names
and hide from them.
I don't want Gla to get rich or famous,
not because I don't want him to succeed,
but because I want to protect him
from those awful people.
Having a child
is easy to do.
But keeping a child alive
is very hard.
You have to take good care of
and support this child well.
Make its life in this world worth living.
Gla is so lucky
to have you as a father.
It's absolutely right
that Gla should love
and respect you more than he does anyone.
Gla's real father is a Westerner.
But he doesn't know who it is.
After Gla was born,
Rakroy found out
her husband had another kid.
The worst part is she later found out
he wanted to have a second kid
so that he could give blood
to the first one, who was ill.
Hey!
Congratulations.
You survived.
I just want to say
that you owe me your life.
If I hadn't saved you,
you might have died by now.
As for the rest of your life,
will you give it to me
or to them?
Having a child
is easy to do.
But keeping a child alive
is very hard.
You have to take good care of
and support this child well.
Make its life in this world worth living.
Are you leaving already?
I have urgent business.
I have to fly home.
Can I help you in any way?
No. But thanks.
Do visit us again.
By then, you will have had your baby.
Make sure you take good care of it.
We just drive across the border.
Once we've delivered the stuff,
we'll get all the money, bro.
Take a look.
He threatened
to make this public.
Your father had a fall.
Won't you go and visit him?
Stop! Freeze!
Put the weapon down!
Turn, bro!
Officers! My son is there!
We've surrounded the suspects.
They won't get away.
We're doomed!
Give yourselves up!
A suspect has been shot.
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit