THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
I know everything now!
I know why he accuses me of killing him.
I'll give you
one last chance to redeem yourself.
Ruin Saikhim's wedding.
I'm going to swindle Gaogla.
I'll have Saikhim
take marital property from him.
Are we still friends?
Why did you betray me like this?
I'm marrying Tan.
I won't let this
get in the way of our marriage.
I wanna settle the divorce.
You said you wanted nothing,
but now, you want hundreds of millions?
Just one night
in exchange for a lifetime with him.
Isn't it worth it?
He's married. He has a wife.
They were together last night.
Before becoming someone else's wife,
make it up to me.
How should I do that?
Just tell me.
Two kinds of people are
friends with their ex.
The first kind
never loved their ex in the first place.
The other kind
are still in love.
Does someone really live here?
Yeah, the owner wants to redecorate it.
I'd like you to clean it first.
All right.
I saw those images when I closed my eyes.
When I was awake, I couldn't tell
what was real and what was nightmares.
For years now,
I've been scared to fall asleep
and never wake up again.
Try living my life,
or go through half what I've been through!
MR. CARL, LORAZEPAM (25MG)
Please put these clothes
in the washing machine.
And then
please bring them back and iron them.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Back already?
Is anyone here?
Is someone here?
Who is here?
You don't like her,
but you let her come and go around here.
Quite a love-hate relationship.
She's not doing it for free.
She's doing it to redeem herself.
Right, so it's not for free.
Is this punishment for her infidelity?
Whoa, what is up with this couple?
You're talking crap.
Right, you must feel so good
about getting back at her.
Wow, look how you're trying to stop her
from getting remarried.
My darling Gla!
In what way do I look
like I'm still in love?
You're like
fans of chains, whips, and handcuffs.
One of you loves torture,
and the other loves pain or something,
letting the other punish them.
Stop talking nonsense. I'm not a psycho.
I'm kidding. Chill out.
-And what's that?
-This?
I don't know. I saw it sitting over there.
Did Khim buy you this?
That's cheating.
Who asked you to use these fragrances?
They smell nice.
Wash them again.
And don't use fabric softener.
Masculine people
don't like soft things, do they?
And throw out this machine.
What? Don't say you don't like technology.
You said you'd give up your time
to make it up to me.
But this machine saves time.
Throwing money at the problem is cheating.
Then who would clean--
I could discount the time
that it does your job for you.
When you're here, make an effort.
Don't just phone it in.
You have to live and breathe me.
Think of me when you wake up
and when you go to sleep.
That's what counts as compensation.
If you can't do that, don't bother coming.
Nothing you do can make it up to me!
You promised me
you'd divorce me if I could stand this.
Why are you wasting power
on this stupid fridge?
Do you let your hotel guests
starve to death like this?
Fill the fridge before I get home.
I'll reimburse you.
Wait.
Keep these keys.
Come and go without bothering me.
You'd better avoid me.
Khim! There you are.
Have you been waiting long?
Tan.
How come you got here so fast?
Whoa, look at all this.
Why are you buying so many things?
I thought you liked dark roast.
Well, I just wanted to try
a different flavor.
Okay, let's buy some things
and take them home.
Come on.
Since you're free now,
use this time to prepare to be my bride.
Come on.
So that means we have less than a day left
to spend together before you fly again.
It's no trouble.
Of course I'll see you off.
I'll call you back.
I came to put your stuff away.
This is for your breakfast.
Tissues, shampoo, and toothpaste.
That's my stuff. You don't have to pay.
The razor too?
You shopped for your partner
during work hours?
You were gone five hours.
You shopped for him for three hours.
You only need two hours
to buy crap for the fridge.
In a day, how many minutes
do you dedicate to me?
I have five months till my wedding.
That's all I can give you.
Then we go into extra time.
Marry him, then divorce me.
It's a sharing society.
We can share everything, even wives.
I'd like to try it.
You're so good at sneaking around.
This is why
I said it'd never work out for us anyway!
You're a brute.
I'm so lucky that I managed to get away
from someone like you!
I'll clean it up in the morning.
Don't eat it all up by accident.
Give me back
the time that you spent with other men.
Try living and breathing me.
When you're here, make an effort.
Don't just phone it in.
You have to live and breathe me.
Think of me when you wake up
and when you go to sleep.
That's what counts as compensation.
If you can't do that, don't bother coming.
Nothing you do can make it up to me!
Carl's very sensitive about kids.
Whenever he sees kids,
he always helps them or protects them.
It's like he wants to be a dad
to the kids who are still here.
Daydreaming, are you?
No.
Had enough yet?
-What?
-I just prayed for you.
Had enough blessings?
The alms bowl isn't full yet.
The novice will go hungry.
Go fill his bowl over there.
If you do a charitable deed,
you can go home early today.
What's going on?
Why is there so much food?
My dear Carl.
A food tour group booked lunch here today.
But their plane happened to get delayed,
so they canceled at the last minute.
These days, convenience isn't the focus
of our competitive strategy.
Guests' satisfaction may depend on
communication instead.
YOU HAVE ONE NEW MESSAGE
Our customer service system should cover
our guests throughout their trip,
even while they're out sightseeing.
Please excuse me.
What? I'm in a meeting.
Can't you bring the meeting here?
Get someone else to do it.
If you help me out over here,
I'll give you a day off.
Stay there. I'm on my way.
It worked!
-We did it.
-We don't have to throw it out.
It's lunchtime.
May I suggest we take this meeting
off-site for the afternoon?
We haven't done
team-building activities lately.
Please pack up your things
and let's get a change of scenery.
Let's go.
Please go ahead.
Khim.
Are you on a break?
Yes. What are you doing here?
Did you forget?
We have a meeting with the catering team.
Right.
She cheated again.
Compensation?
He wants girlfriend duties
as compensation?
If I can manage this,
he'll agree to divorce me.
Hey. Does this count as two-timing?
He's obviously making you cheat on Tan.
That's why I need your help.
I know you're good at this stuff.
Whoa… are you calling me two-faced?
That really hurts.
-What?
-Do you want to make it up to me?
Very much!
In that case,
please take care of Tan for me.
But… so Gla isn't just stalling
because he doesn't want a divorce?
Don't worry.
Time won't make us love each other more.
I thought you wanted a day off.
So what is this?
I know how to do my job.
Stop micromanaging me.
Yes.
-Hello.
-Well, hello there!
Well, we're so lucky
that you and your team are free today.
I happened to be looking for
a team activity for us.
I see.
At first,
Madame and I thought that today,
no one would come to taste this after all.
All right, let's work together here.
I'm almost done here.
I'll be there soon.
Did you talk to your wife?
I haven't seen her yet.
Is something wrong, Claire?
I just wonder how you'll settle things
if you keep avoiding each other.
I'll call her back soon.
Should I talk to her for you?
Speaking woman to woman might be easier.
Save that as a last resort.
I'll do it my way first.
You have until I get back.
If you're not divorced by then,
you'll never see me again.
He didn't admit it, did he,
that he meant to trick you?
MARRIAGE CERTIFICATE
He married that woman
because he got her pregnant.
She was just a spoiled brat
who met him in a dating app.
He agreed to marry her
to look after the baby.
They see each other all the time
but pretend there's nothing between them.
This is Carl.
Carl?
Carl Raman. He's half Thai, half Kazakh.
His name comes from his Thai name, Gaogla.
It's nice to meet you… Carl.
Are you married?
Is this your wife's lipstick?
Who told you that?
Your eyes did.
How could you hide
such a big secret from me?
You made me the other woman.
Why did you do this to me?
What do they think I am?
Miss Khim is getting married. Why…
Maybe there won't be a wedding
if they change their minds
and get back together.
Back then,
if I'd known about the certificate,
I could have warned you long ago.
So are they still in love?
She might keep him to herself
so you can't have him.
Who knows?
They might be together right now.
Watch that other side too. All right.
Miss Claire, what is it?
I haven't seen her yet.
Is something wrong, Claire?
I gave Carl an ultimatum.
If he doesn't get divorced,
I'll dump him.
-Excuse me.
-Yes, all right.
Did he promise to get divorced?
If that woman still has hope,
she won't let him go so easily.
People shouldn't hold on
to those they no longer love.
If that woman's so selfish,
what's her heart made of?
I hope you do get what you want.
I know this man means a lot to you.
And you're great for each other.
I hope Carl means what he says.
I don't want to be stupid anymore.
If you get a chance,
please talk some sense into him.
Maybe
this will show us his true colors.
We'll see for certain
if this man is worth loving or not.
What's going on?
Well! Miss Khim?
The stove is ready.
Miss Khim said there's an organizer
coming to prepare the whole wedding.
There is? But she didn't tell me that.
It's me. I'm your wedding planner.
Where are you up to?
-You?
-Yeah.
Khim said I could call the shots
because the two of us have the same taste.
We like the same things.
-We can change this, right?
-Hey.
Are you sure Khim said that?
We need to talk.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Are you up to no good?
I'm her maid of honor,
and I'm organizing the wedding.
It's not unusual.
Then you'd better truly be
the maid of honor and no more.
What?
Are you afraid
I'll replace the bride myself?
I'm just afraid you'll ruin our wedding.
I don't trust you.
What about you?
Your dad doesn't want you to marry her.
You didn't tell her.
The one who will ruin the wedding
is you alone.
If you keep running away from trouble,
it will only hurt Khim.
MAMA SAJEE
Yes, Mama?
Officer, I want to report an assault.
That bitch slapped me!
-Yes, ma'am.
-I won't let this go. I'll come after you!
Mama! I'm sorry.
Did I keep you waiting long?
I was worried I'd have to stay overnight.
And are you hurt at all?
Yes, emotionally!
They ganged up on me!
Right. Give me a second, okay?
Give them hell!
Officer? I'm bailing out this woman.
Sure.
Out there,
don't seduce anyone's husband again!
Who's seducing whom?
I'm the victim here.
Your husband tried to assault me!
No, you're the one who seduced him!
Do you own a salon or a brothel?
Why do you offer massages?
I just massaged his neck!
Your perverted husband got carried away!
My husband is religious!
He's not a desperate single mom like you!
We're getting fined anyway.
I'll slap her again!
-Ma'am, don't!
-Mama, back off!
Let go. Please! That's enough!
Let go, Mama!
Don't fight at the station. Calm down.
-Had enough? Come at me!
-What the hell?
-I trashed your salon!
-Enough, Mama!
Look at her!
She started it! This isn't over!
-Enough.
-Calm down.
If Lita knew,
she'd make me close my salon.
She's very sensitive to shame.
Mama, I don't think
you could open it now anyway.
Hey!
Mama, watch out!
That was close.
Blood!
Does it hurt?
I'm all right.
Thank you. I'll patch this up for now,
then I'll get someone to fix it.
Don't worry, dear.
You got hurt,
and now you're fixing my house too?
This is nothing.
It's risky to hire an unknown contractor
when you're all alone, Mama.
That's true.
I do feel scared.
If they can do this to me,
who knows when they'll be back again?
I can stay here with you.
If I'm here,
they won't dare try to hurt you.
You'd do that?
If there were a man in this house,
I'd feel much safer.
Thank you, sweetie.
Sure.
Oh dear. Lita is calling.
Don't let her know we're together.
She'd be so embarrassed if she knew
I got mixed up with a jealous wife.
All right.
Hello?
How are you, my superstar?
Don't worry about me, honey.
I have so many clients.
MS. LITA THONGMA
You can go now.
Remember what I asked?
When you return, I must be divorced.
You're always decisive at work.
If you really want to get divorced,
who can stop you?
I'll do my best.
If you don't act fast,
it means you don't think I'm important.
You have to respect me more.
If you're over a woman,
you have to sever all ties.
I'll take care of everything.
Don't worry too much.
I hope this isn't goodbye forever.
Good luck.
The car's over there.
-A car's tailing us.
-Whose car is it?
You didn't notice
when it started tailing us?
So what should we do?
Turn right here.
Just turn right.
Are they still behind us?
If they want to find fault with you,
they don't need to follow your car.
To find out where you go,
they only need to follow your GPS,
and they'll know all about you.
Do you see this?
You even dropped a pin on my garage.
No matter when you visit,
the whole world will know.
Seriously?
I always sleep in a different place
so that no one can find me.
But you can't keep a secret.
Do you know
how dangerous this information is,
especially when I work in IT?
I've never had to live in hiding.
I wouldn't know.
You gotta be more careful
when two-timing men.
You're new at being a hot mess.
You'll learn soon.
We need to change cars.
Park it at the garage.
I'll swap them back after work.
Don't wanna get caught cheating?
Well, your workout clothes are in the car.
You're joined at the hip
but insist no feelings are involved?
I like the card design Lita suggested.
Yes, let's go with that, Tan.
Are you okay with that?
Right.
Sure.
Actually…
You can send it straight to the printers.
I don't have any problems with it.
Anyway, let's update each other later.
Is my drink ready, sir?
What a short run.
Isn't it a workout?
My earring fell off during my run.
It must be here somewhere.
Well, help me find it.
Around here?
Hey!
Right there.
Does it taste nice?
Refreshing, right?
Is it nice and cold?
Serves you right.
Karma works fast, doesn't it?
I ordered a sports drink.
I can't help that he heard "salt drink."
It's okay. We're even.
Wait!
What you did to me isn't the same
as what I did to you.
My clothes are wet.
I don't wear earrings.
If you cared,
you'd know something wasn't right.
Who'd know that much about your earlobes?
I'm not that nosy a person.
Remember all the details next time.
Why do we have to stop by?
You ordered these, sir?
-Yes.
-Here you go.
-Here's what I owe.
-All good?
Yes.
Get changed.
Why do I have to get changed?
You just want me to drive, don't you?
I want you to be my secretary.
Don't make me look bad.
Remember the details.
When we care,
we remember every detail, even underwear.
I'm finished.
You said this was a work meeting.
We're about to go to it.
What are you doing?
Aside from food tours,
herbal liquor bar tours
have been requested by lots of people too.
Take a seat.
You're gonna show Westerners this stuff?
Westerners don't just love
royal Thai cuisine alone.
They want to see commoner culture too.
I wanna see what women may think of it
so I want you to try this out.
Hey! Are you nuts?
Don't try anything!
All these people could see, you nutjob!
Now you're a prude?
As if I really wanna hug you.
Are you okay?
Give me the keys.
You're okay, aren't you?
I'm okay.
You came here as my driver.
Now you're my boss, ma'am?
Well, that fits all right, doesn't it?
If you didn't want it,
I'd give it to a hippo.
All these clothes
are secondhand items
that Lita sold online as a student.
Look at this.
She sold them and modeled them herself.
Look at that.
I wanted her to know how to earn money
so she wouldn't become a snob
like the kids at her fancy school.
Look. Khim helped her sell things too.
Khim is such a good girl.
She treats Lita like an equal.
She was basically the only kid
who was friends with Lita.
Without that family,
Lita could never have had
such an education.
-Ma'am, don't!
-Mama, back off!
Break them up!
Mom!
Why didn't you tell me this happened?
Why did you keep it from me?
It's nothing, honey. I can handle it.
Calm down, sweetie.
Please calm down.
If Berm hadn't sent me the video,
I'd never have known you got attacked!
But I'm all right now, aren't I?
Please calm down, sweetie.
And whose is this?
Who are you sleeping with now?
Well, Tanthai brought money
to bail me out.
-Mom!
-He said he wouldn't tell anyone, honey!
If you're mad at me
for embarrassing you in front of a man,
go ahead and be mad at me!
But at that moment,
I really didn't know
who else to ask for help!
Me, of course!
Your own daughter!
How could you think I'd care
more about myself than about you?
I don't care
what anyone thinks of us, Mom.
But I won't let anyone hurt you!
How could they hurt you like this?
Don't you worry.
I've survived this long.
I'll keep surviving.
And if I were ashamed,
I wouldn't have given birth to you,
my perpetual troublemaker.
Khim's partner
is super nice to me.
He's so nice,
I don't know how I can repay him.
If there's anything we can do
for him and Khim,
we have to do it.
No matter how good Tanthai is,
he's not the best choice for Saikhim!
Khim must have better than the best!
I'm giving you two weeks.
Ruin Saikhim's wedding.
Why are you here?
Well,
I…
I heard about Mom,
so I came here right away.
What did you just do?
-Did you take a photo of me sleeping?
-No.
Delete it right now.
I said, delete it.
Give me that.
There. You really did take a photo.
Why did you do that?
What is this?
What does this mean?
When did you take this photo?
I didn't…
You're betraying Saikhim again?
Tan.
Listen to me first, Tan.
I didn't take those photos.
Then who did?
Well…
someone's been watching us.
Are all the photos like that?
Shush.
Why did you keep those photos?
Look, I'm not gonna blackmail you.
How can I trust you?
Don't tell me you let me stay tonight…
Don't jump to conclusions, okay?
Please?
I promise…
no, I swear
that Saikhim will never see these photos.
I don't know if I can trust you now.
Why do you always have ulterior motives?
I can't tell anymore
who you really are.
Tan!
If you wanna hear the truth,
are you sure you can handle it?
Well…
We're here.
-Khim?
-Yeah.
Wake up.
We're here.
But this isn't home!
If I drop you off,
you'll owe me time for the service.
I'm leaving now.
I'm leaving. Okay.
Khim.
Hey. Khim.
Wait inside.
You can't drive like this.
Hey, I'm fine.
Can you get me the keys?
I called Khem for you.
He'll drive you home.
Come on. Wait inside.
Come on.
Let's go.
Come on, Khim.
What's wrong?
Cancel the flight. Give me the car keys.
Give me the keys!
What? Where are you going?
A car's tailing us.
So what should we do?
Turn right here.
Water.
You're still giving orders?
Don't fall asleep.
Have some water.
Drink it properly.
Are you pretending to be drunk?
Hey!
It's so cute.
Did you do it yourself?
Can you teach me?
You keep saying things are cute,
but you never say you love them.
You have to be even cuter than this.
So you won't love me in this life?
You're so sulky.
You're so infuriating.
Luckily, I'm good at making up.
I've said it so many times.
You just didn't listen.
What are you doing?
Aren't you supposed to do this?
No, like this.
This way, I can tell
if I can still make your heart race.
Is it loud and clear?
Is it seismic enough?
I can't stop loving you.
I told you.
I'll stop loving you
when I stop breathing.
I love you too.
What time is it?
Eleven o'clock.
I'm… going home.
My car keys.
You can't leave like this.
You're still drunk.
I can drive.
Hey. Wait.
Khem is on the way.
I… can drive myself.
Where the hell is he?
Hey, stop here!
Hey!
Hey, bro! Something happened!
What is it, Khem?
Your women are fighting!
Turn around and follow them!
Khem!
What?
Crap!
She wants to kill her?
I'm on my way! Keep an eye on them!
Help! Please help Miss Khim!
What did you do to her?
Please help Miss Khim!
Khim, wake up!
Khim! Bro, call an ambulance!
Khim! Wake up, Khim!
-Khim?
-Wake up!
Open your car door!
Come on!
Move aside!
-Khim!
-Miss Khim?
Miss Khim?
Move aside!
Bro! Is she dead?
Carl.
Bro, stay back! Bro!
Stay back! Brace yourself, bro!
-What do you mean?
-Brace yourself, bro!
-Damn it, let go!
-Khim's not breathing!
No!
Khim!
Khim, wake up!
This can't be real.
This can't be real!
Khim!
No!
This can't be real.
I didn't do this!
Khem!
Take Claire away! Go on!
Come here! Get away!
Khim!
Khim, wake up!
Can you hear me?
Wake up, Khim!
You said you'd use your time
to make it up to me.
Don't run from me like this!
Can you hear me, Khim?
I waited for so long.
You can't leave me like this, Khim!
Khim, wake up!
Khim!
Khim, I beg you!
Don't leave me, Khim!
Stay with me, Khim!
Stop pumping.
Her pulse is back.
-Do you know her?
-I'm her husband.
We met by accident.
We know each other
because of our mistakes.
We loved each other
because we had no one left.
We broke up
when we loved each other the most.
Please be all right.
-Khim!
-Please stay back!
The patient's lungs were bruised
by the impact of the crash.
This could cause respiratory failure.
The patient may need to use a ventilator
if she can't breathe on her own.
Before becoming someone else's wife,
make it up to me.
If I do this…
you'll sign the divorce papers
and let me go, right?
You have to sacrifice your time.
You have to be at my beck and call.
If you feel nothing when you're with me,
it means we're nothing to each other,
and I'll sign the papers,
and you can go away,
and marry anyone you want.
If it's not what you asked for last night,
I can do it.
Does it taste nice?
Refreshing, right?
Hey! Are you nuts?
Don't try anything!
All these people could see, you nutjob!
Now you're a prude?
As if I really wanna hug you.
It's a sharing society.
We can share everything, even wives.
I'd like to try it.
You're so good at sneaking around.
This is why
I said it'd never work out for us anyway!
You're a brute.
I'm so lucky that I managed to get away
from someone like you!
Get up and be mad at me,
hate me, or insult me.
But please be all right.
Nurse, we have to move her!
She's not doing so well!
Please don't come in.
Family members have to wait out there.
You can't come in yet.
Out, please.
-Please wait out there.
-Okay.
Even if we aren't friends,
we don't have to be enemies.
We're just strangers
who share some memories.
What do you need?
Are you in pain?
Are you cold?
Are you scared?
Forget it, Khim.
This isn't the time to talk about it.
When you're better,
wake up, and we'll talk.
Then, no matter what you have to say,
I won't stop you.
Bro! How is she?
Not good.
-What about Claire?
-I took her to your place.
She's still shaken.
If something happens to Saikhim,
she could be charged
with manslaughter or murder.
Look after Claire.
I'll deal with the case.
Go on.
So you were at the scene, sir?
-Yes, sir.
-Tell me the details of the incident.
How's my daughter, Doctor?
Her blood carbon dioxide level's high.
The oxygen level in her lungs is low.
We have to give her supportive treatment
and watch out for lung infections.
The doctor said Miss Khim was lucky
someone performed CPR on her.
That's why she regained consciousness.
What caused this accident?
The patient may have driven
while she was intoxicated.
She was drunk?
But that's impossible.
Khim's so careful about that.
For tonight,
we'll observe her in the ICU.
If necessary,
we'll intubate her,
just like I told her husband.
Husband?
Wait.
Doctor, don't tell me
the person who brought Saikhim is…
I had him sign this informed consent form.
You can talk about it as a family.
Please excuse me.
Who does he mean?
CARL RAMAN, THE PATIENT'S HUSBAND
That's Mr. Carl.
Did the doctor misunderstand something?
You might as well know.
Saikhim and Carl were married.
But if they were together last night,
maybe "were" is the wrong word.
What does this mean?
It means they're still a married couple!
And that makes you an adulterer!
Now you know!
I thought you went home.
Your wife is Miss Khim?
If I weren't here,
I wouldn't have found out.
And you brought her here last night.
Today, I meant to confront Miss Khim
about her lie, that's all.
You know you almost killed her?
I didn't want it to end up like this!
The car suddenly rushed forward!
I may be angry,
but I wouldn't kill someone!
I know. I'm not blaming you.
I minded my own business.
How did I get mixed up in this mess?
Calm down.
Let go!
I didn't do it!
Why?
Claire.
If anyone should be blamed, it's me.
I alone should face the consequences.
Seven years ago,
Miss Khim ran off with that man.
He wasn't Carl back then.
He was just a poor young man
called Gaogla.
Gaogla?
Remember the yacht incident?
The man who snuck onto your yacht…
Have you seen the guy who came with us?
Not lately, no.
He followed us on purpose.
He might be a con man.
Really?
She got pregnant by accident,
so Mr. Seen disowned her for a while.
The relationship didn't last long.
Miss Khim miscarried,
Gaogla died in prison,
and we thought it was all over.
But he survived.
Miss Khim recently found out
that Gaogla and Carl are the same person.
Eventually, the dark side had to come out.
You're a coward face to face.
Behind my back, you're so brave.
She's good at killing people
who feel sorry for her.
What do you mean?
Wait and see.
I'll drag your lies and deceit
out into the light.
And you'll see that this woman
is so evil on the inside.
One day,
you'll know the taste
of a lover's betrayal.
They're getting divorced,
but marital property is still an issue.
When Miss Khim agreed to marry you,
she didn't know
that she was still married.
If something happens to you,
I'll get revenge in your next life.
How is Khim?
Still unconscious.
Has the doctor visited her?
Why is Khim so unlucky lately?
You should ask Gla.
So last night, you kept me close
to let Khim cheat on me
with her ex-husband?
How many more secrets
are you hiding from me?
You knew Khim was with him,
but you both kept it from me?
Well, so what?
Will her secret make you leave her?
What choices do I have?
I'd be stupid to marry her.
You'll call me small-minded if I dump her.
Who's the selfish one?
Which of us?
Why do you ask?
Do you want her to die?
What a perfect ending for you.
You'll get sympathy,
and you don't have to pretend to be nice.
You want that ending?
"Nothing else matters now."
"I just want Khim to wake up."
If you really love her,
aren't those the words
that you should say now?
I beg you, Tan.
When she wakes up, don't be cruel to her,
because if she knew, she'd be so hurt
that you're not as nice as she thought.
When we show our true selves,
and someone can stand us at our worst,
and they don't want to run away,
and they're not repulsed,
no matter how awful we are,
if someone
loves us for who we are like that,
then that's called love!
You have to ask yourself
if you can do that for Khim yet.
Sir, Miss Saikhim is awake now.
Family members can see her now.
The doctor said
her oxygen level is back to normal now.
We'll move her to a special ward
where she can recover.
Thank you.
Khim?
Where does it hurt?
I don't even know how I got here.
I only know
I was driving, and I blacked out.
You went drinking with Carl.
Rest up before the divorce.
I hope you survive long enough.
I'm sorry…
Get well soon.
Don't worry about me.
As for the wedding,
let's talk about it later.
Based on this dashcam footage,
it's obvious that they tailgated her!
They wanted to kill her.
He wants his wife's fortune.
But the street CCTV shows
that they didn't hit her car.
And Gaogla was the one who helped her.
Helped to hurt her!
They conspired to do this.
Fortunately,
Khim has fate on her side and survived.
Throw everything at them.
If there's proof
that he tried to kill her,
or that his girlfriend did,
one of them must be charged.
I'd love to know
if he'd let a woman take the fall for him.
But if there's a scandal,
Miss Khim's wedding could be ruined.
Well, let it be ruined!
As long as Gla is still around,
do you think he'd let Khim be happy?
Your father suspects
this wasn't an accident.
I can't remember
if there was a car following me.
I only remember
feeling sleepy the whole time,
like I was gonna black out.
Miss Khim, don't you remember
a car cutting in front of you?
I really can't put the pieces together.
The police are questioning them.
We have a witness
who saw that it was Miss Claire.
Your father thinks this incident
can be used to file for divorce.
So they do wanna press charges.
What should I do?
Do I need a lawyer?
Don't worry. I'll talk to them for you.
Don't forget.
Don't put her reputation at risk like this
'cause if people knew
adultery was the cause,
it could end her career.
Come on.
They waited for this moment.
They'll use this case to get back at us.
How are you?
It still aches.
Claire knows we were together.
She tailgated you yesterday.
She may have gone too far.
She's sorry.
She didn't think it'd get this violent.
I know about the case
the police are putting together.
That's why you're here, right?
Can you leave Claire out of it?
What do you mean?
If you don't accuse her,
I'll agree to the divorce right away.
I'll end it with you unconditionally.
I won't demand anything of you.
No marital property.
No time.
I won't rehash our past.
You can forget we loved each other.
I just want you to leave Claire alone.
You must want to protect your partner.
This wouldn't have happened
if I hadn't lied to her.
If I'd been unlucky and never woken up,
you'd have taken the fall for her?
Yes, I would have.
It's great that I'm still alive.
I could've missed out
on seeing you beg me like this.
I could do even more than this.
I haven't had any food.
Would you really do anything?
My leg is numb.
Seeing you love someone this much
is worth waking up for.
Some things
aren't this obvious
even when said out loud.
Here's the divorce agreement.
I've signed it.
If you agree to sign,
I'll submit the paperwork
to the district office now.
When you feel better,
you can sign it there.
So that means
this may be
the last time we see each other.
As if we've never been apart before.
Death already parted us once.
What's wrong?
Where does it hurt?
My painkillers must've worn off.
It hurts.
What? Miss Khim? What's wrong?
-What is it?
-Khim?
What's wrong?
Rubbing salt in the wound?
Miss Khim, what's wrong?
What did he do to you, my dear Miss Khim?
Khim?
If you don't beg Khim for forgiveness,
I'll make you end up alone!
Why should I apologize to her
when I don't feel guilty?
I need an ambulance now!
A bedridden patient's having seizures!
Nate!
He was the one who helped me.
I thought he hated me!
Do you know where Gla is?
If we had a choice, you'd probably choose
not to have me in your life.
If we could go back to being strangers,
it might be good.
Why was Khim interested in him?
If I said she liked his you-know-what,
could you deal with that?
Get out of Khim's life!
Now I'm gone, try to stay together.
I'm not your excuse anymore.
If she forces herself to stay with you,
it means she still can't move on from me.
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit