THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
You watch your boyfriend at all hours.
Are you scared he'll get away?
No, I'm scared he'll want
something more casual like you do.
Someone else has tried to mess with us.
The housekeeper you hired
is quite something.
Deal with this father and daughter pair.
If you can't handle it,
I'll deal with them myself.
One day,
you'll know the taste
of a lover's betrayal.
Keep this evidence secure.
I'll humiliate him in front of the media
so he won't be able to work in Thailand.
Tell your family that now,
I'm fighting them kamikaze style.
You think this is enough to defeat me?
I'm just happy to humiliate you
in front of the media.
Even if I could create a time machine
and turn back time to meet her,
even if I could erase my mistakes
dozens of times,
it would mean nothing
if we didn't learn to take responsibility
for what we did wrong the first time.
Why did you mess with him?
I just wanted to find out
what he's planning to do to us next.
You couldn't even hurt him,
and he clapped back at you so hard.
Serves you right!
At least I found out
he's going to open
a boutique hotel opposite ours.
He's talking to the property owner.
What are you waiting for?
He'll gain the upper hand, so stop him!
I'm trying, Dad.
I'm trying to make contact
with the hotel owner.
You'll fall for his tricks.
You're never wise to them!
So is our condo project still viable?
Gaogla keeps visiting that house.
The property owner seems to favor him.
But I don't yet know
the details of their negotiations.
Good. If we can't have it, neither can he!
I have a suggestion.
Ten years ago, that land was
almost expropriated to build a gallery.
If we restart that project
and expropriate that land,
Gaogla will lose.
That's good.
That's how we'll get back at him.
I hope no one lets in
his Trojan horse again.
I'm not easily satisfied.
You know what?
Getting revenge on you alone isn't enough.
What did I do to you?
What made you want revenge on me?
I've also asked myself
what I ever did to your family.
What your family did to me,
I'll do it back to you all.
But it might hurt you worse
if you never learn.
Good job correcting your course
in time the other day.
They wanted to play dirty with me.
I only gave as good as I got.
Their new strategy is probably
to take that old house.
We'll have to close
the boutique hotel deal ASAP.
That place will be our first hotel,
so it'll definitely create buzz.
I want you to see it in person.
I don't think it's suitable for a hotel.
Let me take you there.
I'll show you what I want to do with it.
But if you disagree,
I can change my mind.
You're so confident.
I would love to know
what you're dreaming of.
If Mr. Seen changes his mind
and builds a gallery instead,
Prom's condo project will never go ahead.
But Mr. Prom isn't so good
at running such big projects anyway.
I want Prom to get to prove himself.
The gallery project is just politics.
He just wants to defeat Gaogla
while we get almost nothing in return.
Let's take back this project
so you can run it,
and you can train Prom little by little.
If you keep playing his errand boy,
when can we ever stop sneaking around?
Is the award ceremony tonight?
Yeah.
They say this award is cursed.
Whoever wins
either stays single or gets divorced.
Then I can help you break the curse.
If you do win the award,
I'll let you wear the pants
in our relationship.
Don't you think Lita could win?
Our Lita?
If she knew she'd have to stay single,
I doubt she'd still want to win.
Congratulations on winning
Woman of the Year.
Woman of the Year? Me?
Yes, you.
You're kidding, right?
Hello.
We'd like to record an interview
for tonight's press kit.
We need a minute to prepare.
All right.
Hell, that does hurt.
So your dream has come true.
What dream, sir?
You'll outdo Saikhim
for the first time in your life.
It'd be even cooler
if you got to be
the director of a new gallery.
What's this?
An application for that job.
They'll be recruiting
gallery directors soon.
And your victory today will pave the way
for you to gracefully accept
the position of the new gallery director.
I bought this award to upgrade you
even though it should go to Saikhim.
Well?
Am I generous?
Aren't you touched?
You bought the award?
What does this mean?
Gaogla wants to open
a competing hotel opposite mine.
I need you to help me get rid of him
by opening this gallery to beat him to it.
You cut him out of Saikhim's life once.
Why don't you do it again
to win this award?
The Stupid Woman of the Year Award.
That's what you think I deserve, right?
If you don't want it, don't accept it.
Let Saikhim have it.
How could you do this?
Would you rather let Gaogla expose you
for switching the letters
and making them break up?
If you promise me
that you'll keep everything secret
and keep him out of Saikhim's life,
I promise
I'll pay for you
to study in England with her.
The one who'd blackmail me isn't Gaogla.
That would be you!
And I'm not Saikhim.
I won't let you control her life
with your dirty tricks!
If you don't seize this chance,
your life will never get better again.
A reward for being a good girl
that Saikhim misses out on when she's bad?
Of course I don't want it.
I don't need to win it.
I don't care.
For the 2021 Woman of the Year Award,
we selected women
who play important roles in…
You're not going in?
Are you afraid you'll lose
and be disappointed?
Be more gracious.
Can't you bear it
when someone outdoes you?
And the Woman of the Year Award
for this year goes to
Ms. Lita Thongma,
an up-and-coming young designer,
for her globally recognized talent.
Congratulations!
I'm happy for you.
Where are you going?
Accept your award first.
It should've gone to Khim.
Hey. Accept your award first.
Accept your award first!
Hi, Ms. Lita. Come on.
It's your cue to accept the award now.
Please go ahead.
Ms. Lita is here!
Please welcome her to the stage!
-Congratulations, Ms. Lita.
-This way, please. Go ahead.
Congratulations.
Let's get a photo together.
Another round of applause, please!
That girl has accepted the award.
That wasn't so hard.
Take care of her application.
Yes, sir.
Lita! Hey!
What's wrong? What happened?
This award is supposed to shame me
for not being good enough.
That's nuts.
Who'd think that?
It's not an award, Khim.
It's a punishment for us both.
Punishment for what? We did nothing wrong.
Well, for…
the land on the other side
that you didn't give your dad.
You didn't do it,
so I got screwed.
Lita!
-Lita, take it!
-No! I said I don't want it!
-But Mr. Seen said you should!
-I said no!
As for Mr. Songseen,
tell him to go to hell!
Lita, this way, please.
Miss!
Give her this.
That award
should actually go to you.
But a sponsor made a big donation
all of a sudden, so the award was stolen.
They even organized the award ceremony
to secure the prize for their nominee.
How do you know?
Well, everyone here tonight knows that.
What did you do to offend your dad?
Now he's not spoiling you like before.
We may be competitors,
but you're smart.
I don't mind.
I'd rather work with you.
By the way, have you heard?
I'm about to open a hotel across the road.
If you feel uncomfortable staying here,
you can come and work with me.
Don't stay and let men
treat you like their puppet.
Where's Dad?
He's gone out again.
GALLERY CONSTRUCTION PROJECT MODEL
…the land on the other side
that you didn't give your dad.
You didn't do it,
so I got screwed.
I'm about to open a hotel across the road.
If you feel uncomfortable staying here,
you can come and work with me.
Hey, bro.
That gallery project just got resurrected.
They want to expropriate
that old property.
It can't be a coincidence.
It was your father-in-law
who brought this project back.
He must want to mess with us.
What will you do?
I'll talk to Gloy first.
Turn your face up.
Gloy?
Where are you now? You're late.
I can't make it now.
Is something wrong?
Look, I'm busy. I'll call you back later.
Khem, what the hell's going on?
Why won't Gloy come here?
I'll find out.
Are we done here?
Cut!
-Claire, take a break.
-Sure.
Carl.
My mom's flight is landing tonight.
Why did you invite her here?
I'm introducing you to my family,
so I want us all to be together.
I wonder if your mom will like me.
I'm not her favorite.
She's not so protective of me.
So no pressure.
Don't worry.
Whoa, it's so pretty.
How did you find this place?
I was staying at the hotel opposite here.
It's nice and cool here.
When this flower is on you,
it looks even prettier.
Claire, this is Asia, my adoptive mom.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Hello, darling.
We meet at last.
Please come in.
-Hello.
-I want to ask you about that old house.
I've prepared food
just for you, Madame Asia.
Have you had this before?
I haven't, but I'm not very fussy.
Just like Carl.
He's not fussy either.
Sometimes he's so laid-back,
he's almost careless.
He always eats rich, bland food.
He can't really be taught
to have better tastes.
Mom.
-There you are.
-Yes.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Do you visit your home in Thailand often?
Actually, I never visit at all.
You see,
I have no home here anymore,
so there's no reason to.
But don't you have any relatives
who still live here?
No, I don't.
I invited you all here today
because I'd like to start food tours here.
Auntie, since you're a good cook,
I'd like to bring tourists here
to enjoy your cooking
in this friendly atmosphere.
Thank you so much.
You should do it.
All your food is tasty and hard to find.
Thank you, my dear.
This house is beautiful
because it's lively.
I want visitors
to experience this loving atmosphere
that's just like a family visit.
Auntie is compiling
a book of traditional Thai recipes,
so I'd like to ask you
to work on the manuscript.
Of course.
Excuse me. Another guest just arrived.
Another guest?
That might be my guest.
I hope you don't mind
that I went ahead and invited someone.
When I heard that this meal was special,
I wanted to invite this person.
-Please excuse me.
-I'll go and get them.
Miss Khim, please go on in.
Everyone is there already.
Why are you here?
Your adoptive mom invited me.
Don't you have manners?
The host didn't invite you.
Why did you come?
I told you. Your mom invited me.
I invited her myself.
Don't be rude to my guest.
Come on in, darling.
This is Saikhim.
Her family owns the hotel across the road.
Well, hello, my dear.
Well, we're neighbors, aren't we?
-Come on in.
-Please sit.
Come on, Miss Khim, let's eat.
This is my mom.
Mom, this is Miss Khim, my idol.
Nice to meet you.
This is Rarin.
She flew from America.
She just arrived today.
Rarin?
Come and sit here, Miss Khim.
Would you believe
that I was a picky eater as a kid?
Mom had to make me a packed lunch
to take to school every day.
And I only ate
Mom's chicken stew all the time.
Can you guess
what was the only Thai food Mom made me?
American fried rice.
The American kids had never heard of it.
Right, Mom?
How nice.
I don't have a mom.
I don't know what a mom's cooking is like.
When I get sick,
and I think of home-cooked meals,
for me, home-cooked meals,
they're…
they don't exist.
I don't know what they are.
What are you doing?
Why did you invite Saikhim tonight?
Are you dating Claire
because she and Saikhim share a mom?
You knew,
so you brought them together.
Didn't you do everything
to make today happen?
The day Saikhim finds out her mom left her
to have a new daughter?
Well, here's your chance for revenge.
What are you waiting for?
Even so, you have no right to interfere.
You're saying you're not holding a grudge?
What did you make all these plans for?
If you want to be cruel, do it properly.
Go in for the kill.
You're not taking this seriously.
Whoa, it looks so difficult.
It's so elaborate.
My dear,
noble ladies in the old days had to know
how to carve fruit,
roll betel leaves,
and make traditional dumplings
and crispy pancakes
to call themselves proper noble ladies.
Actually, it's not so hard.
Let me show you.
There.
Put it there for them.
-Try it. Please go ahead.
-Try carving the fruit.
Thank you.
-Try it.
-Good.
-How do I start?
-Okay. Look.
-Teach them.
-First, we have to make the base.
Right.
-Can you do it?
-Maybe.
Look.
-See?
-It looks like a flower.
You're so good at this, Mom.
It's not so hard. It's finished.
-Oh no!
-My dear!
-You're bleeding!
-Careful.
I'm all right.
I'll clean myself up.
My goodness!
I hope it's not a deep cut.
I'm so sorry.
Does it hurt, honey?
It hurts less than knowing
you're still alive, Mom.
But everyone said that my mom died.
So why…
Your dad wouldn't let us see each other.
He claimed that I died,
and he made me
walk out of your life that day.
Not only are you still alive,
you also have a new daughter.
What am I supposed to think?
Claire isn't my real daughter.
She's my new husband's daughter,
so I had to raise her.
I feel so much better.
You didn't just leave your child,
you raised someone else's.
You were so young.
You wouldn't have understood.
So you had to pretend
you didn't know your own daughter?
Okay. I get it now.
Ma'am, I can't even call you Mom.
Let's just say
that we've never met, okay?
As far as you're concerned,
I never existed anyway.
All these ghosts are coming back to life.
You all came back to mock me, didn't you?
This is just how your dad makes
people around you disappear.
You can't blame everyone for leaving you.
It's you who disrespects
and kills everyone.
You really want to hurt me?
If you do,
you've succeeded.
I'm in pain. Are you happy now?
You're in pain
because it hurts to see us
doing better without you.
I'm in pain
because I still remember who you were.
You were someone who never hurt me.
Where are you hiding him?
He's the one I wish I could get back.
How much must you hate me
to do this to me?
I just want you
to be unable to love again.
You selfish people don't deserve love.
Ask yourself this.
As a mom, what did you do to your kid?
-What do you mean?
-You can't love anyone but yourself.
So now you have no one left.
Not even your dad.
You think he cares a lot about you.
But he's not honest with you.
He took your mom away from you,
saying only that she wasn't worthy.
I guess you know now
that it's you who isn't worthy of us.
So this is it.
This is the lesson you want me to learn.
Hey! You're going to leave just like that?
Where's Miss Khim?
Well,
she left.
Right. So did Carl go to see her off?
No, he's on the phone.
Right. No wonder he disappeared.
-Yeah.
-Wait inside with us, ma'am.
Sure, darling.
Khim!
Miss Khim!
What happened to you?
What have you been doing?
Miss Khim! What's wrong?
You must care a lot about her
if you ran out after her.
Are you happy now?
Don't give me attitude.
You did everything to get here today.
She's probably shouting at her dad now.
Everything is going as you planned.
Did you come to threaten me?
You're too softhearted.
That's why your life can't get any better.
You should be fighting with them, not me.
Don't try to pick a fight with me.
Do you need to get something in here?
Dad, guess who I just saw.
I just saw Mom.
I've seen everyone who died and came back.
The truth is
they're still alive, aren't they?
Dad, explain to me
what the hell is going on!
I did something
that Saikhim's dad couldn't live with.
He said that I don't deserve
to be someone's mother.
So he pressured me
to stay away from Saikhim.
Look at these photos.
Look!
Do women who are willing
to pose for such lewd photos
deserve to continue being mothers?
She fell for the photographer.
He tricked her into posing for this smut,
and the photos were leaked.
I couldn't bear the shame!
How was my daughter supposed to live?
She couldn't face people's judgment,
so she attempted suicide.
She was the one who left me and you first!
I was so young…
so I did something stupid
to solve the problem.
I took pills to kill myself
and to get back at Seen
for not forgiving me.
I kept blaming myself
and forgot to think of Khim.
I wanted to run away from my problems.
He made me feel like I was disgusting.
Too disgusting to be a mother.
Then I found out
that while he thought I was wicked,
he was already looking for
a new mom for Saikhim.
He let someone replace me.
Later, I realized
that maybe my story became a scandal
because someone leaked it on purpose
so that they could break up our family.
When I suggested that she die
and disappear from your life,
she agreed to do it
though you were so young.
She didn't care about you at all.
She was so unfaithful.
Why should I have held onto her?
If you decide to leave,
don't let her see your face again.
She wanted to be with someone else.
She chose to have a new life.
I warned her in the strongest terms
that she'd never see you again.
She left anyway.
It's unbelievable
how selfish she was.
I agreed to walk away
to let Saikhim think
that her mom died back then…
and to allow Seen
to hold his head up high in public.
That's why I couldn't see Khim again.
And she was so young.
She didn't even understand sadness.
Because this whole time,
she's only known one side of the story,
I don't know
why I should destroy this girl's life now.
After all, we've managed
to get on with our lives all this time.
Why did you keep me in the dark
this whole time, Dad?
You lied to me
about something so important.
Is there anything left in this life
I can trust you on?
What did Rarin say to you?
Why is she back?
Mom has a new daughter now.
And that daughter is
Gaogla's new girlfriend.
Gaogla again?
He never gives us a moment's peace.
-Why don't you criticize him too?
-He only showed me the truth to hurt me.
Even if it hurts, at least it's the truth!
I'm wondering if his death and mom's
were just your excuses.
You use me as an excuse
to get rid of everyone you don't like!
What are you talking about?
Gaogla said that we are
the ones who killed him.
Why did Gla go to jail?
Can you explain that to me?
You let him manipulate you again?
Well,
when someone is unworthy,
you don't keep them around anymore!
And now I'm unworthy
of being your daughter,
so you bought that award for Lita
just to use her to grind me down, right?
Lita sees you as a competitor.
She's never even seen you as a friend!
She's done everything to outdo you!
You know what?
She'd steal your boyfriend if she could!
So what?
If I'm not as good as Lita, will…
will that embarrass you?
Will you kill me like this too?
Maybe Mr. Seen lied
because he didn't want you
to hate your own mom.
Lies
are sometimes told out of kindness, honey.
Just like how you're consoling me
but you're actually laughing at me?
Miss Khim?
Your dad really wanted the best for you.
Believe me.
But Auntie Oon,
you don't tell me the truth either.
How sad for poor Saikhim.
Everyone around her
is so insincere.
Khim! What have you been doing?
What happened, Khim?
Can I… stay the night here?
What's wrong, Khim?
I called, but you didn't answer.
I just want you
to be unable to love again.
You selfish people don't deserve love.
Ask yourself this.
As a mom, what did you do to your kid?
Do women who are willing
to pose for such lewd photos
deserve to continue being mothers?
She fell for the photographer.
He tricked her into posing for this smut.
She was the one who left me and you first!
Shall we go and see your mom?
Let's hear her side of the story.
Don't make any rash decisions now.
People have good sides and bad ones.
But it doesn't mean
they can't be parents.
Your dad wouldn't let us see each other.
He claimed that I died,
and he made me
walk out of your life that day.
You didn't just leave your child,
you raised someone else's.
You were so young.
You wouldn't have understood.
You can't love anyone but yourself.
So now you have no one left.
You really want to hurt me?
If you do,
you've succeeded.
I'm in pain. Are you happy now?
You're in pain
because it hurts to see us
doing better without you.
I'm in pain
because I still remember who you were.
You were someone who never hurt me.
Where are you hiding him?
He's the one I wish I could get back.
THE WELL-BEING SCHOOL
Is he sleeping, or rehearsing for death?
I think he's tired.
He drove very far.
As for you,
give him a chance now.
But Dad!
Do you see that?
Do you think I'm a beggar
who can't be a chooser?
If you don't like him,
don't keep him to yourself.
When have I ever done that?
Well, you ground down his confidence
by saying that he's filthy
to stop him flirting with other women.
You're mean.
I feel sorry for Khem.
He's so innocent.
Gloy, stop, please.
Sorry I didn't look after you.
Be careful. Watch your step.
By the way, Gloy,
Gla said you were driving
back to your dad's place.
Wait. You're pampering me.
Did you do something bad?
What? I'm just being kind.
If you appreciate it, thank me.
Don't insult me.
Come on.
You're making amends.
-You'd better keep it up.
-All right.
This way, please.
Other than guilt,
do you feel anything else?
Maybe she doesn't just want your pity.
This life we're given,
I've lived half of it and got nowhere.
The rest of it
I'll give to you if you want.
It might be good for me
to live for someone else.
This is unbearable enough.
I can't bear the rest of your life!
Ew.
It's his fault he's a dummy.
I can't help that.
Where are the land transfer documents?
Right. I forgot. I'll go get them for you.
I prepared them already.
Here. This concerns the land.
And I found this.
It's been seven or eight years.
I don't know if it's still valid.
MARRIAGE CERTIFICATE
Dad.
What is this?
What? It's from back then. Remember?
People think Gla died.
And he changed his whole name.
I didn't think this was still a problem.
Would this be a big deal?
Well, hurry up and call the lawyer, then.
-Hurry.
-Okay.
Yes? Mr. Carl asked me
to deal with the expropriation.
Okay, could you please check the document
that I just sent to your phone?
Is it still legally valid?
This is very important.
I need you to check it now, please!
All right.
Hey, Khem!
Khem, wake up!
Get your stuff and come down now!
What? Okay.
You're leaving now?
-Yeah.
-What did the lawyer say?
I have to go to Bangkok to follow up now.
This is deadly serious.
I have to fix it for Gla now.
As for your land transfer,
I'll handle it later.
Okay. All right, honey.
What's happening?
Come on! Don't waste time.
Where are we going? Bye, sir.
-Bye, Dad.
-Bye, sir.
-Come on!
-Khem! Look after my kids.
Yes, sir. Where to?
Listen. Let me tell you something.
I am wondering
if they'll transfer some land around here
to build a gallery on.
You never know.
Maybe I won't get to die here.
I might even have to move
to a retirement home.
They're empty threats.
This project was already canceled once.
I'm looking for ways to threaten them too.
Don't give up yet, Auntie.
Maybe they'll self-destruct.
Someone wants to investigate our gallery
for promoting our hotel's interests.
What?
And they know
we're appointing our own gallery director.
How is this possible?
We haven't announced the vacancy yet.
How do they know?
What if Lita betrayed us?
PROTESTERS DEMAND GRAFT PROBE
I bet Gaogla did this.
He's accusing you of corruption.
Such stupid advisers
could land you in jail, Uncle.
It's you and Khim's marriage certificate.
The lawyer says it's still legally valid.
Gla, you have to divorce her now,
or this could hurt our business.
If you don't divorce her,
she can't marry her partner.
That's good.
We have the upper hand.
Hey, why don't you look bothered?
Are you saying
you already thought of the certificate?
I'm waiting to see
when Saikhim will figure it out.
Gla!
Don't you worry about what would happen
if your girlfriend found out about this?
Khim? Are you feeling better?
Yes, a little.
Aren't you busy?
I think I'll resign from the bank.
I just spoke to someone about a new job.
It's your family's bank.
Would your dad let you resign?
If I want to grow up,
I have to get out of there,
or Dad will keep dominating me.
LAND EXPROPRIATION GRAFT PROBE
That story's about Dad!
It's about your hotel too.
He's coming after my dad.
Who is?
Picking up an item?
Yes, I am.
Was it you who had someone
request a graft probe on my dad?
Your dad wanted
to expropriate this land for himself.
He's abusing his power
so he deserves to be investigated.
What if we gave you this house?
Would you forget your grudge against me?
I don't want to hold this grudge.
So withdraw the request.
If you want to get revenge on me,
leave other people out of it.
You want this house? Take it.
But leave us alone for good.
If only it were that simple.
Even if I got this land,
we might still be co-owners.
We never got divorced.
Legally, we're the same person.
That's impossible.
Sometimes retribution comes
in the form of marriage.
So let's get divorced.
I'd love to.
But I need to make sure
you won't take my money.
Who wants your money?
This land isn't even mine,
and you want it anyway.
Can I trust litigious people like you?
So what do you want?
Give me your hotel shares
if you want to remarry.
If you've a better offer,
I'll consent to the divorce.
Dream on.
So let your husband-to-be wait forever.
You won't marry him in this life.
Maybe you will in the next.
How long have you been here?
Let's talk.
What were you and Saikhim talking about?
Do you know each other from somewhere?
We do.
What marriage were you talking about?
We dated for a little while.
Just dating? Or were you married?
And does Claire know about this?
It was a long time ago.
I haven't told Claire.
I've been with Claire
longer than I was with her.
I'm not interested in her anymore.
Let me tell you something.
Nature lets time slowly destroy love,
anger, vengeance, infatuation,
and sadness,
leaving only memories.
It's like
how I've forgotten the disappointment
I had with Saikhim's dad.
From what I've seen,
it's like you're trying to defy nature.
You're afraid of forgetting something.
Can you honestly say
that Saikhim means nothing to you?
If circumstances didn't bring us all
here together like this,
I'd never let my daughter get stuck
in such a complicated relationship.
No matter which daughter.
Legally,
if we can prove that a married couple
has not cohabited for over three years,
that marriage has ended,
and they can file for divorce.
If they don't file for divorce,
are there easier ways to end this?
They can both sign a divorce agreement,
but both parties must give consent.
What about their assets?
That will be a problem.
They have to find solutions together.
This divorce agreement includes
the following conditions.
You won't demand marital property.
The assets acquired during the marriage
will be considered
each party's personal property.
You can try making this offer to him.
If he has no objections to the terms,
you may not need to file for divorce.
I heard you've consulted a lawyer.
So that means you and Saikhim signed
a marriage certificate, right?
This woman could bankrupt you.
Our business
is Nate's too.
I won't let anyone else
try to steal my son's inheritance.
Before you enter the stock market,
deal with this mess once and for all.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll never put the company at risk.
When your father snuck around
with your mother,
he said the same thing.
Men don't do things definitively.
That's why this mess has escalated now.
You're lucky you didn't have kids,
or they'd come begging!
Yes, know!
I'm already freeloading.
You can barely deal with me.
The designer sent this
decorating plan for the boutique hotel.
If you don't finalize this divorce,
I'll take this project back.
Don't let your ex-wife
steal this opportunity.
I guarantee that I'll deal with it.
If you can be tied down
by a piece of paper,
you must be really weak.
BOUTIQUE HOTEL DESIGN
Hey, bro, what did she do to you?
Nothing yet.
But she might try to take everything back.
We're playing into her hands.
Wait.
You have to get divorced now.
She'll have no excuse to take your firm.
If I have to obey her every command,
I'll only be a mindless body like him.
I wasn't born to be anyone's errand boy.
I won't let anyone replace you…
because we shouldn't covet
someone else's destiny.
So that means you can't marry Tan yet?
Not only can't I marry him,
I also can't let him know about this.
I gotta get divorced
before Tan suspects something.
And does your dad know about this?
He can't know either.
Right now, other than us,
the only person who knows is Auntie Oon.
But I guess she doesn't suspect what I do.
There's no reason he won't get divorced.
He has to protect his interests too.
But I have to placate him
with the divorce papers
before he uses my past to blackmail me.
Honestly, I'm so afraid
of what he might do.
If he could kill me
so he could be single again,
I think he would.
He wouldn't go that far, right?
He hates me so much, he could do anything.
You used to love each other so much.
How could he hate you this much?
Hey!
So… did Dad get you involved
in this gallery too?
I dodged that bullet.
Otherwise, I'd be screwed.
They'd say I was your dad's plant.
Lita, I'm sorry
that Dad brought you into this mess.
He's paying for it now.
Not only can't he steal that land,
he's getting interrogated so much,
he may lose his job as a minister.
Did you tell anyone
that I nominated you
as the gallery director?
Here's the evidence.
Take it if you're so scared.
Who leaked this story?
Now Gaogla has reported me.
If you're worried I'm a double agent,
you should never have involved me.
Forget all this.
If anyone asks,
you must say that you know nothing!
Of course.
Abuse of power
has never been my thing.
Good.
Just don't turn on me later.
And you shouldn't use Saikhim's letter
to threaten me again!
If you do,
I might change my mind,
switch sides, and tell Gaogla
that you wrote that fake letter
and used me
to break up their relationship.
If he finds out,
he might make you
pay for what you did plus interest
even worse than what's going on now.
Good manners really can't be taught.
You paid for my education,
not an attitude adjustment.
Our bad habits
die hard, don't they?
Watch Lita closely.
-See if she contacts Gaogla.
-Yes, sir.
We're requesting a graft probe
into the gallery,
so we need to know if you're in on it,
or if you just got used.
He can't even protect himself.
Do you think he can protect you?
I think
she bites the hand that feeds.
I usually train here,
but I haven't had much time lately.
I know you're having a tough time
with work and your family,
so I thought I'd bring you here
to blow off some steam.
If you want to vent for any reason,
give me all you've got.
I'll be your emotional punching bag.
Too tight?
-It's fine.
-Good.
-Coach?
-Yes?
-Please look after this student.
-Of course.
Should we warm up?
Wait. Miss Khim!
Hey, it's Miss Khim.
That's my mom.
What a coincidence.
You're boxing here too?
I brought her.
Carl needs volunteers
to teach foreigners Muay Thai
in exchange for foreign language classes,
so I wanted to give it a try.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm Tanthai, Khim's partner.
This is great.
I'll have a study buddy.
Looks like she doesn't want one.
She looks more like she wants an opponent.
Her hands are itching for a fight.
Khim told me all about you, ma'am.
You see, we're getting married
in five or six months.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to invite you to honor us
with your presence at our wedding.
But
Khim's father might not want me there.
But I'm happy for you.
I guess Khim wants
to build a perfect family.
One that she's never had.
I guess Khim is still in shock.
But deep down,
I think she's happy
to know that you're still around.
I think we should make the best
of our time together today.
-Right block.
-Left hook.
Great job, Claire.
Very good.
-Enough.
-I'm taking a break.
When she comes at you, defend yourself.
Don't be scared.
If she fights hard, you fight hard.
Let's have a duel.
-Khim!
-Carl!
-Enough!
-Are you okay?
You're weak.
-Hey, Carl!
-What the hell?
You really want a fight?
Hey!
Khim!
Do you know what you did?
You're a sore loser.
Khim.
Let's go.
Take a break.
Come on.
Let's go.
Khim, how could you hit him
when his guard was down?
He had his girlfriend attack me first!
Didn't you see?
Okay, Khim.
I think you should take a break,
or you'll get angrier during training.
Come on.
Jeez, Tan.
I'm not scared of weaklings like him!
All talk, no walk.
Khim, do you realize
that every time you see him,
you lose your temper?
Well, didn't you see him, Tan?
-He…
-Khim!
You have to compartmentalize.
Okay, if you want to blow off steam,
I think you'd better take it out
on that sandbag.
Come with me.
Come on.
Right. Yes. Sure thing.
Right. I've found it.
That's right.
That's correct.
Hold on one second.
Why don't you have him
read these important documents?
Don't flatter yourself.
There are more important things than you.
Have him read them
so we can schedule the divorce.
Make him read them.
BOUTIQUE HOTEL DESIGN
I want his answer today!
-Bro.
-Again.
I sent the lawyer the proof.
He should also be charged
with unlawfully appointing
a gallery director.
We'll knock him out this time.`
I've better news too.
The divorce agreement your wife drew up.
Check it out.
It says she won't demand` any assets.
Kick! Great!
Good! Great!
Great!
You don't want any money from the divorce?
Your whole family is the same.
You play dirty then play nice.
I'm fair.
I don't want anything.
Just sign the papers.
I'm almost touched.
If you hadn't ambushed me earlier,
I could've signed them by now.
You wanna make me angry?
You get angry like your dad.
Would you dare do this
in front of other men?
Just tell me what you want.
The farm isn't far from here.
If those two don't want to go,
I can take you there on the way back.
Khim.
I invited her to the coconut farm too.
Maybe she'd rather be
with her family, Tan.
I want to be with you, Khim.
Let me come with you.
Show-off.
Be careful!
Okay.
Tan!
Wait there. I'll come and get you.
To trust me with your life,
we must trust each other.
Then we'll both survive.
Watch out!
Hey.
I want you to get to know your mom.
The chance for you to spend time with her
doesn't come around often.
Maybe she feels uncomfortable.
She doesn't want her child to know.
But I want her to know
I'm ready to look after you in her place.
Then she'll feel assured
because you trust me with your life.
She doesn't care about me that much, Tan.
Khim.
Pick that up.
You're the one who's too mean
to care about her.
That's not true.
Don't make that face.
Come here.
Come here. Smile. Go on.
Aw.
They're so sweet.
There you go.
Tan.
Such show-offs.
Pardon?
I said it's too sunny.
It's getting too hot.
Come here.
Hold on, okay?
Let's spoil my mom.
-Okay?
-That hurts.
Does it hurt? Take this.
Coconut water.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Can I ask
what Mr. Tan loves about Miss Khim?
Don't be nosy. They're embarrassed.
Have you heard the saying,
"True love is
falling for one person every time"?
That's how I feel about Khim.
That's very sweet.
See how she finishes her drink
but keeps trying to drink more?
The first time I saw that, I thought,
"She doesn't care how she looks."
She looked so natural.
Every time I think of that,
it makes me smile.
Disney princesses would never dare
to drink so greedily in front of men.
Don't do that again anywhere. It's rude.
I think you feel the same way, Mr. Carl.
No, I don't feel that way.
I don't like greedy women.
Well, I wasn't talking about that.
-I meant--
-I don't know. I have a short memory.
Hey!
Where are you throwing them?
Khim.
I know that you already have everything.
But if anything bothers you,
and you can't talk about it with anyone,
I want you to think of me.
Although I'm not
the most important person in your life,
I'm ready to listen to all your problems,
no matter how serious they are.
I'm ready to help you.
Don't let your dad numb your feelings.
Men who have been disappointed
will not ask for anyone's love.
But they will hurt others
to protect themselves
from more disappointments.
Men like that
pressure us to feel guilty
about everything
until we feel we're not good enough.
I don't know what happened
between you and him.
But I think it's for the best
that you're trying to stay away from him.
You know about us, ma'am?
Carl… is a lot like your father.
I can tell he's hard to live with.
He doesn't say what he means.
He wasn't like this before.
Seen wasn't like this before either.
It was my fault.
Boys, you must be so tired.
Take a shower, and then we'll eat.
Yes, sir.
Khim, I'm sorry
if I make you feel bad about your dad.
Maybe the reason he's like this is
I disappointed him.
Tan? I've brought you a change of clothes.
Where should I leave them for you?
You!
Let go! Are you nuts?
You wanted to flirt with your man?
Sorry.
I'm the wrong one.
What are you doing? Hey!
Don't! No!
Now we're even.
That's for what you did this morning.
Hey! Wait.
You're too violent.
I'm all beaten-up.
You see this?
That scar, it's…
All your fault.
Of course it is.
What do you mean?
Excuse me.
Is Mr. Carl in there?
Please feel free to shower in there.
And… I'll just shower out here.
There's no such thing as a secret.
It's okay if everyone knows.
What did you say?
Hey!
The bathroom's free.
Feel free to use it.
But watch out for creepy-crawlies.
Hey, Khim.
Why are you all wet?
I got so hot
that I just showered like this.
Why didn't you get changed?
Do you still have an outfit I can borrow?
Let's find one.
-All right.
-Come on.
So shall we go ahead and eat?
-Yes.
Take this.
How is it?
Do you like it?
-It's very good.
-Both the food and the eye candy.
Pervert.
I meant the view. Don't be dirty-minded.
Psycho.
Be quiet and eat.
Don't say such rude things.
Eat this first. Don't get angry yet.
So hangry. So mean.
Hey!
Gosh.
-What's wrong?
-It's so spicy.
Are you all right?
Is it too spicy?
I'll get water.
-Sure.
-Here. Try this.
Curry.
Have some first.
Does that help?
How did you know that?
Coconut curry.
Give your woman some.
Chili's spicy chemical is fat-soluble.
Coconut milk reduces the spiciness.
It soothes the burning too.
-Coconut curry.
-Eat it. You'll feel better.
Go on.
-Well…
Well… we're screwed.
I thought everyone knew
that coconut milk cancels out spiciness.
I've heard that too.
And I've heard it too.
Look it up. Search for it. Yeah.
You know, it really does help.
-You see?
-Yeah.
For my daughter,
200 million isn't asking too much.
Though Dad isn't thrilled,
I'll still marry you.
I'll give you
one last chance to redeem yourself.
Ruin Saikhim's wedding.
Is this your wife's?
Are you married?
I uncovered his lie.
And he said he's not divorced yet.
I want this divorce.
I can't live
with this man in my life anymore!
He almost ruined your whole life!
You should at least
get marital property as compensation.
The new divorce agreement.
She wants marital property.
So she wants to be this dog's tick.
Get her to talk to me face to face.
This has to end today.
Just one night
in exchange for a lifetime with him.
Isn't it worth it?
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit