THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
You know, don't you, that Gla
isn't my own son?
His garage customizes tax-dodging cars,
so it's being raided.
If he's arrested,
Saikhim has nowhere to go.
Marry me, Khim.
I won't make you regret
giving up your future
to be with someone like me.
Today is the first day
of the rest of your lives
as lawfully wedded husband and wife.
Kissing practice.
You'll feel less awkward,
or you'll get punished.
You closed it?
Where's the money?
I gave it to Khem for his own--
I gave him all the money
'cause I got a power plant surveying gig.
I'll go to the forests of Laos
with the engineers.
I want to make all that money back
before our baby is born.
I have learned
that love is most fragile
when you have fears and doubts.
Love is strongest
when you have trust and certainty.
Well? What are you staring at?
What are you doing here?
I came to surprise you.
Surprise?
What if I'd died of shock?
Then you'd be a scary pregnant ghost.
I'm not laughing.
Are you really mad?
I've missed you so much
for almost a month.
Please don't look so grumpy.
Let me see you.
Hey, put it down.
Why didn't you put on weight?
Don't you eat?
Hey, kid, you're not too hungry, are you?
Mommy's not eating.
Why is Mommy like this?
It's okay, kid. Daddy's home.
Don't worry, you won't starve.
I've brought you something.
You've brought something?
I've replaced your broken one.
I have money now.
I'll pay it off for you.
Thank you.
I'll make good use of it.
I have to go back next week
to survey the potential tunnel site.
It'll be even harder work.
You're leaving again?
I'm here just one week.
I'll make you both nice and fat.
What?
What happened?
Why are your hands so filthy?
They're covered in dirt.
Well, I've been working.
I'm back now.
You can be a lady of leisure again.
Okay?
Work your magic, Mama Ooi.
-Sure.
-Make her hands soft again.
Make them smoother than my face.
You're newlyweds, right?
That's why you're so lovey-dovey.
Sorry, my honeymoon period will go on
for decades to come.
Decades?
Make it to the end of this year first.
Give me your hand.
What is it?
Is he seeing someone else?
Excuse me.
Yes, Auntie Oon?
Miss Khim, I have some news.
I've heard that Mr. Seen isn't very well.
Is Dad all right?
Your father had a fall.
It might be due to his blood pressure.
The doctor said he's at risk for a stroke.
How's Dad doing now?
He's just left the hospital.
I've heard he's going to stay
at a friend's plantation near yours.
Really?
Miss Khim, won't you go and visit him?
Does he really want to see me, Auntie Oon?
You knew the risks,
so why did you take this job?
How else could I make a living, bro?
I tried to open my garage and got scammed.
Will this be worth the risks?
Well, I accepted this job
because it's close to your home.
We'll just drive across the border.
Once we've delivered the stuff,
we'll get all the money, bro.
I can't do it.
I promised Khim I wouldn't do crime again.
Okay, bro.
I'll do it alone.
Khem, if you really have money problems,
I can find ways to borrow money for you.
Don't put yourself at risk, okay?
Don't worry, bro.
I don't want to trouble you again.
Hey, Khem…
I charged the battery for you.
You have to go to the forests prepared
so we can stay in touch.
I love having someone to worry about me.
Don't complain if I call you too often.
If only I could bring you
as a spare battery.
When I'm tired,
I think of you, and I feel stronger.
I don't know where that energy comes from.
I want you near me so you can recharge me.
In that case,
I'll fully recharge you right now.
What? I haven't been home long.
I need more time to recharge.
I'm still tired. What should we do?
Can I charge my spare battery?
You don't have to see me off.
Save yourself the long trip.
This is far enough.
Look after yourself.
Don't work too hard, Dad.
Hang on.
It's so cute, Khim.
Hurry back, okay?
You take care, okay?
You take care too.
Bye.
You want to see Daddy off, do you?
Gla!
Gla, the baby's moving.
Why are so many cops around today?
Is there trouble again?
Maybe there's
another counterfeit goods raid.
Khem.
-Let's go that way.
-What? Aren't we going to the border?
I need to do something. Turn that way.
Okay.
Hey, man, stop right here.
You can go now.
Khem! Are you around here?
Hey, Khem!
-Khem!
-Bro!
-What are you doing here?
-What are you waiting for?
There are checkpoints everywhere.
Don't take the car!
This gun, it was in the car.
Stop! Freeze!
Run, Khem!
Bro…
Don't move! Put the weapon down!
What should we do?
Give me the gun.
Don't move!
Freeze!
Put the weapon down slowly.
Hey!
-Khem, get in the car!
-Okay!
-Hey!
-Hey, bro!
Hey!
Mr. Seen is staying in the area.
I heard that you were here, Miss Khim,
so I've come to bring you to him.
Does he really want me to see him?
I'm worried
that if he sees me,
he won't be able to cope.
How will we get away from them?
You wanna die in jail an old man?
Hey, what now, bro?
We have to leave the car.
Khem.
-Hey, here's our way out of this!
-Hey!
Gla! The cops!
-Stop!
-Stop! This is the police!
-Hey!
-Khem! Come on!
I'm coming, bro.
Stop!
Gla, hurry!
Come in. We need backup right now.
The suspects are fleeing by boat.
Move! Hurry!
Lock onto the target!
Hey! The cops!
Gla! The cops!
Turn, bro!
My family called.
Please stop here.
Uncle?
Is something wrong?
It's Gla. He didn't go to the border.
He's causing trouble again.
Please keep out. It's dangerous.
-Gla!
-I'm coming too.
-Don't enter.
Officers! My son is there!
-Sir, it's dangerous.
-Can I go in there?
No, ma'am. It's dangerous.
We've surrounded the suspects.
They won't get away.
We're doomed!
Surrender now!
-Be careful, Miss Khim.
-Keep out.
-Please let me in.
-No, it's too dangerous.
Fire!
Khem!
A suspect has been shot.
Gla.
Put your hands up!
You're not getting away!
Get on the boat!
Move! Hurry!
Uncle?
If they refuse to be taken alive,
we'll take them dead.
Khem!
Khem! Wake up!
Stop!
Don't you dare give up!
Put your hands up and surrender!
Khem!
Don't leave me like this!
Attention.
Our informant is dying.
Informant?
We just want Saikhim back,
and we want Gaogla
to admit that he abducted her.
Then we'll find ways to help you
with your vehicle fraud case.
Get Gaogla to surrender
and let the man have his daughter back
if you don't want a life sentence.
I'm sorry.
Listen! We've seized all the evidence!
The case against you is ironclad.
Give yourself up now!
How could you?
-Why did you do it?
-I didn't think it would end like this.
I'm sorry, bro.
Do not resist arrest or try to flee!
Why did you do it?
If I can't be good,
I'll just give up and be bad!
Let's go.
Out of our way, please.
Dad?
How are you?
What about Gla?
All our actions have consequences.
So, is Gla safe?
-I have to see him!
-Khim.
You have to stay here.
Listen.
Even if he survives,
he won't stay out of jail.
You as well.
He could drag you down with him
if you don't leave him.
Gla did nothing wrong, Dad.
He promised me
that he'd change for the better.
People who are used to living recklessly
promise to change their ways,
but do you know
what they're doing behind your back?
Here.
Take a look.
He threatened
to make this public.
And he said that your unborn baby
will not be his responsibility.
That's why he distanced himself from you.
That's not true.
-It's not true. I need to see him, Dad!
-Khim.
Khim, listen to me.
You don't even know him that well.
You don't love him. You never did.
It's just an infatuation.
That's not true.
-Khim.
-No!
-Gla!
-You don't love him. You're infatuated.
It's only infatuation. Trust me.
Trust me.
I won't let you go.
He must pay for what he did.
Dad.
Your assistant, Khem, is safe now.
What about Khim?
Her father took her away.
I've been framed.
They set me up to arrest me
so that he could take Khim back.
We seized this evidence.
You accepted this job.
You still saying you were set up?
Question him at the station.
-Hey!
-Gla!
-The suspect is escaping.
-Seal the exits now!
-Gla!
Stop!
Stop! Put down the scissors!
Put them down!
You did this, didn't you?
-Khim.
-Gla!
You framed me! Khim, don't listen to him!
I did nothing wrong.
You can't pin this on me!
They want us apart!
I promised Khim.
Why would I break my promise to her?
Don't mess with us!
-Stay out of this!
-Stop it!
Put the scissors down!
They used Khem to entrap me
then tried to kill him to shut him up!
Are you nuts?
Put your hands up and surrender!
Well, arrest him!
His people are the ones who hired me!
Or did he bribe you?
-Is that why you're doing nothing?
-Final warning.
Don't make us use excessive force!
Hey, please don't hurt him!
Khim.
Do you believe that I was framed?
One!
-I believe you.
-Two!
Then come back. Come to me!
Three!
-Don't shoot him!
-Khim, no!
Honey, he's using you!
I didn't do it.
I swear!
Don't you see he's holding her hostage?
Khim, do you trust me?
Please don't do this.
We'll figure it out together.
Okay?
What are you doing?
Why are you afraid?
Do you think I'd hurt you?
Gla!
-He'll kill my daughter!
-Mr. Seen, no!
-They're just talking!
-Gla!
Gla.
Please don't do this.
Do I seem that awful?
It hurts like I'm being stabbed
when you look at me like that.
Wanna know how much it hurts?
Gla.
-Please let go.
-Khim.
I'm begging you.
-Let go, Khim.
-Gla.
Gla, calm down.
Gla!
Don't do this.
-I'm scared, Gla.
-Let go, Khim.
-Gla, that's enough!
-Khim!
-Mr. Seen, no!
-Gla, calm down.
Gla, that's enough!
Don't!
Gloy!
-Gloy!
-It'll be okay, honey.
Officers! My daughter has been shot!
Who hurt my sister? Why did you shoot her?
-Gloy!
-Miss Khim!
Gloy!
-Gloy!
-Stop!
Why did you hurt her? Gloy!
-Gloy!
Let me go!
Why did you hurt her?
-Gloy!
-Hurry, sir!
Gloy!
You'll be okay, honey.
Am I bad enough for you now?
My only mistake was falling
for a woman like you!
She doesn't eat,
she doesn't sleep, and she doesn't speak.
If we let this go on,
her body won't be able to take it, sir.
The doctor said it's stress.
It's affecting her body.
If her mood improves,
everything will be fine.
She doesn't seem
like she'll be able to get over it.
If she stays like this until the birth,
she won't be able to get through it.
We have to help her somehow, sir.
I want my daughter back as she was.
Dad.
How is Gloy, Dad?
Still unconscious.
Stay strong.
I'll use the plantation deed
to get a loan to bail you out.
Dad, you haven't even asked me
if I really did it.
I raised you myself.
Of course I know what you're like.
Even if you did do it,
it wouldn't change
the fact that we are father and son.
No matter what you do,
I will always protect you.
Why are you so good to me, Dad?
I'm not even your real son.
Gloy is the one you should help.
You shouldn't be saddled with
a crappy son like me.
If you were bad,
they wouldn't hurt you like this.
They did it because you're good.
Much too good.
If no one loved you,
I would still love you,
and I'd always be there for you.
If anyone doesn't love you
for who you are,
maybe
it's not real love.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Gla.
Please don't do this.
Do I seem that awful?
He threatened to make this public.
And he said that your unborn baby
will not be his responsibility.
It hurts like I'm being stabbed
when you look at me like that.
Wanna know how much it hurts?
Gla!
Am I bad enough for you now?
My only mistake was falling
for a woman like you!
If you want to trust me with your life,
we must trust each other.
Then we'll both survive.
Hey!
Is it okay?
I'd like you to give me sole custody.
I can raise just one kid.
Could you show me
how you'll raise it?
If you can cope with raising it,
I'll give you sole custody.
Go on.
Bro.
I'm sorry
that I had to betray you.
Those bastards tricked me
into luring you out.
They told me
that if you gave them Saikhim back,
they'd make our case go away.
They just wanted revenge.
Maybe they even wanted to kill me.
You suffered because of me.
No, bro.
Bro, don't say that.
Just hit me, bro.
Come on, hit me, bro!
I deserve it for betraying you!
Bro!
Gla!
Just kick me, bro!
Kick me, bro!
You son of a bitch!
You want to go back
to the way we were, do you?
Khem!
Dad and Gloy have nothing to do with this.
Why did we burden them with this crap?
It's my damn fault, bro.
-What do you want me to do?
-They did nothing wrong.
We can't bring them into this crappy life.
Do you know how much
Dad and Gloy have suffered because of me?
How can I ever face them again now?
-How, Khem?
-Bro.
Is this all our lives will ever be?
SEVEN YEARS AGO
JUVENILE HALL
Hey!
Snobby, aren't you, new guy?
Go on!
Learn to respect your elders.
Arrogant, are you?
Hey! What the hell were you looking at?
You want more hazing?
Hey, assholes.
If you're hungry,
come get your asses kicked.
-Come on.
-Come here.
You piece of trash!
What the hell are you looking at?
Hey, it's happening!
Let's do this, you sons of bitches!
What the hell do you want?
Hey! If you're not eating it, I will!
If you're too proud today,
you'll starve for weeks
unless you flatter those bastards.
Hey, he's scoffing it down like a dog!
What a piece of crap!
You can be a snob
if you don't mind starving to death.
This is nothing
compared to what you'll face later.
If you want to be an asshole,
you have to be a crazy one like me
so everyone leaves you alone.
All right. Hangry now, are you?
I'll kick your ass!
Hey, dude!
Don't!
This is not what I meant!
Dude!
Hey, dude!
Never forget.
Being fed at all is a blessing.
We're juvenile delinquents.
Life won't get any better.
Don't ask for more than you deserve.
We nearly achieved something good.
Why?
Why do we keep getting stuck here?
I'm sorry, bro.
Gla.
Auntie Oon, please help my baby.
The doctor's here. Please don't worry.
Please don't worry.
Family members out, please.
You can wait outside, ma'am.
Saikhim, can you tell me where it hurts?
Can you point to where it hurts?
-Khim, how are you?
-Sir! Miss Khim's hemorrhaging.
The doctor said
it's a threatened miscarriage.
Her hormone levels
have dropped dramatically.
The only way to save the child is
to treat her with hormones.
How is she, Doctor?
The patient is still bleeding.
We can still see the baby's vital signs.
If we give her hormones,
we could save the baby--
What about its mother's life?
If she keeps bleeding, that's troubling.
It could lead to a secondary infection.
My daughter still has a future.
Doctor, keep her safe. Do what you must.
If we must choose,
I choose my daughter.
What about the baby?
Any parent would love their child.
At this point,
who could be more important than Saikhim?
But would Miss Khim consent?
Maybe this is the baby's fate.
Just do your best, Doctor.
If we really can't save it,
we'll have to accept that.
We have to salvage Saikhim's future.
And in ten years,
she'll be grateful she survived today.
Can I count on you, Doctor?
Yes, sir.
Did you know that when I was little,
I would pretend to be asleep
so that you'd pick me up
and take me to my bed?
But you never did that, not even once.
Forget picking me up.
You probably don't even want
to look at me anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's all right,
my good girl.
Following the arrest of suspects
in the car import tax fraud case
at the border several days ago,
the court found
the men had tried to evade capture
and had previously been involved
in an illegal car importation case.
Therefore, the court ordered
that the men be detained without bail.
The Department of Special Investigation
and the Customs Department will both…
Khim?
Are you awake?
How are you?
Khim, it's all over now.
You don't have to worry anymore.
That child
went to a better place.
Don't blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
You did your best, as any mom would do.
You see,
your dad was worried
you wouldn't be able to take the news,
so he asked me to come.
Now that you're awake,
I'll go and tell the nurse.
I'll be back.
Wait.
Lita, can you help me out?
I want to talk to Gla.
I don't want to believe
that he's lied to me this whole time.
Okay.
Khim is awake.
She says she's very hungry, Auntie Oon.
Really? I'm so glad to hear that.
-Then I'll go and order some food.
-Sure.
Saikhim is so lucky
to have such a nice friend.
Uncle Seen must be so generous
to let you keep seeing her.
Friends are our chosen family.
Have you never heard that?
But it's not so odd
that Khim would be closer to a friend
than to her own family.
Really? I thought you wanted to be
a member of our family.
I'm Cousin Prom.
Prom what?
Prompat, sweetie.
Auntie Oonruean, I'm going downstairs
to find something to eat.
Please go ahead.
I'll come too.
Want another bite?
Don't you want more?
Khim?
Are you full?
You're finished already?
Let me put that away.
Very well done. You nearly finished it.
-Yes.
-Let me put that away.
It's okay, Auntie Oon. I'll do it.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Shall we get some food?
Okay.
What are you doing?
It's the dinner menu.
Khim asked me to order something.
All right. Please go ahead.
INPATIENT FOOD MENU
I'm going to England with Khim.
You take care of business here.
Don't worry about work.
Worry about this.
My people at the jail told me
that a stranger visited Gaogla.
Uncle, can you guess who?
Hello, I'd like to visit
Mr. Gaogla Chayodom.
Please open your bag.
I knew that annoying girl would betray us.
I've brought news.
I don't think you'll like it.
Your baby is gone.
Is that good news or bad?
Khim wants to talk to you,
so she wrote you a letter.
She wants to hear the truth
from you and no one else.
I miscarried a few days ago.
I couldn't let it be born
to a father like you.
Since you brought us shame,
it's better that the baby not be born
to bear that shame.
I need to get my life back.
The time we've had,
consider it payment for the bad deeds
we committed in our past lives.
I don't want to sink any lower.
Now I know we're too different.
If you can still behave like a gentleman,
please sign our divorce papers.
I want a clean break.
After we sign the papers,
we can go our separate ways.
I'm not asking too much, am I?
I guess she wants to get rid of me fast.
Khim's worried about you.
She's worried I won't die!
Hey! I'm just the messenger.
Just write your reply.
Tell her to come here
if she wants a divorce.
I'm in jail because of her.
Why do I have to throw my life away here?
If she loved herself,
why would she resort to this?
She can go live where she wants.
But she can't just act
like my life means nothing!
What have you two done?
I gave you access to this home
so that Saikhim could vent to you.
But you betrayed me.
You tried to help them make up.
So this means yesterday's letter…
It was fake.
-Guard, show her in.
-This way, please.
GAOGLA
Tell her to come here
if she wants a divorce.
No wonder he mentioned a divorce.
You switched the letters.
You know very well
that he's not good enough for Saikhim!
Why would you help them rehash this?
Why did you do this?
If you really wanted the best for Saikhim,
you'd protect her
from that good-for-nothing man!
You're the only one
who knows all about Saikhim.
If you promise me
that you'll keep everything secret
and keep him out of Saikhim's life,
I promise
I'll pay for you
to study in England with her.
Yes, you're uncomfortable.
It's like betraying your friend.
But you know, deep down,
that he's not suitable for Saikhim at all.
Good friends want the best for each other.
Isn't that right?
Prove to me
that you're truly Saikhim's friend.
Have fun with your new life.
Here's a map and the keys. There.
I got this phone for you
as a surprise present.
Hey, I signed you up to a dating service
and picked five local guys for you.
Why is this happening to me?
I never should have let this happen, Lita.
-How could I let this happen?
-It's not your fault, Khim.
It's my fault.
I brought those men into your life.
You got her pregnant,
but that doesn't mean you own her.
What century are we in?
Don't use the baby
to bring her down to your level.
If I hadn't been careless,
you'd never have slept with her.
Remember this.
Never dare to touch
this forbidden fruit, ever.
If you promise me
you'll keep him out of Saikhim's life,
I promise
I'll pay for you
to study in England with her.
He said
he wants a divorce.
Really?
An actual divorce?
He said he doesn't wanna rehash things.
He doesn't care anymore.
He doesn't want to explain anymore.
No matter what you think of him,
he doesn't care anymore.
It all started because of me,
and it'll end with me.
No one wanted that child,
so it should all end here.
TRAISIT'S CASH ON WHEELS
TRADE YOUR CARS FOR CASH
-Let's go now.
-All right.
Hey, watch out!
Hey!
It's my fault
for thinking money didn't matter.
Counselor, who knows
if this money will help Gla's case?
And now I don't even have
enough money to fight this case.
Use this money to get Gla back.
The prosecutor found the money
that was transferred into this account.
That money
will be used to prove
that you've been part of this operation.
We won't be acquitted this time.
Following the arrest of suspects
in the car import tax fraud case
at the border several days ago,
the court found
that the men had tried to evade capture
and had previously been involved
in an illegal car importation case.
Therefore, the court ordered
that the men be detained without bail.
You father's selling the plantation
to fight this case for you.
He said this is the last-ditch attempt.
What's the point of helping me?
He should use that money
to save Gloy's life instead.
About the money, he said
he can make more while he's alive,
but he only has one son,
so he has to get you back.
I give up.
Let's not fight it anymore.
This last bit of money is more useful
for my little sister.
If Dad keeps doing this,
even if I repay him my whole life,
I don't know if it will ever be enough.
Dad, please stop trying to help me.
Since Mom's death,
you've suffered so much because of me.
From now on,
please let me do my duty as your son.
I want you to be comfortable,
to have everything you need,
and to hold your head up high.
Keep your plantation.
Don't waste it on this wayward son.
This money
is my way of paying my debt.
Use it to save Gloy.
Gloy!
Gloy, honey!
If she survives,
pay for her to go to good schools
so she'll get a degree.
You could buy a big new car.
All my life,
I've never made you proud.
This might be my last chance
to do something for you.
Who knows what will happen next?
If reincarnation is real,
I hope I get to be your son again.
Maybe then we'll truly be father and son.
I'll never love you less.
I'll only love you more every day.
What if you stopped loving me?
What would happen?
I won't stop loving you.
DELETE FILE
DELETING
Am I bad enough for you now?
My only mistake was falling
for a woman like you!
Hey! What's with all this noise?
Go to sleep! I told you to go to sleep!
Yes, sir.
Bro.
Look at that.
Who says jailbirds are useless?
At least those guys can earn money
for their families from here.
I've heard
that an order came in.
They can earn money by selling organs.
If your organ is a match,
they'll pay through the nose.
They don't care who you are.
Gla!
Gla.
Come back.
Gaogla has hanged himself in jail.
To run away from his problems?
I never thought he'd be such a coward.
It's like he knew
we've been arranging his divorce.
What's going on?
Did something happen to Gaogla?
What happened?
Dad, please just tell me.
What happened, Dad?
Dad, please tell me.
I'm begging you. I want to know.
Please, Dad? Please just tell me.
He attempted suicide
in jail.
His condition is serious.
We don't know if he'll live.
How did it end up like this?
I…
-I have to see him.
-Khim.
-Miss Khim.
-You can't go anywhere.
-Don't.
-No.
-Listen to me, honey.
Khim.
Listen, honey.
You must forget him.
You have to forget him!
Even better, act like you never knew him.
Start living your life again.
Dad.
We're going to move him
to scan his brain, sir.
We have the results now.
They are a match.
Our doctor is prepping the operating room
for the kidney transplant.
They found this contract in the jail.
Someone smuggled it to us.
What does this mean?
Your son has chosen
to give his organs to these traffickers
and will receive something in return.
But that's illegal.
I don't understand
this crazy situation either.
That's a person's whole life.
They can't just trade it!
I hope he'll survive.
But if he doesn't,
you should think about it.
Would you let him die for nothing?
We're going to move him
to scan his brain, sir.
They were going to scan his brain.
Gla!
Where is he going?
What are you doing here?
He's my husband's illegitimate son.
So it's you.
You followed us.
You can't take him anywhere.
You hid him away for decades
and couldn't take good care of him!
I'm taking him!
But he's still alive.
He could still wake up.
I'm not going to kill him!
I just want him
to help save my son's life!
Well, he's my son too.
Do you have any morals?
He wasn't born
to be someone's spare parts.
No matter how bad life is,
he has the right to live.
All of us
have one life each.
Your money can't dictate
someone else's life.
He will never wake up
because his wife
has already prepared
his treatment refusal forms.
If anything happens,
he'll be left to wait to die.
No one can save him.
Those people are the ones
who are going to kill him.
I will not lose this chance
because without him,
my son will not live.
If someone has to die,
someone else should at least get to live.
It's better than both of them dying.
That's Nate, my son.
He had a mountain climbing accident.
He never regained consciousness.
We used equipment to support him
and brought him here
to buy time and wait for a miracle.
To me, your son is that miracle
because three days ago,
Nate had kidney failure.
Tissue forceps, please.
Your son is in great danger.
You really think he'll survive?
How many days will Gla buy him, huh?
I'll buy as many days as I can
because Nate grew up
with this deadly condition
and he's survived this long.
He needs a liver today.
Maybe tomorrow it'll be a lung or a heart.
Let me tell you something.
Gla
is a miracle to me too.
He tried to kill himself,
meaning he didn't want
to donate just his kidney.
He wanted to save his sister's life
by giving his own in exchange.
That's the kind of heart
that deserves to be loved,
not destroyed.
That miracle of yours
is his heart!
He has had to live in the shadows
to hide from a father
who doesn't treat him like a human.
He got arrested after being bullied
for not being my own son.
We've ruined their childhood
by making them face grown-up problems.
We've acted like we own them.
From the cradle to the grave,
we've never let them live their own lives,
and now we're even taking their lives.
How could you do this to him?
I'm begging you.
Please give Gla's life back to me.
-Blood pressure drop.
-How much?
Fifty over seventy, Doctor.
Prep one unit of blood, stat.
Attention.
The following flight has been suspended…
Start CPR.
-Now!
-Yes, Doctor.
-Any increase?
-Heart rate dropping.
Khim, what's wrong?
Gla!
Don't die!
I gotta go.
Gla!
Stay strong!
Don't die, Gla!
I won't stop loving you.
If I stopped loving you,
it'd be because I'd died.
Gla!
Khim, what's wrong?
Because love is fragile…
only love can heal love.
When we have to say goodbye…
You can only hope that…
we'll still dare to love again.
Hey, Tan.
Dry your hair first, oppa,
then dry yourself all over.
He's in the past now.
Even if he had lived,
you're way out of his league.
Anyway, now,
you're in a serious relationship.
Marry me.
Do you know someone in heaven, miss?
You can send them a letter.
I don't know if he's still up there.
It's been seven years.
Miss Khim hasn't called yet.
She must be on the island.
Why did you let her go alone?
I'll follow you there.
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit