THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
The cops accused me
of luring and assaulting you.
So you came here to harass me?
Hey!
Are you an informant?
I just want to say
that you owe me your life.
If I hadn't saved you,
you might have died by now.
No man would be interested in you
if you didn't have my fortune!
I think I'm pregnant.
What?
Let's end things here.
It's not worth it for either of us.
Just pretend
that we've never met.
Let's not ruin our lives more.
Try starting it, sir.
Okay.
All done, sir.
Call me if you need anything else.
-Thanks so much.
-No problem.
You can wait here. I won't be long.
This is Gaogla.
This is Lita.
Don't let them near Miss Khim.
Hello, I'm Annie, or the Guzheng Angel.
Today, I'm so delighted
because we're going to participate
in a wonderful activity here.
It's called Blind Date.
It's all about blind people
and partially-sighted people.
I, too, am a partially-sighted person.
We would like everyone here
to understand the feelings
and the difficulties
that we experience in our daily lives.
Did you bring it?
In here.
Ms. Lita?
May I help you?
Let's put this on.
-Your ID card.
-Thank you.
-Find your seat and put this eye mask on.
-All right.
Please go ahead.
We'd like you all
to take part in this event…
-That way.
-Thank you.
…and try living
like a visually-impaired person for a day.
Let's find out what it'd be like
for you all to be in the dark
and to walk around in the dark.
What good impressions
will you bring home from this event today?
All right.
Today, what we'll do is
try doing some shopping.
Have you wondered how we
visually-impaired people navigate malls?
Apart from walking around the mall,
today, we will also bring you…
Sir, your eye mask.
-Put it on when you sit down.
-Okay.
…buy your fruit and vegetables,
and go to eat some food.
The most exciting part is
we will go walking up the escalators.
Doesn't that sound exciting?
All right, if you're ready,
let's go ahead
and start doing our activities.
Everyone, find a partner.
-What?
-Go ahead, miss.
-Khim?
-Hey.
-Khim.
-Wait.
Lita.
Saikhim.
Go ahead, miss.
How did you know I'm a woman?
I can smell your perfume.
This way, please.
All right.
Good. Now, walk forward.
-Go ahead.
-Okay, let's begin.
Follow each other.
I can't keep up.
Khim? Saikhim?
-Then please wait downstairs.
-It's okay.
We'll catch up with you.
Let's go.
I… I'd better not risk it.
Don't be afraid.
Follow me.
It's not so dangerous.
I'll tell you when to step up.
Got it?
Up.
We'll make it, right?
We have to.
If we trust each other,
it won't be so hard.
Trust me with your life.
Take a step.
In our next activity,
we'll try putting a top
on our partner without looking.
People aren't always
what they appear to be.
If we don't look at them,
we won't judge them
by their outward appearance.
More importantly, we might even understand
who they really are much better.
Let's find out
who everyone is and learn more about them.
All right, try getting to know
the person in front of you.
You can touch them and ask them questions.
Try and guess
who they are and where they're from.
Try it out.
So I guess I'll go first.
Sure.
I think
you must work very hard
because
you have the hands
of someone who works all the time.
You can say they're rough.
I don't mind.
Not everyone is born rich like you.
Who's rich?
Give me your hands.
Your hands are soft like a rich kid's.
I guess you've never washed
any dishes in your whole life.
It's like you grew up in
Disneyland or something.
Disneyland?
I think
you're definitely single.
-Why?
-Well…
You're not wearing any rings.
And you have a very blunt way of speaking.
I guess you don't talk to women very much.
I think you'll end up single too.
Why?
Disney princesses would never dare
to drink so greedily in front of men.
Don't do that again anywhere.
-It's rude.
-Here's your order.
Let's figure out
how to eat this food
while we can't see it.
First, try to find your utensils.
Your knives and forks.
To check which is the knife
and which is the fork,
try touching one with the other.
Once you're sure, take the fork
and pierce your food,
then use your fork to slice your food.
Use your fork
to figure out what's on your plate
and where on the plate it is.
Is someone ill?
Khim, are you okay? Do you need help?
-Are you okay?
-I gotta go now.
…let's continue.
Khim, you have morning sickness?
Oh no. My symptoms are so obvious.
I guess I can't hide it much longer, Lita.
I've done some research.
Most people use this drug
to deal with the problem.
Maybe…
it will help us put an end to this.
Will it really end, Lita?
I'm being watched 24 hours a day.
I'm worried
that my family will suspect me.
Let's try something.
Why don't you go back
to England as a cover?
I can't.
If I went back,
Auntie Oon would have to come with me.
I don't think I can hide this from her.
There must be a way. I'll think of one.
It's okay, Khim.
I'll find a way to help you.
Hey, they're our photos from earlier.
But that's…
That guy.
Hey, did he come here just to harass you?
Why has he followed you everywhere?
What's this?
PAY MR. GAOGLA CHAYODOM FIVE MILLION BAHT
What's that for?
This is bad.
Hey.
It's that bastard.
Why is he here?
Looking for trouble?
He dared to come to my turf.
He will regret it.
For real?
Excuse me, we've received reports
of someone invading the ladies' room.
What's that got to do with me?
You can't just accuse anyone.
A victim reported it, sir.
May I search you, please?
Go ahead.
Hey!
Come in. Do you copy?
I've found the item on the suspect.
Don't make the framing so obvious.
It's that guy.
The sneaky thief.
Let's teach him a lesson
so that he doesn't come back.
Maybe another charge would do the trick.
We can't have ex-cons
strutting around here, Guard.
Remember his face.
With a face like that,
he should have stayed in prison.
-Hey!
Calm down.
Take him away.
Come on, sir.
I won't go to prison alone.
Will you confess
that you stole this gold jewelry?
Petty larceny like this is not much fun.
Wouldn't you rather I stole billions?
That's nonsense.
You really don't wanna know
why I was there?
If I gave you information
about counterfeit cars,
would you help me
reach a settlement, Officer?
That car was imported without paying tax.
They added fake Thai license plates.
Those rich people drive nice cars,
but they're breaking laws.
Each car is worth
tens of millions in taxes.
Just think about it.
How much has this gang alone stolen?
Maybe tens of millions.
You can't know someone
just by looking at them.
You have to dig deeper.
It's just like those fancy cars.
They look good on the outside.
But the outside is just a facade.
Maybe they're just as fake as the drivers.
Without legit-looking plates,
even the most beautiful cars are
just pieces of junk.
People are the same.
You can be born rich
and still be worthless.
Miss Khim, can I help you?
Where's Dad?
He went to Chiang Mai for a meeting.
Is it urgent, miss?
He'll be back tomorrow.
Don't worry about it.
We need to examine the car again
to see if the vehicle ID code is fake.
I'm just a customer.
How would I know
the dealer sold me a fake?
We need to finish examining it.
Then we need
another testimony, Mr. Prompat.
Please excuse us.
Let's go.
How could you have been so careless?
You couldn't even buy one car properly?
Someone must have tricked Khimhan and me.
Don't involve the company,
or you'll pay the price.
Pretend you know nothing.
And convince the police
that you were tricked by Khimhan.
Following further inquiries by the DSI,
dozens of luxury cars
of the rich and famous
have been seized for examination.
The investigation has targeted
imported luxury cars
sold by the showrooms
of Khimhan Dechachan,
the famous car showroom owner.
So far, the investigation has found
that the state has lost
a total of 300 million baht in taxes
thanks to 25 of the cars
in this tax evasion scam.
Next, the investigators
will examine luxury cars
that have been imported
via customs houses.
This is Saifon Tongsamud reporting.
Revenge on that family
turned into an inquisition
of their whole circle.
You went too far.
Will it come back to hurt us?
The cops got the cars.
But with no Electric Control Units,
they're basically rickshaws.
They wouldn't dare hurt us
if they knew we did their cars.
But if they try to hit us back,
we'll keep the ECUs.
Their cars will only ever be scrap metal.
Good, right?
Oops.
I'm sorry.
Don't mind me. I'm done here.
Prom didn't mean to cause trouble
for our family, you know?
Please don't take offense.
If you feel
that Prom has any room for improvement
and you'd like to teach him
how to be a better man,
I would welcome that.
Besides,
we are both single parents,
so wouldn't it be better
if we worked together to be his parents?
You should look after your own kids.
Khim causes enough trouble for me.
Excuse me.
Dad?
It's good that you're here.
I need to talk to you.
Oops.
Sorry, sweetie.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I'm a big girl now.
I would understand
if you were seeing someone.
You don't have to hide her from me.
I'm not a little girl.
You've been around the block now.
Nothing can shock you now.
Gaogla
has gave the check back.
Maybe he never planned to blackmail me.
You tried to buy him off.
You disrespected both him and me.
Don't you understand?
He gave the check back
to make himself look like a gentleman.
You still can't see that?
I'm not so boy crazy
that I can't tell right from wrong.
Every problem I've caused,
I'm ready to take responsibility
for them myself.
I'll never bring shame on you again.
I promise.
PAY MR. GAOGLA CHAYODOM
Gaogla.
Auntie Oonruean?
It's me.
-What is it?
-I need your help with something.
A magazine wants to do
a photo shoot with me and Tan.
But Tan refuses to do it.
Can you ask him what he's so afraid of?
I guess Tan has his own reasons.
Are you refusing to ask him
because… you're jealous?
You want to keep him
as a friend with benefits?
Tan and I aren't dating each other.
So I guess if I started dating Tan,
you'd be okay with that?
Of course that's okay.
That's great to hear.
Now I can tell Tan not to worry about it
because you gave us your blessing.
Miss Khim?
Hello, Miss Khim?
Yes?
It's nice to have a heart-to-heart
as cousins once in a while, isn't it?
I've set the table, miss.
Your father is waiting.0
When you're the only daughter,
your dad watches you like a hawk.
He watches your every move.
You should go. Don't keep him waiting.
Yes, Auntie Oon.
She has spread her wings out there.
She won't be put back
in her gilded cage again.
Reset your expectations.
She is disobedient.
You can't call her back.
Did I keep you waiting?
Sorry I'm just a bit late.
I'll see a hotel group
in New York next week.
What about me, Uncle?
Stay here and deal with your car.
Your classes resume next month, right?
Is it such a good idea to have her
studying somewhere so far away?
Why do you ask?
She's in a Top Five university.
She can't throw that away.
But I don't want to go back yet.
You've been home for over a month.
Maybe studying is not a priority.
Studying is so stressful.
Maybe if you find a…
…that would be better.
She's not like you, Prim.
Come on, Prom.
I'm not stupid enough to debase myself
by letting any random man have me.
Return to England immediately.
End of discussion.
Pregnant?
Well, I saw the pregnancy test in her room
with my very own eyes.
Uncle Seen is too biased towards her
to see the ugly truth.
He probably doesn't know
what a degenerate she has become.
I should've embarrassed them more
so he'd stop looking down on me.
If she's pregnant,
how can she cope
with going back to university?
Mom, this isn't something
you can just hide.
And who can tell
if her dear old Auntie Oonruean
knows and is protecting her?
I think if she knew,
she'd help her hide it.
Maybe she'd even take advantage
of Seen's absences
to dispose of all the evidence.
We can't let all this
just go away quietly.
This shock could kill Uncle Seen.
Now his own daughter is
such a delinquent,
let's see if Uncle Seen
would dare to look down on me anymore.
Return to England immediately.
End of discussion.
If we trust each other,
it won't be so hard.
Trust me with your life.
Hey, Khem,
pass me the wrench.
I asked for the wrench,
not the screwdriver.
What are you doing, Khem?
When you said…
"If we trust each other,
it won't be so hard."
"Trust me with your life,"
did you mean that,
or was it just something cool to say?
I'm a man of my word. I meant what I said.
I gave the check back to my dad.
Why did you run away?
You should have stayed to talk.
Well, you said you wanted to end it.
You didn't want me to come see you.
Let's end things here.
It's not worth it for either of us.
Just pretend that we've never met.
Let's not ruin our lives more.
Actually,
we're virtually strangers.
Tie them properly, or you'll trip.
If you're going to be so nice to me,
I could cause more trouble for you.
Would you be mad at me
if I told you…
that I'm pregnant?
What?
You're pregnant?
Do you… do you think I'm lying?
No.
I knew it would turn out like this.
I shouldn't have told you.
Wait. Hey.
Come on. Wait.
Are you very mad at me?
Mad at you? For what?
I should apologize to you.
Actually, you can insult me,
or slap me, or whatever you want.
Come on, slap me really hard. Go on.
No.
It wasn't your fault.
I have to go back to university.
I can't let… this incident derail my life.
You mean
you're not keeping the baby?
If we don't do this,
my dad could kill me or you.
We'll eliminate the problem.
We can't let anyone else
suffer because of us.
This may be the only way.
Can you please tell me
how I should begin?
Begin by trusting each other,
and we can get through anything.
Are you leaving now?
Yeah.
What is it?
Well,
I'd like to go back to England sooner.
I thought I'd go back this weekend.
What happened? Didn't you want to stay?
While your dad's away,
you should pretend you're flying back.
Well… I want to get back
to continue my project.
I feel like I can't focus while I'm here.
Then you can run away with me.
I'll take you to a clinic.
When you feel better,
you can fly back to England.
Go ahead.
If you weren't in a hurry,
I'd have flown back with you.
Since you're already here, Auntie Oon,
I'd like you to spend as much time
with your family as possible.
You must have missed each other.
Besides, you'll have to go back to England
and stay with me for a long time.
I spend time with you
not only because it's my duty,
but also because I raised you,
so I love you in my own way.
When someone hurts you,
they hurt me even more.
Don't talk as if you were
a stranger to me.
You're just like one of my own children.
The first step is complete.
You look so happy using your phone.
Either you won the lottery,
or you found a woman.
You're too interested
in other people's lives.
Which rich person
are you getting into bed now?
"If you still can't tell sex from love,
you won't find
true love in this life," Gaogla.
If you're not careful,
you'll go to prison.
-Damn you, Khem.
-Hey, bro, relax.
Hey, relax, bro.
There's that smile.
-Khem!
-Okay, bye.
Please call me when you get there.
Yes, Auntie.
Take her to the check-in desk.
Yes, ma'am.
That's not necessary.
-What? Why?
-Wait. I can do it myself.
-Really?
-Really, Auntie.
My dear.
I have to go.
Remember. Don't forget to call me.
Sure.
What's wrong?
Is this right?
You came this far to hesitate now?
I feel like
I'm betraying my family.
I'm a brat just like my dad said I was.
If you turn back now,
will everything get better?
We've all made mistakes.
And when we behave badly,
we really want our parents
to understand us.
But each of our mistakes
could make us impossible to love.
So we can't let them know what we did
if we still want them to truly love us.
We're not running from our problem.
We're just solving it.
In three days,
you'll be a good girl just like before.
Once it's solved,
we never have to meet again.
Your future is the top priority.
Stay here today.
The garage is busy.
I don't want anyone to know about us.
The clinic will see you tomorrow.
We'll go together.
Are you okay on your own?
Should I stay?
See you tomorrow.
Why are you so scared?
Call me if you need help.
The garage is close by.
Hey, Khem.
What happened?
Someone messed with us.
Maybe it's that showroom owner.
He trashed the place.
He must've been after something.
Is anything missing?
Where are the ECUs?
Hey, don't bother.
Luckily, I thought ahead.
I hid them in your house already.
What? In my house?
Yeah. I'll go and check on them.
Hey, don't worry.
I'll check on them.
You clean up here.
SAIKHIM
What is it?
What?
It was like this when I got here.
Were you burgled?
What are those?
What's in there?
What they wanted to steal.
You troublemaker.
You had the nerve to snitch to the cops
while you took money from my peers and me.
You shouldn't have flown
so close to the sun.
You even ran off with Saikhim.
-What do you mean?
-Saikhim isn't on the plane.
You deceived my cousin.
You thought you'd outsmart me?
You took my cousin
so that you could get rich faster, right?
What do you want?
Give me back my car's ECU,
or I'll tell my uncle
that Sakhim ran off with you.
Hey, or maybe you do want me to tell him.
You are marrying
into our rich family anyway.
When do you want it?
By the end of the day.
An ECU for a billion-baht heiress.
Totally worth it, right?
Take your ECU back
and don't snitch.
With a scandal like this,
even if I said nothing,
you'd still get caught one day.
I don't understand what she sees in you.
Why is Saikhim so into you?
See you tonight, and do keep your promise.
What's happening?
Don't ask now.
You can't stay here today.
Take your stuff and go now.
Come on.
-Where are we going?
-It's not safe here.
What's in that bag?
The tools of my profession.
Don't ask now. Let's go.
I'm not going.
What exactly is your job?
You're not an auto mechanic?
How is that relevant?
Well, you've been in prison, right?
What's happening,
is it connected to that?
I'm not going to kill you.
I just want to know
how much I can trust you.
Why are you paranoid now?
Well, I don't know who you really are.
You're good one minute and bad the next.
That doesn't matter.
At least I wouldn't kill my unborn child.
I just meant
that I'm not a murderer or whatever.
So you… aren't helping me willingly.
Let's just go.
Or you can wait for your cousin
to pick you up here.
He knows we're together.
Luckily, though he knows we ran away,
he doesn't know about our baby.
So I'm playing for time.
We'll deal with the kid,
then you'll have a clean slate again.
Come on.
Khim?
What's going on?
You abducted her, did you?
Lita.
I lied to my family,
and we ran off together.
What?
We're solving the problem.
So now you're a gentleman?
He promised
to help me solve the problem with the baby
while Dad's overseas.
Can I leave Khim with you for now?
Of course.
Who'd leave her with you, sex addict?
Khim.
But if you stay here,
your dad will find you
because his foundation knows
that I'm living here.
Ms. Ji-Yeon!
-Hello.
Come here.
-So cute. Mom?
-Yeah?
Can my friend stay tonight?
Hey, you have normal friends like these?
Mom, what did you expect?
Your friend is so pretty.
Hey, she's absolutely gorgeous.
Please come in.
Come on, you can come in.
Sweetie, you're like a doll.
All right. My mom is renting this house.
They won't look for you here.
Well?
Go on.
Are you sure he's not your boyfriend?
Mom! What a silly question.
Look at his face. I can't stand it.
Isn't he the one
who stares at your boobs
while you're talking?
-Mom!
-What did I say?
Hush.
Stop talking. Don't.
Mom!
What a nice body.
You've been so helpful with her bags.
Hey, serious question.
Do you have feelings for Lita?
Mom!
Stop matchmaking. Do you even know him?
Do you know his family?
No, I don't know.
I do know that he drove you girls here.
He didn't let you come alone
so late at night.
Well, that sounds like a gent to me.
He's treating you so nicely.
If he didn't like you,
he wouldn't drive you home.
So tell me,
are you single?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Yeah, right. He already has a kid.
Well, you don't waste time either, do you?
I'm a single parent of an only child too.
Well, it's not so bad, is it?
Hey.
Do you really want
to help Khim with her problem?
If I didn't, would I do all this?
Are you still being so nice
so that you can pursue her
until she falls for you?
I warn you, my friend is not easy.
Don't use the baby
as an excuse to make her stay with you.
Make her stay?
You got her pregnant,
but that doesn't mean you own her.
What century are we in?
Don't use the baby
to bring her down to your level.
If I hadn't been careless,
you'd never have slept with her.
Remember this.
Never dare to touch
this forbidden fruit, ever.
I know.
I'm just paying for my sins
for this life
and for the next one as well.
Start counting down. It won't be long now.
So we're even.
I get my stuff back. You get my cousin.
No one must know about this.
You're not much of a gangster.
Own your mistakes, won't you?
In just a few days, Saikhim will go home.
Used cars depreciate.
She's a used person.
How damaged will she be?
Who knows if my uncle
will still want his daughter back?
If you don't keep your promise,
another charge might come your way.
Even if I say nothing,
it doesn't mean he won't know.
You watch yourself too.
My uncle won't let you get away with it.
So this is all for that girl?
You sabotaged your career,
and you could go to prison.
How much more
will this woman ruin your life?
Khem.
I wonder where Miss Khim is now.
I've asked a friend
who works with the airline to check.
They said Khim never got on the flight.
They asked Immigration, and they said
that she's in still Thailand.
Is it possible
that Saikhim ran off with her lover?
When Prom found out,
he tried looking for more answers.
So what should we do now?
This must mean
that Khim really loves this person.
That's why she lied to us over and over.
My goodness, Khim.
She shouldn't care about him
more than about her dad.
I didn't know
whether I should tell everyone this.
Earlier,
I… happened to see that Khim had bought
a pregnancy test for herself.
I don't know if that was related to this.
I think
we should wait for updates from Prom.
I hope Uncle won't forgive Khim this time.
If they're already having a baby together,
I doubt Seen could cope with that.
He loves her and wants to protect her
more than he does anything else.
Since Saikhim is a reminder
that Rarin left behind,
Seen probably won't be able to bear it
if he lost another person he loved.
Well, Auntie Rarin has been dead
for ten years already.
Why isn't he over her yet?
Well, she didn't die of natural causes.
She killed herself.
-What?
-What? She killed herself, Mom?
I thought she…
she was ill.
Back then, you two were little.
No one wanted you to know about it.
Saikhim's mother was obsessed
with a photographer.
She had him take nude photos of her.
When they were leaked,
the scandal lasted for some time.
That's why Seen couldn't deal with it,
and they never reconciled.
Rarin ended her life
to run away from the problem.
I thought it was just an ordinary affair.
I never thought it was that toxic.
It's no wonder.
That's why he's not over it.
That's why he's overprotective.
Seen can't stand betrayal.
Since it happened,
he refused to let Rarin touch Saikhim.
Rarin felt so hurt
that she overdosed on pills.
When Saikhim ran away with her lover,
Seen felt she was slipping away from him.
He couldn't stand seeing her
loving someone else rather than him.
If Khim knew about this,
she wouldn't dare come home to face him.
She was stupid to get fooled.
She brought this on herself.
Maybe this scandal
could rip this father and daughter apart
once and for all.
It must break his heart
to see her run off with a man.
Uncle Seen is unlucky.
The women in his life are all degenerates.
Well, who could stand
such a heartless person?
This is great.
Now he'll see the good in you,
Prim and Prom.
I was just tidying Miss Khim's room.
I never knew that Miss Khim
was hiding these things.
It's been over a month since that day.
I'm so worried.
I'm afraid…
This scumbag wants to use this kid
to manipulate Saikhim.
And if it turns out to be true,
what should we do?
Why are you paranoid now?
Well, I don't know who you really are.
You're good one minute and bad the next.
That doesn't matter.
At least I wouldn't kill my unborn child.
You got her pregnant,
but that doesn't mean you own her.
What century are we in?
Don't use the baby
to bring her down to your level.
If I hadn't been careless,
you'd never have slept with her.
Remember this.
Never dare to touch
this forbidden fruit, ever.
No matter how much
I want to take care of you and the baby,
I guess I'm too worthless
for you to throw your life away for.
Right?
SAJEE'S HAIR AND BEAUTY SALON
That feels so nice, Mom.
It feels so nice, doesn't it?
Now I understand why men fall for you.
You have the hands of an angel.
You can slay evil spirits.
I don't have to worry about you.
Actually, I have some other special moves.
Like what, Mom?
I don't like where this song is going.
No. Enough. Please stop.
-So much fun.
-Hey, Mom.
-What?
-My friend is up.
You're awake, dear? Are you hungry?
I'll make you some breakfast.
How about you?
-I'm hungry.
-You're hungry?
I'll do the best I can.
Hey, tell me what you want.
-You're the best.
-Tell me.
Let's take a shower and brush our teeth.
So having a mom
is nice like this.
When a student has a baby,
they grow up together like this.
She's a former teen mom.
If my mom had been
a deep thinker like you,
I wouldn't be here.
She didn't think hard enough,
so now you're all stuck with me.
My goodness.
I thought you'd flake out.
I'm not holding on.
Hey, did you actually sleep in your car
to watch over Saikhim?
Is Khim awake?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
You took the pill?
Did you? What did you take?
Spit it out.
Come on, spit it out.
What are you doing?
It's candy?
Of course it is.
I didn't know. I thought
you got impatient and took that pill.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
You didn't mean it?
But you kissed Khim so deeply.
-Khim?
Hey.
Where did that kiss come from?
-Khim. Hey!
-Stop, you psycho!
-Hey!
-Get out!
-Khim!
-My goodness. Do this.
-Mom, it's too short.
-Hey!
-Yeah!
Mom, go all out.
-Get out!
-Yeah!
This is crazy.
How dare he do that?
He should have asked.
What have I done?
Damn it.
For goodness' sake.
How can I face her now?
LITA
Who are you,
and what right have you to invade my home?
Just go away right now.
GAOGLA
I'm looking for Miss Saikhim.
Saikhim?
Why would she be here?
Miss Khim ran away from home yesterday.
May we search your property?
You may not!
We both told you that she's not here,
so you've no right to search here.
Her father's very worried about her.
If there's evidence
that she contacted you,
it could make it easier
for us to find her.
How could the two of us
know where Saikhim went?
If you search our home,
and you damage our possessions,
you have to take care of the damages.
Where is Saikhim?
How should I know?
I know you took her away with you.
Can you afford to keep her happy?
Is that why you took her from me?
Let me ask you this.
If you made her so happy,
why would she run from you?
Leave my daughter alone.
Don't use this baby to manipulate her.
You can't even survive on your own.
How can you look after a woman?
I admit that I don't have
the resources you do.
Although I can't afford a gilded cage,
I can give her the sky.
You should think about it.
Between a gilded cage and the sky,
which would a bird rather have?
Even if I had nothing but my body,
you still couldn't beat me
because you never let her be free,
so she flies back to me, the scumbag.
Call the cops, honey. Call them.
Hey!
-Hey!
-You can't go up there, sir!
Don't go there.
-No one's there.
-Get out now!
You can't go up there.
You can't go there without permission.
That's so rude. It's my home.
I told you you can't do this!
Don't open it!
You're not allowed to open it!
-Don't open it, sir!
-Don't!
Close it now.
See? There's nothing there.
Only panties hung out to dry. Your loss.
-Satisfied?
-Yeah.
-We said there was nothing.
-Hey, we said there was nothing up there!
-We said there was nothing there!
-Mr. Sansern!
-There's nothing up there.
Don't go inside.
It's our home.
You don't have our permission.
How dare you? Who do you think you are?
How dare you disrespect the law?
If Miss Saikhim isn't here,
you don't need to worry.
If you really are her friends,
you should cooperate
so I can find her sooner.
Such a rude attitude.
No wonder she can't stand you.
It's good that she ran away.
Mr. Sansern!
Gaogla.
Get back inside!
Someone's there.
Stay still!
See? There's nothing there.
Mr. Sansern.
We told you there was nothing there.
See? For goodness' sake.
So much walking around for nothing.
We told you there was nothing.
-There's nothing there.
-They're still searching.
-You searched already.
-We said there was nothing!
-You searched there already.
-Yeah.
Stay still, okay?
Hand me the bag.
We said there was nothing.
Why won't you believe us? Damn.
Has Gaogla been in contact?
Gaogla?
Who's that?
He tricked Miss Khim into running away.
This is the second time.
So you know they ran off together.
But why are you searching here?
Your daughter may have helped them.
Such strange ideas
tend to come from your daughter.
Really?
But I really have no idea this time, Mom.
I swear.
Stay calm. Don't be afraid.
Carefully take a step.
Give me your hand.
Look over here.
Move slowly.
Count to three, then take a step.
One. Two. Three.
We're done. There's nothing there.
-Told you.
-Unbelievable.
And these clothes?
We didn't find those.
Mom, we've had no clients yet today.
That's awful. In that case,
since you kept my clients away,
why don't you try a facial massage?
-Would you like a facial massage?
-No.
-Where are my clients? Take this.
-That's enough.
-Take this.
-Hey. Wait.
That's enough.
Here you go.
Compensation for reduced foot traffic.
If you hear of those two, call me.
That's all?
You don't want it?
Hey, wait. I'll take it. Jeez.
All right, who wants a facial massage?
Another facial massage?
Yes? Facial massage?
Thanks for your business.
That was close.
Gently.
Are you okay?
If you want to trust me with your life,
we must trust each other.
Then we'll both survive.
All three of us.
It'll survive, right?
That's up to you
whether it stays or goes.
But with me, it will be safe.
Are you sure?
Of course.
I got killed at sea, but I'm still alive.
-Come on.
-Don't be silly.
Actually, I'm helping you
avoid getting arrested.
If I'd died that day,
where would you be today?
Well, I guess
I'd be hanging over there,
or maybe
lying still down there.
If all three of us survive,
can I ask you something?
What is it?
I'd ilke…
Hey!
Are you okay?
Is it okay?
Watch out!
The doctor says the X-ray results are in,
and the patient is safe.
There are only cuts and bruises.
We'll treat the wounds,
then he can go home.
Thank you.
Since we met,
I've gotten you hurt so many times.
I've ruined your life too.
Your dad must know about the baby by now.
It's time to go to the clinic.
We should go now.
It managed to survive.
We can't kill it now.
It's not just the baby's life.
Your life is important too.
I'm worried about your future too.
As for me, I have nothing to lose.
Just before our accident,
you wanted to ask me something.
If all three of us survive,
can I ask you something?
What is it?
What did you want to ask?
How can I repay you?
I'd like you to give me sole custody.
I can handle one kid.
But I know it's impossible.
Ruining your life to have the baby
is too much to ask.
Eight or nine months
aren't worth the sacrifice, right?
But with me, it will be safe.
Is it okay?
Watch out!
Come on.
Wait.
Could you… show me…
how you'll raise it?
If you can cope with raising it,
I'll give you sole custody.
Are you sure you'll keep the baby?
Honestly, I think this guy is useless.
Shouldn't we regroup here
and figure it out together?
Thanks for caring about me, Lita.
But I can take care of myself.
Khim.
Your life isn't over yet.
Come back, and we'll figure it out.
We might find a better solution.
We can't go back and fix things anyway.
I'd rather move forward
even if there's an abyss in front of me.
I never thought a rich kid like her
would agree to try her luck
with me when I've no future.
No matter how smart you are,
anyone can make mistakes.
I admit that I messed up
because of something stupid.
You asked me how I would raise the kid.
This is how.
I'll raise it where I grew up.
Don't worry. It won't turn out like me.
I promise, I can take good care of it.
I'll show the kid
how lucky we all are to be alive.
At least it will have an awesome life.
It will be a life worth living.
And it won't starve
like when it's with you.
No. Actually, I'm not that hungry.
Stop acting tough.
We've come too far to be embarrassed now.
You act like we're strangers.
Since when have we been close friends?
You're so closed off.
We're distant friends.
Am I distant enough now?
Distant enough for you?
How about now?
Because of her,
I want to be a good person again.
I think Gaogla is using that kid
to manipulate Khim
to defy us, actually, Uncle.
Did you abduct her?
Who do you think I am, Dad?
You're hotheaded and impatient.
You good-for-nothing.
What have you ever done right?
-What are you doing here?
-Dad, enough.
-Dad!
-You…
What are you doing here?
You see what happens
when you let emotions run your life?
So what do you think?
Would you live here with me?
Who would I be to you here?
Why are you so scared?
Don't.
I'll take responsibility
for the damage to your daughter's life.
If you don't mind,
my son wants to marry Saikhim.
Gla!
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit