THIS FICTIONAL SERIES IS INTENDED
FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY
This life swap
could improve both our lives, you know.
Lita, explain yourself right now.
Whose house did you put me in?
Well, Khim?
Can you hear me, Khim?
You know very well
that I hate women like your mom the most.
But I'm not Mom.
Don't you talk back.
Sidewalk!
Damn it!
Whoever dares to make you cry
is very cruel.
Don't let anyone make you feel worthless.
Don't!
Will this person always be the one?
All we can do is hold on to the days
when that person was the one.
Gla!
Wake up! Don't make that stupid face.
You forget what you did yesterday?
Did you?
Who are you looking for?
Who is it?
Hey.
Go back the way you came.
I'm staying.
-Leave.
-I won't.
Who's there?
-It's not your business.
-Who's there?
-Hey.
-Come out right now!
Keep your voice down in here.
Are you hiding someone?
Come out. I said, come out!
-Be quiet.
-Come out.
You're not coming out?
I knew it, Gla.
You called me a skank.
You're just as bad.
It's been less than a day.
You've already hooked up with someone.
You should go now.
Is she conning you?
How long have you known her?
-Hey, shut up.
-Answer me.
Why? You got to beat up my man.
Don't protect her.
Why can't I beat up this girl too?
That's enough.
Hey. Come here!
I guess you're a spoiled brat
he got into bed.
You saw him driving a nice car,
so you let him have you?
Shut up.
What? Are you such a saint?
You're as awful as anyone.
And yet you left your husband
to come back here.
I came for my stuff.
I've seen enough of you to know better.
Just get out!
Hey! Don't forget to take your fee.
-Hey. Don't go.
-Hey!
If you don't mind sloppy seconds,
I'm happy to lease him to you.
If you want to get serious with him,
you should think twice,
or your life will be even more ruined.
Hey.
Serves you right. You ruined my life.
You don't get to start a new life.
Get out of here.
Stop ruining my life already.
Without me, your life'll be even worse.
You'll see.
Hey.
Hey, Miss… Miss what?
Damn. What's her name?
Miss!
Miss, wait!
I said, wait.
Please stay. Don't go anywhere.
About last night…
What about it?
-We were drunk.
-Of course.
-So what?
-Listen, okay?
Last night, everything happened so fast.
But I think… I have feelings for you.
I can't hear you.
I think I like you.
What did you say? I can't hear you.
Do you get it now?
Miss Saikhim.
Your father sent me to bring you home.
Are you hurt, miss?
No, I'm not.
I'm all right.
Why are the police here?
If you're safe,
there's no problem.
Take Miss Khim home.
I'll take care of things here.
-Yes, sir.
-Go on, miss.
Do you own that garage?
Yes, sir. What about it?
You're a suspect
in this abduction-for-ransom case.
Ransom?
Yes.
That's crazy, sir.
Why would I hold her to ransom?
My dear Miss Khim, where have you been?
And why did you run off like this?
I've been so worried, you know that?
Let's go inside.
Where's Dad, Auntie Oon?
He's already left.
What? You're back already?
Where have you been, Khim?
We've all been worried sick.
We couldn't eat or sleep.
Don't pull silly stunts like this again.
If you hadn't come home today,
Seen would've died of heartbreak.
I'm so sorry.
Take her to the shower.
Come on, Miss Khim.
The brat is back.
She looks like a total mess.
It's like she wants everyone to know
what she's been up to.
It's unbelievable.
She seemed so meek.
You'd never guess she'd do this.
And poor Uncle Seen protected her so well.
Maybe she's taking after her mother.
That's why she's so disobedient.
History is repeating itself.
If your poor uncle knew, he'd be livid.
This is great.
I can get into his good books.
Maybe he'll give me the Phuket project.
Stay tuned for the good news, Mom.
Yes, dear. Come here.
You should take a shower.
Let me help you.
Why are your clothes so messy?
After your shower,
come downstairs and eat something.
I'll set the table.
All right?
Sure.
Search and Arrest to Patrol. Do you copy?
I repeat, search the crime scene.
Collect every piece of evidence.
Interview local witnesses. Over.
Search and Arrest. Copy. Do you copy? Out.
Okay. Tell me everything.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I only know that her name's Khim.
But I'm not sure if it's her real name.
People who meet on dating apps
don't always use real names, you know.
I don't know her that well.
If that's true, why was she at your place?
My ex is renting out my house
and charging by the day.
I just ran into Khim one day.
You're seeing her casually,
and she's renting your ex's place.
What does that mean?
Is this really a coincidence?
Serious question.
What's her real age?
You can't charge me
with kidnap of a minor.
I assure you that she misled me.
I'd say I was her victim too.
You forced her to ask her family
for a ransom of one million baht.
That's insane. I know nothing about that.
She crashed my car.
She claimed she would pay for the repairs.
I didn't know how she'd find the money.
I never even wanted that money.
So you're telling me
that you didn't unlawfully detain her
to demand a ransom, right?
Why would I demand a ransom?
I don't even know who her family is.
But you brought her to a hotel
to make a scene.
Don't tell me you didn't know
she's the hotel owner's daughter.
I didn't know.
I swear, I really didn't know
that her family was so rich.
Or maybe you did know
that she was the Kidakarn heiress,
and that's why
you pretended to flirt with her, isn't it?
And once you knew she was rich,
you became her lover,
and you lured her there to meet you.
So she's not some biker's chick.
She's a spoiled rich kid.
You just want me to bring the phone?
Yes, I can do that.
The outfit from last night?
Yes, I can bring you everything.
The bra and underwear too?
Are you hungry, Miss Khim?
I've prepared food for you.
I came to let you know.
Once you're dressed,
please come downstairs.
Last night,
you two were at the garage.
Do you often bring strangers to your home?
We got on well,
so we talked for a long time.
You got on well.
But you don't know her real name.
Drunk people aren't known
for having rational conversations.
What were you doing all night?
I passed out.
I can't remember when.
Once we get the physical exam results,
we will see
how reliable your statements are.
To make sure, why not take my DNA sample?
Good idea.
So we'll know what to charge you with.
Unlawful detention,
extortion,
or sexual assault.
Or maybe you did all of them.
So that's fine with me.
We got on well,
so we talked for a long time.
You got on well.
But you don't know her real name.
Drunk people aren't known
for having rational conversations.
What were you doing all night?
I passed out. I can't remember when.
That man denied all the accusations.
He's been released.
I've checked Miss Khim's phone.
There were no messages to or from him.
Should I take her to the hospital
for a physical exam?
No.
It's time I tried trusting
the daughter I raised myself.
But watch Saikhim closely.
Don't let her contact such men again.
Even better, make them disappear
from her life completely.
You said you didn't like dating apps.
How did she get you into bed?
How dare you give me attitude?
This is your fault.
You flirted irresponsibly.
I almost went to jail for abducting her.
Well, how could I have known
that she was so rich?
You should be happy, bro.
She's way out of your league,
but you got lucky for once.
I hope that some day,
I'll be someone's lover too.
That girl is more like
my nemesis from a past life.
Don't you understand?
I could go to prison.
But she consented, right?
You didn't force her or anything.
You're missing the point.
If the police come sniffing around here,
and they see this evidence,
what else would they charge me with?
You should finish stamping
that vehicle identification number.
Deliver that car before the cops show up,
or I'll get pinned with more charges.
Go on.
Don't tell me
you didn't know
she's the hotel owner's daughter.
And once you knew she was rich,
you became her lover,
and you lured her there to meet you.
I guess you're a spoiled brat
he got into bed.
You saw him driving a nice car,
so you let him have you?
Shut up.
What? Are you such a saint?
You're as awful as anyone.
Your father sent me to bring you home.
Are you hurt, miss?
Will the rich kid be punished?
Why do I care? I should save myself first.
Did Dad get home already?
Yes, miss.
Wait, miss.
He's on a video conference
with overseas colleagues.
He can't see you right now.
We both live here
but don't see each other.
Yet the other side of the world sees him.
I think he's actually avoiding me.
Are you still mad at me?
Is that why you're avoiding me?
I don't have the time
to do stupid things like you do.
Actually, you're still mad at me.
You're bringing feelings into this?
You don't even dare to look me in the eye.
That's how I know you're still mad at me.
You can't keep pretending I don't exist.
Who was it
who tried to run away?
Who was it`
who cared about him and not about me?
The crook wants cash.
He's not a crook, Dad.
That money…
I asked for it just to test you.
How has he fooled you? How?
Why are you protecting him like this?
He hasn't fooled me.
You don't understand.
If he's such a good person,
why was he in juvenile detention?
Whom are you talking about?
The person you ran off with.
He's an ex-con.
He's a criminal.
He went to prison for assaulting someone.
You really can't tell?
So much for those good grades.
You almost got fooled by him.
He's been
in prison?
You see?
Because of your insolence,
you almost got fooled by him.
Wouldn't you be mad too?
I'm your father. I want the best for you.
But you don't listen to me.
You listen to that ex-con instead.
Go and stay in Phuket.
Don't let him get close to you.
GLA PRISON CASE
POLITICAL CRIME SUSPECT TURNS…
The person you ran off with.
He's an ex-con.
He's a criminal.
You really can't tell?
So much for those good grades.
You almost got fooled by him.
GLA PRISON CASE
POLITICAL CRIME SUSPECT TURNS…
SAIKHIM KIDAKARN,
A PRECOCIOUS BILLION-BAHT HEIRESS
Billion-baht heiress?
I'm an idiot.
Why didn't I suspect anything?
They've resorted to this?
Miss Khim, let's buy some snacks.
Come on. What would you like to eat?
-What would you like?
-I'll get you something.
-That looks delicious.
-Hi.
SANGUAN PHARMACY
-Which would you like?
-These ones.
All right.
Or maybe these ones.
EMERGENCY BIRTH CONTROL PILLS
WHAT TO EXPECT AFTER TAKING…
EMERGENCY PILL SAFETY
How may I help you?
You can ask me anything.
Here.
I see.
-These pills--
-Miss Khim?
What are you doing?
I came to buy motion sickness pills.
My dear, you should have asked me.
I brought some.
I've got everything in my bag.
-I'm sorry. We already have some.
-It's okay.
Let's go.
Back from your honeymoon?
You were with your lover, right?
I don't have a lover.
It's natural to have one.
Raging hormones. I understand.
But you should have better taste.
You know very well
that your dad is a snob.
You debased yourself with that lowlife,
so it serves you right
that you're being grounded here.
Wait, Khim.
Next time,
if you want a good guy,
let me know.
I'll find you one.
I heard Saikhim misbehaved so much
you had to fly here earlier.
What a shame.
I don't mind. I'm just worried about her.
Uncle Seen sent her to Phuket.
She's on probation.
So Khim is in Phuket now?
Yes. She might be there for a while,
until Uncle Seen can trust her again.
Girls with overprotective dads don't know
how to cope with men.
-Men?
-Hey.
Tan, do you really think
Khim came back because of her friend?
She's very sneaky.
The house-swapping story is a cover.
The truth is she probably just wanted
to come back to see her boyfriend.
Please excuse me.
I've never met that man, sir.
We've only talked via the app.
He lives in the area
near the house I rented,
and I wanted to introduce him to Saikhim
so she'd have
a friend to hang out with in Thailand.
And how do you know Saikhim?
Mr. Seen,
she's in that program you sponsor.
Every year, you contribute
tuition fees and presents.
And I organize rewards for good grades.
Miss Khim happened to see me
preparing those presents.
-Miss.
-Yes?
Do you like it?
Whose is it?
At first, Miss Khim thought
you had a secret love child,
so I explained that you sponsored
another child via the foundation.
In that case, let's give this to her.
I already have so many.
I'll take that one instead.
This one, miss?
I was so happy, sir,
that you gave me that expensive stuff,
so I wrote you letters to thank you.
But I guess you never got them
because Saikhim answered them all herself.
Ever since, Miss Khim said
that whatever birthday gift she got,
she wanted to give the same gift
to this sponsored child too.
Saikhim and I stayed in touch
via email for years.
Neither of us knew whom the other was
until Saikhim moved to my school.
We have been friends ever since.
So that's why you have the gall
to take advantage and steal her identity.
It's not like that.
You see, the two of us agreed
to swap houses
to find out what it would be like
to live different lives.
If you lie down with dogs,
you get up with fleas.
Isn't that the expression?
May I be frank with you, sir?
I used to really envy Saikhim
for having you as a dad.
But as our friendship grew over time,
I stopped envying her
because she has a life
that isn't truly lived.
She has everything,
but she's unhappy,
so she needs friends like me.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Seen is canceling your scholarship.
If you keep contacting Miss Khim,
we'll make sure you stop.
Don't you feel guilty yet?
Why should I feel guilty?
I didn't trick anyone.
You should have known
that what you did was wrong.
Maybe Khim is too innocent
to realize you're a phony.
My word.
You rich people,
you're so good at bitching…
I mean, insulting people.
Let me tell you something.
Khim's never been interested in you, dude.
If she were, I'd have heard her
gushing over Mr. Tantai.
Hey. Go back where you came from.
Stop looking around.
Khim isn't here.
Miss Khim.
Guess who turned up.
Tan.
I heard that you were here,
so I came to see you.
Dad was afraid I'd go out
and do more stupid things,
so he's grounded me here.
So, is something wrong, Khim?
Why did you run off like this?
I just wanted to live
like other people do.
But if you get lonely,
you can talk to me at any time, okay?
Hey, wanna go diving with me today?
I'll take you diving.
I don't know
if Dad would let me.
Auntie Oon?
May I go out on a boat with Tan?
Won't you wait for Mr. Seen first?
Auntie Oon, tell Mr. Seen not to worry.
I'll bring Khim back very soon.
I promise not to let her
do anything stupid.
-Come on.
-Then I'll come too.
It's okay, Auntie Oon.
Stay here and prepare dinner.
I'll be back this evening.
Tan?
I need to buy motion sickness pills.
-Sure.
-I'll be quick.
Who came to the garage?
Did they say who they were?
Good job moving that stuff in time.
Find out why they came.
I'll take care of the problem.
How can I help you this time?
Birth control again?
How long has it been
since you slept together?
Over 72 hours?
It's okay. I can help.
Take one of these pills immediately.
Take another one 12 hours later, okay?
This other product is new.
You only have to take one.
Which would you like?
-All of them.
-It's 60 baht per box, okay?
That's 240 baht for four boxes.
So there you are.
Let's talk right now.
Hey. You followed me here?
You gave me trouble.
Why'd you get me arrested?
Wait. You dropped your stuff.
Are you done, Khim?
-All done, Tan.
-Where are the pills?
I took them already.
We should go.
Bro, they're going through the cameras.
They're even taking the CCTV
from our clients' cars.
Luckily, I was prepared.
I already removed our CCTV's hard disk,
so they won't see
your videos from that night.
So she must have told them something.
I'll take care of this.
Hey.
Give me that.
Sir, stop.
Follow that car.
Stop. Stop right here.
The troublemaker's still walking free.
Do you need help? All right. Come on.
Wanna get changed? Come with me.
-Sure.
-Come on.
It'll be just me and her today.
Please tidy the kitchen.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
You… how did you get in here?
I came to see
how you manage to move on so happily.
You followed me all the way from Bangkok?
Hey. Did you tell anyone about that night?
What about that night?
You're making me say it?
That night that we…
that we…
that we did it.
Are you crazy?
I didn't tell anyone. Why would I?
The cops accused me
of luring and assaulting you.
So you came here to harass me?
Wait. Harass you? Watch what you say.
Hey! Watch out!
Look, you followed me everywhere.
Isn't that harassment?
I didn't harass you.
And I didn't lure you.
You know you were willing that day.
No.
I wasn't willing.
I see. So that's why, isn't it?
That's why they've come after me.
That night, I was drunk.
How could I know
things would end up that way?
We were equally drunk.
How can you blame it all on me?
I didn't tell anyone.
You're the one who acts suspicious.
Khim? What are you doing?
Khim?
Tan, I--
Don't tell--
I'm getting changed, Tan.
Well, if you need anything, ask me.
Yes, Tan, I--
-What are you doing?
-What? Hey--
I'll be right there, Tan.
Let go of my hand.
I don't even want to touch you.
So stop bothering me.
So tell the cops to leave me alone.
Drop the charges first.
Ask yourself
if you've got anything on your conscience.
If you don't have a record,
no one should suspect you.
Where are you going?
Let's talk properly.
Khim, are you all right?
I was asking him
which coral reef we were going to.
Would you like a drink?
Yes. Sure.
What do we have?
Drinking water. We have drinking water.
It's nice and safe.
Khim, let's go and enjoy the view.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Nice weather, right?
Yes.
Come down here.
-Come here first.
-No. Go away.
You come here.
Hello?
I set off a while ago. Yes, there is.
There's one attendant here.
He's not an employee?
What? If he isn't, why is he on my yacht?
You have to go right now.
I'll ask him myself
why he got on my yacht.
Hurry.
Hey, come here.
Listen.
Leave the yacht right now.
We can't let them see us together.
I'm not going until you promise
to settle this with your dad.
I already told you
that I never told anyone.
Even if you didn't, here's the evidence.
What woman takes these
when she hasn't slept with a man?
Well? You're going to land me in prison.
-Hey, give me those.
-No.
-Hey, give them to me.
-I won't. No.
We're already in deep trouble,
you know that?
Give them to me.
Promise me first.
Yes, Mr. Sansern?
Yes, I know we have a stowaway.
I haven't found him yet.
Sure, I'll check the deck again.
I beg you.
Can you find a way to leave the yacht
so that things don't get worse, please?
Where can I go? We're at sea.
Just jump in.
-Are you nuts?
-I'm not kidding.
-Go!
-Are you trying to kill me?
I can't help it. You asked for trouble.
If my dad knew that you followed me,
you'd be sorry.
-I'm not going.
-What?
Khim?
-Khim?
-He's here. Tan is here.
Do you want to die or what?
I told you to jump.
Are you trying to kill me?
-You have to go now!
-What?
Khim?
-Jump!
-I won't jump.
That's too bad.
Hey!
Khim?
-Yes?
-Have you seen the guy who came with us?
Not for a while, no.
He followed us on purpose.
He might be a con man.
-Really?
-The guards are coming to detain him.
Hello?
Sure.
Please don't die.
Congratulations.
You survived.
I don't think this is the end of it.
I'm so sorry we didn't see this coming.
-Did you find the suspect?
-Perhaps within an hour.
It would be a miracle
if he could swim for longer than that.
-Thank you.
-Sir.
Khim?
Don't be afraid. The police will get him.
-Right.
-Let's go.
Were there any problems?
No, sir. I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Please keep an eye out.
-He has fair skin and is about my height.
-Yes, sir.
Wait.
Where are you going?
When you land today,
you're supposed to report to the office.
Did you hear me?
I told you to report to the office.
Why haven't you fetched the car?
What are you waiting for?
Why is this car with you?
It's been mine since I was in England.
It was stolen
and given someone else's number plates.
I had to travel the world
to get this car back.
Imagine the pain of a mother
who is separated from her beloved child.
You understand that pain, don't you?
Who are you exactly?
I suppose I'm not the only one
you've caused trouble for.
Are you an informant?
I just want to say
that you owe me your life.
If I hadn't saved you,
you might have died by now.
Anyway,
as for the rest of your life,
will you give it to me or to them?
My poor Miss Khim, you must be so shaken.
At least you weren't
on the yacht alone with that intruder.
The rescue divers are searching for him.
They should be done tonight.
Dangerous people like him should get
the most severe punishment.
Hopefully, he won't die first.
Tan,
is there really no way
to get from there back to shore?
Well, it's risky
if you don't have flotation devices.
Damn. Are they informants for the cops?
If they were, I wouldn't be free now.
If I'm caught this time,
I'll surely go to prison.
Bro, things are looking bad here too.
They managed to get our CCTV hard disk.
What if they report on us
just to punish you
for popping his daughter's cherry?
Are they the Mafia?
Did I sleep with the Godfather's daughter?
What should we do?
They took all the evidence.
Are they trying to make me disappear?
Khem, try to find more information.
What businesses do the Kidakarns own here?
I won't be their sitting duck.
Yeah. All right.
The AC unit is this way.
Any updates?
Did you find the suspect?
You have my permission
to search the yacht for evidence anytime.
And if you detain the suspect,
I'm happy to identify him.
I never wanted to kill anyone.
Please be okay.
You have to survive.
Please survive.
Miss Khim, I noticed
that the AC wasn't working.
The unit is going to be cleaned.
Of course. Please go ahead.
I'll open it.
Please come in.
Be thorough.
We need it to work since it's summer.
Check everything carefully.
When you're done, find me downstairs.
-Sure.
-Good.
It's getting late.
They might call off the search.
Right.
It's lucky no one got hurt.
So, Khim,
are you still frightened?
Well, I won't rest easy until we find him.
Awful, isn't it?
Why are there
such shady characters around these days?
This is why
you shouldn't look for trouble.
You can't trust anyone these days.
It's finished.
All right. Wait a second.
What a nice life.
She's an actual princess.
Sinner.
Wait. You're not dead?
I… I didn't mean to do it.
I'm sorry that you didn't kill me.
You really survived?
You can't kill me that easily.
I can't let you get away with it.
Wait. How did you get in here?
What if you get caught?
Since I survived,
I might as well check out
how rich people live.
You have to go, or you'll get caught.
At least I won't be alone this time.
We'll go down together.
I thought they came to clean the AC.
But they actually installed spy cameras.
For keeping an eye on you, I guess.
Are you on vacation, or are you in prison?
My dad resorted to this?
It will be even worse
if he sees what's on that hard disk.
What hard disk?
The CCTV hard disk
from the garage that night.
If there's a camera,
Dad will see--
If you don't want to kill us both,
go get those files.
If he sees our videos,
you might never leave this room again.
They must have put
the CCTV files in there.
His spies have watched
the garage for days.
Once they knew I was gone,
they barged in and seized everything.
I bet they'll pin charges on me.
Sweet-talk your dad.
Get all the evidence.
Don't sabotage my future.
Dad?
Is this a good time to talk?
Why?
I want to watch a movie with you.
Sure.
Which one should we watch?
I think you should pick one.
Here.
That looks good.
It's the sequel of that other one we saw.
Are you sure
you want me to choose?
Any movie is good
if I get to watch it with you.
What about this one?
Don't think I don't know
about the lies you've told me.
You've behaved recklessly and hopelessly.
What's so good about him
that you can't resist?
Do you like
how he recorded this to expose you?
Is this the life you want?
This disgusting life?
You slut.
You're good-for-nothing.
What? Are you embarrassed?
You weren't then.
And today, on the yacht,
don't think I don't know it was him.
The CCTV
recorded him hanging around that area.
You knew it was him,
but you didn't tell Tantai.
You brought him on the yacht.
That attached to him, are you?
How did he do this to you?
What did I do wrong
to make you turn out like this?
Saikhim didn't know I followed her.
What does he mean?
Did you bring him here?
No, I came here.
Enough. That's enough. Please stop.
Get away.
Why did you trick her?
I didn't trick her.
You mean she's stupid enough
to just believe you?
You raised her, but you can't tell?
She feels nothing for me.
She hates me.
She insults me,
and she'd even kill me.
She's not in love with me.
Then why'd you dare mess with her?
You dragged me into this.
You came after me.
You act like you're so superior.
But you're such a disaster
that she lost faith in you.
What did you say?
She hates herself when she's with you.
You never make anyone feel good enough.
She didn't fall for any man.
She just feels good about herself
when she's with someone else.
Have you ever made her like herself
like when she's with me?
You've gone too far!
Dad!
Stop. Please stop.
-Dad--
-Get off.
Dad! Stop! Dad, that's enough.
It's not his fault. He did nothing wrong.
I was the one who went to him.
Dad, look at this. Do you see this?
It's not his fault.
I went to see him. Do you see?
That's enough!
That's enough.
Have you lost your mind?
He didn't try to trick me.
He opened my eyes to the truth.
Opened your eyes?
Think he's sincere with you, do you?
If you didn't use the Kidakarn name,
what man would be interested in you?
Remember this.
No man would be interested in you
if you didn't have my fortune!
Get out.
Get the hell out!
Stay out of my life.
Go!
You dare show up here?
-Why are you here?
-To see my girl.
You scumbag.
Prom!
Take him away!
Come on.
Prom, what are you doing?
Prom, don't!
Prom!
-Get away!
-Why isn't he moving? Is he okay?
Prom, what are you going to do?
Prom!
That's enough!
Gla!
Prom, that's enough!
Who do you think you are?
Your cousin-in-law?
Prom!
That's enough, Prom!
Dad!
You're letting Prom kill him?
Tell him to stop!
When he humiliated me, you didn't care.
You dare call me cousin again?
See? See what a scumbag he is?
Isn't what you're doing just as barbaric?
You're treating him like he's not human.
Prom, that's enough!
-Prom, enough--
-Why?
Why are you so desperate
to save this scum?
Don't you know
he wants five million for the video?
It's not true.
He was going to blackmail you.
I had to pay five million for the video.
It's not true!
He already took the five million,
but he's still messing with you.
Isn't five million enough?
He held you hostage,
and he manipulated us to make us fall out
so you'd see me negatively.
Liar!
-Liar!
-Shut up!
I'm the liar?
I've been with you all your life.
Who is he? How well do you know him?
You still can't see how deceptive he is?
Now will you leave my cousin alone?
Stop using women's cash!
Enough! That's enough.
Let's end things here.
It's not worth it for either of us.
Just pretend that we've never met.
Let's not ruin our lives even more.
Did you hear that?
That's how much you disgust her.
Get out of Saikhim's life
if you still want to live.
You really think I'm that disgraceful?
You said you'd give your life to me,
so why are you about to die again?
I've had bad luck with women lately.
Come with me, and we'll make our own luck.
FIVE MILLION BAHT
Khem.
You had the check?
It's your fee
for leaving his daughter alone.
They left it when they took the CCTV.
Why the hell did you accept it?
-Damn it!
-Bro, calm down!
Bro! Hey!
Do you think it's worth
what I've been through?
Well, who said you had to go alone
and let them destroy you?
You think you're a pro boxer?
If I take this money,
it means I admit
that I really wanted to use her for money.
Just think of it
as compensation for your injuries.
Would you really sacrifice
your honor for money?
Is it different
from how we work for rich people's money?
We make money
from these sinners' obsessions.
But this check was earned
when we ruined a good woman's future.
While that poor girl protected me,
you rubbed salt in my wounds.
If you didn't take the check,
her dad wouldn't like you anyway.
But at least Saikhim wouldn't look
like she got conned by a man.
She'd be a beloved daughter
who could face up to her dad.
This five-million-baht check
could ruin her life.
She doesn't deserve
to be pitied because of me.
Mr. Seen is canceling your scholarship.
If you keep contacting Miss Khim,
we'll make sure that you stop.
-Khim?
-Lita!
-Khim, get out!
-Khim!
-Lita!
SHARING IS CARING ROTI
Dad! Stop! Dad, that's enough.
It's not his fault.
I was the one who went to him.
Enough! That's enough.
New member.
Awesome.
-I think I'm pregnant.
-What?
If I'm really pregnant,
what can I do, Lita?
Wait, Khim.
Try to stay calm.
How can you be pregnant? Whose is it?
Well, you know how we swapped houses?
Don't tell me you got pregnant
with one of the guys I picked on the app.
Lita.
If I'm really pregnant,
my dad will definitely kill me.
Maybe it won't be that bad.
Stay calm for now.
Dad watches my every move, Lita.
I'm so stressed out.
Can you help me, Lita?
I want to know if I'm really pregnant.
Okay, Khim, I'm about to finish my shift.
Can you discreetly come and see me?
Don't freak out. Let's make sure first.
Stay calm, I'll be there soon.
Okay.
Is this real?
What have I done?
The steam room, please.
What do I do now?
Why is this happening to me?
Try to stay calm, Khim.
Wanna do another test?
Just in case.
I never should have let this happen, Lita.
-How could I let this happen?
-It's not your fault, Khim.
It's my fault.
I brought those men into your life.
I should have seen through them.
Now we're in this mess.
Lita.
I'm scared.
If my dad knew,
he'd definitely kill me, Lita.
He doesn't have to know.
We…
we'll figure this out together.
We can figure this out together.
Okay?
I share the blame.
I'll help you take care of it.
Don't be scared, Khim.
Hey.
Are you Saikhim's friend?
So you're here. What do you want?
Can I have Saikhim's number?
Damn you. Who do you think you are?
So you know about us?
-I want to return--
-Shove it.
Saikhim told me
how much she wants to kill you.
If she could,
she'd kill you more than just once.
Just listening to her
makes me want to castrate you.
You're both awful and fertile.
May demons curse you with infertility.
The world doesn't need your kind.
That's so harsh.
Wanna do another test?
Just in case.
When you said…
NEXT EPISODE
… "Trust me with your life,"
did you mean that,
or was it just something cool to say?
You'd better watch out.
My uncle
won't let you get away with it.
But if you stay here,
your dad will find you.
-Hey!
-You can't come up here, sir!
Don't go there.
-I said, no!
-Get out now!
You can't go up there.
This scumbag wants to use this kid
to manipulate Saikhim.
Even if I had nothing but my body,
a dad like you couldn't beat me
because you never let her be free,
so she flies back to me, the scumbag.
Is it okay?
Subtitle translation by: Tanchira Arjinkit